{"Question": "Q: 393 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 435", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n2 + 5 = 7\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1648", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 70 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 504", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 4 = 34\n1200 + 34 = 1234\n1234 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 136", "Answer": "A: 541", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n5 + 30 = 35\n500 + 35 = 535\n535 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 8 = 12\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 334", "Answer": "A: 553", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 30 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 372", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 70 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 628", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 3\n1483 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1579", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 9 = 79\n1500 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 353", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 50 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 422", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n15 + 20 = 35\n1200 + 35 = 1235\n1235 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 247", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 40 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 8\n638 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 766", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 60 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 593", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 90 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 5 = 845\n845 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 482", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 267 + 572", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 109", "Answer": "A: 400", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n91 + 9 = 100\n300 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 222", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 2 = 7\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1568", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 5 = 8\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1478", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 240", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 287", "Answer": "A: 793", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n6 + 80 = 86\n700 + 86 = 786\n786 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 338", "Answer": "A: 471", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 30 = 60\n3 + 8 = 11\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 405", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n9 + 5 = 14\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 3 = 6\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1722", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 70 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 550", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1558", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n22 + 20 = 42\n1000 + 42 = 1042\n1042 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n3 + 5 = 8\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 136", "Answer": "A: 410", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 30 = 100\n4 + 6 = 10\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 244", "Answer": "A: 631", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 40 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 953 + 225", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 437", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n1100 + 60 = 1160  \n1160 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 7 = 27\n1000 + 27 = 1027\n1027 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 5\n1390 + 1\n139"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 553", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 50 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n9 + 40 = 49\n1400 + 49 = 1449\n1449 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 419", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1514", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 545", "Answer": "A: 681", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n600 + 70 = 670  \n670 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n8 + 6 = 14\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 348", "Answer": "A: 840", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 40 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 10 = 840\n840"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 290", "Answer": "A: 493", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n3 + 90 = 93\n400 + 93 "}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1646", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n18 + 20 = 38  \n1600 + 38 = 1638  \n1638 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 769 + 132", "Answer": "A: 901", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9 = 899\n899 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 401", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 1 = 41\n500 + 41 = 541\n541 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 207", "Answer": "A: 597", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 7 = 97\n500 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 179", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1 + 9 = 10\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 229", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 20 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3\n813 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 182", "Answer": "A: 336", "Explanation": "150 + 180 = 330\n4 + 2 = 6\n330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 104", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 4 = 34\n900 + 34 = 934\n934 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 394", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 7 = 57\n1400 + 57 = 1457\n1457 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 185", "Answer": "A: 446", "Explanation": "200 + 60 = 260\n260 + 1 = 261\n100 + 80 = 180\n180 + 5 = 185\n260 + 180 = 440\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 236", "Answer": "A: 337", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n1 + 30 = 31\n300 + 31 = 331\n331 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 434", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 30 = 70\n9 + 4 = 13\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 245", "Answer": "A: 903", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 261", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6 = 1146\n1146 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 431", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1550", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 236", "Answer": "A: 515", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n9 + 6 = 15\n500 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n1300 + 60 = 1360  "}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 462", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n3 + 2 = 5\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 144", "Answer": "A: 340", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 40 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1628", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n2 + 6 = 8  \n1500 + 120 = 1620  \n1620 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1 + 3 = 4\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 103", "Answer": "A: 726", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 3 = 23\n700 + 23 = 723\n723 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 242", "Answer": "A: 427", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 5 + 2 = 427"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1651", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 6 = 46\n1600 + 46 = 1646\n1646 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 2 = 4\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 559", "Answer": "A: 701", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 50 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 237", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3 = 1303\n1303 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1579", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 90 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n900 + 150 = 1050  \n1050 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 439", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 567", "Answer": "A: 747", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 749", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 241", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n4 + 40 = 44  \n1100 + 44 = 1144  \n1144 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 2\n1100 + 2 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 195 + 121", "Answer": "A: 316", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 20 = 110\n110 + 5 = 115\n200 + 115 = 315\n315 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n17 + 40 = 57  \n1200 + 57"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 470", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 70 = 80\n900 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 211", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n20 + 10 = 30  \n1100 + 30 = 1130  \n1130 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 693", "Answer": "A: 1655", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 249", "Answer": "A: 432", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n3 + 9 = 12\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 186", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 8 = 818\n818 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 553", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 10 = 1340"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 596", "Answer": "A: 1431", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 90 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 703", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "150 + 700 = 850\n2 + 3 = 5\n850 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 628", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "150 + 600 = 750\n3 + 20 = 23\n750 + 23 = 773\n773 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 4 = 1034\n1034 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 183", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 80 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 359", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 244", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n3 + 4 = 7\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 281", "Answer": "A: 641", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n500 + 140 = 640  \n640 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1376", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 763", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 6 = 76\n1600 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 594", "Answer": "A: 722", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 254 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4 + 9\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n2 + 1 = 3\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 710 + 131", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n3 + 3 = 6\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 198", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n3 + 98 = 101  \n700 + 101 = 801"}
{"Question": "Q: 949 + 400", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n49\n1300 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 181", "Answer": "A: 468", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 1 = 8\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 60 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 1 + 5 = 1456"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1916", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1800 + 110 = 1910  \n1910 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 411", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 114", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n10 + 4 = 14\n800 + 14 = 814\n814 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 202", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n14 + 2 = 16\n1000 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n9 + 4 = 13\n1500 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1664", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 80 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n9 + 5 = 14\n1650 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 312", "Answer": "A: 614", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n2 + 12 = 14\n600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 231", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 30 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1622", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 30 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1848", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n10 + 30 = 40\n1 + 7 = 8\n1800 + 40 = 1840\n1840 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1851", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n7 + 40 = 47\n1800 + 47 = 1847\n1847 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 496", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 191", "Answer": "A: 767", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 90 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 1 \n760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 104", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 4 = 34\n900 + 34 = 934\n934 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1674", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 90 = 160\n9 + 5 = 14\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 340", "Answer": "A: 474", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n34 + 40 = 74  \n400 + 74  "}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 180", "Answer": "A: 568", "Explanation": "300 + 80 = 380  \n88 + 80 = 168  \n380 + 168  \n380 + 180"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1690", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 60 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 10 = 1690"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 234", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 4 + 5 = 789"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1319", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 292", "Answer": "A: 646", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 90 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 714", "Answer": "A: 1344", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 591", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 248", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 9  \n1090 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 851", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n18 + 50 = 68\n900 + 68 = 968\n968 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 334", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n5 + 30 = 35\n1000 + 35 = 1035\n1035 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 282", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 2 = 82\n800 + 82 = 882\n882 + 81"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n1300 + 90 = 1390  \n1390 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 379", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 520", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1601", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n10 + 80 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 332", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 2 = 9\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 370", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n49 + 70 = 119  \n600 + 119"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 498", "Answer": "A: 616", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 90 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 8\n600 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 466", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 512", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 10 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1736", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 80 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 268", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 410", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 10 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 286", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 80 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 6\n510 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 524", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 359", "Answer": "A: 478", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n10 + 50 = 60  \n9 + 9 = 18  \n400 + 60 = 460  \n460 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 114", "Answer": "A: 944", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 10 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 327", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n8 + 7 = 15\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 60 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1458", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 186", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 80 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 242", "Answer": "A: 461", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n10 + 40 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 611", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1558", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 90 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 459", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n9 + 9 = 18\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 227", "Answer": "A: 812", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n5 + 7 = 12\n800 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 395", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1791", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 50 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 232", "Answer": "A: 787", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 30 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n15 + 40 = 55\n1400 + 55 = 1455\n1455 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 188", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n2 + 80 = 82\n900 + 82 = 982\n982 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 397", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n8 + 90 = 98  \n1100 + 98 = 1198  \n1198 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1770", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n1600 + 160 = 1760  \n1760 + 10 = 1770  \n1770 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1370", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 40 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 10 = 1370\n1370"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 156", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 391", "Answer": "A: 549", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 90 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 184", "Answer": "A: 317", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n200 + 110 = 310  \n310 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1776", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 9 = 16\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1012", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n4 + 8 = 12\n1000 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 343", "Answer": "A: 605", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 40 = 100\n2 + 3 = 5\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 331", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 8 +1 = 899"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 188", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n500 + 140 = 640  \n640 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 476", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 381", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 80 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n6 + 7 = 13\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1365", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n9 + 6 = 15\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 2 = 32\n1500 + 32 = 1532\n1532 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 111", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 358", "Answer": "A: 609", "Explanation": "250 + 350 = 600\n1 + 8 = 9\n600 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n90 + 7 = 97  \n1600 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 407", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 0 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 658", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1778", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n19 + 50 = 69\n1700 + 69 = 1769\n1769 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 414", "Answer": "A: 1413", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n90 + 10 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 9 + 4 = 1413"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 698", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 563", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 104", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 4 = 54\n900 + 54 = 954\n954 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n9 + 90 = 99\n1300 + 99 = 1399\n1399 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1772", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 50 = 70\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 604", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 4 = 84\n800 + 84 = 884\n884 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 198", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 1 + 8 = 889"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 426", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 139", "Answer": "A: 502", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 30 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 285", "Answer": "A: 400", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n15 + 80 = 95\n300 + 95 = 395\n395 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 287", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6 \n1120 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 864", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n3 + 60 = 63\n900 + 63 = 963\n963 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 60 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n9 + 5 = 14\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 597", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 10 = 1360"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 314", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 14 = 24\n700 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 125", "Answer": "A: 313", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 20 = 100\n8 + 5 = 13\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 215", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 289", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 80 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 429", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 20 = 60\n9 + 4 = 13\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 9 = 1569"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n99 + 11 = 110  \n1200 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 420", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 108", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 8 = 78\n900 + 78 = 978\n978 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6 \n1000 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 715", "Answer": "A: 1688", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n1600 + 80 = 1680  \n1680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1798", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n9 + 80 = 89\n1700 + 89 = 1789\n1789 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 212", "Answer": "A: 825", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n10 + 10 = 20\n800 + 20 = 820\n820 + 3\n820 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 302", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 2 = 62\n600 + 62 = 662\n662 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 10 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 7 = 1357\n1357 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 225", "Answer": "A: 730", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n5 + 20 = 25\n700 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 207", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 7 = 37\n700 + 37 = 737\n737 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 237", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 320", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600 \n40 + 20 = 60 \n600 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n31 + 30 = 61\n1400 + 61 = 1461\n1461 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 594", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n9 + 4 = 13\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 428", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n7 + 8 = 15\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 4 = 74\n1400 + 74"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1547", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n20 + 20 = 40\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 678 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 292", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1919", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 80 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 30 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8 = 1318"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 680", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 168", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 1  \n1000 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 370", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n45 + 70 = 115  \n700 + 115 = 815  "}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 479", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n7 + 9 = 16\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n11 + 15 = 26\n1200 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1691", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n5 + 80 = 85\n1600 + 85 = 1685\n1685 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 688", "Answer": "A: 888", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n88 \n800 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 119", "Answer": "A: 220", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n1 + 19 = 20\n200 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 302", "Answer": "A: 755", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 2 = 52\n700 + 52 = 752\n752 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 70 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5 = 1415\n1415 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 470", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n12 + 70 = 82\n1200 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 347", "Answer": "A: 704", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7\n7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 70 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6 = 1016\n1016 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 8 = 18\n1100 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 129", "Answer": "A: 529", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n29\n500 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n53 + 70 = 123  \n1000 + 123 = 1123  \n1123 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 121 + 506", "Answer": "A: 627", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 6 = 26\n600 + 26 = 626\n626 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1598", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n1500 + 90 = 1590  \n1590 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 567", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 60 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 245", "Answer": "A: 1000", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n3 + 6 = 9\n1300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 4 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 405", "Answer": "A: 523", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 5 = 15\n500 + 15 = 515\n515 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 338", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n6 + 30 = 36\n500 + 36 = 536\n536 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1784", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 90 = 180\n3 + 1 = 4\n1600 + 180 = 1780\n1780 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1747", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 70 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 229", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 562", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n7 + 2 = 9\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 597", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n25 + 90 = 115\n1100 + 115 = 1215\n1215 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 143", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 40 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1783", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 50 = 70\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n1000 + 80 = 1080  \n1080 + 9  \n1080 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n7 + 7 = 14  \n1100 + 90 = 1190  \n1190 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1643", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n30 + 7 = 37  \n1600 + 37 = 1637  \n1637 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1869", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 70 = 160\n8 + 1 = 9\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 185", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 3 = 1123\n1123 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n1 + 30 = 31\n1700 + 31 = 1731\n1731 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1795", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 9 = 99\n1600 + 99 = 1699\n1699 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1610", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 80 = 110\n1500 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 154", "Answer": "A: 288", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 50 = 80\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 775", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 663", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n700 + 80 = 780  \n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 282", "Answer": "A: 487", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n5 + 80 = 85\n400 + 85 = 485\n485 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 4 + 6 = 1020"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1304", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n2 + 2 = 4\n1300 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 822", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n18 + 20 = 38\n900 + 38 = 938\n938 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 202", "Answer": "A: 767", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n5 + 2 = 7\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 327", "Answer": "A: 576", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n9 + 7 = 16\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 30 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 401", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n35 + 1 = 36\n1000 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n3 + 2 = 5\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 656", "Answer": "A: 1541", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 50 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1739", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 70 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 435", "Answer": "A: 663", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 489", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 10 = 860\n860"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1603", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 0 = 90\n5 + 8 = 13\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 60 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370 \n1370 + 8 = 1378"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 175", "Answer": "A: 436", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1 + 5 = 6\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 30 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 165", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n99 + 60 = 159  \n1000 + 159 = 1159  \n1159 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n15 + 1 = 16\n1300 + 16 "}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 581", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n2 + 80 = 82\n900 + 82 = 982\n982 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 610", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1544", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 975 + 220", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1789", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 70 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 149", "Answer": "A: 461", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 40 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 11 = 461"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n10 + 10 = 20\n7 + 6 = 13\n1700 + 20 = 1720\n1720 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1079", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 0 = 70\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n8 + 80 = 88\n1200 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 312", "Answer": "A: 862", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n91 + 1 = 92\n1000 + 92"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 224", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 323", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n8 + 3 = 11\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 255", "Answer": "A: 554", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n90 + 50 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 800", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n26  \n900 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 693", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n3 + 90 = 93\n1400 + 93 = 1493\n1493 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n1 + 5 = 6  \n1300 + 140 = 1440  \n1440 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 355", "Answer": "A: 616", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 50 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 397", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n47 + 90 = 137\n600 + 137 = 737\n737 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 311", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 160", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 60 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 290", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1422", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 207", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n15 + 7 = 22\n1000 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 171", "Answer": "A: 335", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 70 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 5 = 335"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1692", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 50 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 559", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 3\n860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n7 + 30 = 37\n1400 + 37 = 1437\n1437 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 164", "Answer": "A: 457", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 60 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1369", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 10 = 60 \n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 687", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 7 = 87\n800 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1885", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n10 + 60 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n1800 + 70 = 1870\n1870 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 440", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 445", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 40 = 120\n1 + 5 = 6\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n5 + 50 = 55\n1300 + 55 = 1355\n1355 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1813", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 50 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1503", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 387", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n900 + 170 = 1070  \n1070 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 476", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 70 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1439", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 3 = 33\n1400 + 33 = 1433\n1433 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 564", "Answer": "A: 993", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n9 + 4 = 13\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 479", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 10 = 870"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 514", "Answer": "A: 623", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n9 + 14 = 23\n600 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 318", "Answer": "A: 693", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n5 + 8 = 13\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1535", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1857", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 90 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n11 + 89 = 100\n1000 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1771", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 40 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1494", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n1400 + 90 = 1490  \n1490 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 138", "Answer": "A: 448", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 30 = 40\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 565", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 804", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n20 + 4 = 24\n900 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 491", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n7 + 90 = 97\n900 + 97 = 997\n997 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 306", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 6 = 86\n900 + 86 = 986\n986 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1542", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n6 + 30 = 36\n1500 + 36 = 1536\n1536 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1865", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n40 + 20 = 60  \n3 + 2 = 5  \n1800 + 60 = 1860  \n1860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 2 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 462", "Answer": "A: 750", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n600 + 140 = 740  \n740 + 10 = 750"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 40 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 685", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 7 = 957"}
{"Question": "Q: 539 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 471", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 338", "Answer": "A: 838", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 8 = 38\n800 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 394 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1873", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 30 = 70\n1800 + 70 = 1870\n1870 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 283", "Answer": "A: 405", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 80 = 100\n2 + 3 = 5\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n6 + 30 = 36\n1000 + 36 = 1036\n1036 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1030", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 40 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 10 = 1030"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n11 + 50 = 61\n1000 + 61 = 1061\n1061 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 232", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 179", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 6  \n1026 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 70 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n6 + 8 = 14\n1600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n9 + 4 = 13\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 690", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 90 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 169", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 60 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 80 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n3 + 3 = 6\n1320 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 151", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n11 + 50 = 61\n900 + 61 = 961\n961 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 299", "Answer": "A: 562", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n3 + 9 = 12  \n400 + 150 = 550  \n550 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 225", "Answer": "A: 518", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n400 + 110 = 510  \n510 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 275", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "150 + 850 = 1000\n2 + 8 = 10\n1000 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1886", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 2 = 82\n1800 + 82 = 1882\n1882 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1555", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n50 + 5 = 55\n1500 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 659", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 50 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 126", "Answer": "A: 722", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6 = 716 \n716 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 442", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n7 + 2 = 9\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1416", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 6\n1416"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 653", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n3 + 50 = 53\n700 + 53 = 753\n753 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 561", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 40 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 473", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n3 + 70 = 73\n800 + 73 = 873\n873 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 423", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 405", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n19 + 5 = 24\n900 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 371", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 255", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9 + 5 = 1004"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 677", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n6 + 70 = 76\n1400 + 76 = 1476\n1476 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 113", "Answer": "A: 644", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 517", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 110", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n10 + 10 = 20  \n900 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 501", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 0 = 20\n800 + 20 = 820\n820 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 469", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3\n813 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 389", "Answer": "A: 631", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 80 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 9\n620 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 30 = 60\n9 + 7 = 16\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 631", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 446", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 123", "Answer": "A: 273", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 20 = 70\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 317", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 130", "Answer": "A: 304", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n200 + 100 = 300  \n300 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1393", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n83 + 10 = 93\n1300 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1520", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 20 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 261", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 60 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 249", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 126", "Answer": "A: 401", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 20 = 90\n5 + 6 = 11\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n3 + 5 = 8\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 20 = 40\n40 + 9 = 49\n1100 + 49 = 1149\n1149 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 329", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n94 + 20 = 114\n800 + 114 = 914\n914 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 516", "Answer": "A: 713", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 10 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n7 + 6 = 13\n700 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1811", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 20 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n4 + 7 = 11\n1800 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n8 + 30 = 38\n1400 + 38 = 1438\n1438 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 205", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 5 = 45\n600 + 45 = 645\n645 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 316", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n8 + 6 = 14\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1810", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 20 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 719", "Answer": "A: 891", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n10 + 20 = 30\n1700 + 30 = 1730\n1730 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 520", "Answer": "A: 890", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 393", "Answer": "A: 641", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 655", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 1 + 5 = 886"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n3 + 30 = 33\n1000 + 33 = 1033\n1033 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n3 + 11 = 14\n1100 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1757", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 80 = 150\n6 + 1 = 7\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 268", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n5 + 7 = 12\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 351", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 221", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n5 + 20 = 25\n1000 + 25 = 1025\n1025 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 276", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n6 + 70 = 76\n900 + 76 = 976\n976 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1756", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 30 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 400", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n500 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1646", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1577", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n8 + 9 = 17\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 275", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 70 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 5 = 755\n755 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 329", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n6 + 9 = 15\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 435", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "150 + 400 = 550\n4 + 30 = 34\n550 + 34 = 584\n584 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 495", "Answer": "A: 848", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 90 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 614", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 10 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 4 = 744\n744 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 = 1375\n1375 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 478", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 7 \n660 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 747", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n6 + 40 = 46\n900 + 46 = 946\n946 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 511", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n15 + 10 = 25\n1200 + 25 = 1225\n1225 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 390", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 90 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 504", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 4 = 24\n900 + 24 = 924\n924 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 554", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 353", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 180", "Answer": "A: 482", "Explanation": "300 + 180 = 480\n480 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 60 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n6 + 30 = 36\n1100 + 36 = 1136\n1136 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n75 + 50 = 125\n1000 + 125"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 123", "Answer": "A: 510", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 3 = 10\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 10 = 510"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n4 + 30 = 34\n1000 + 34 = 1034\n1034 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1 + 8 = 9\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 240", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1583", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n10 + 70 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 284", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n5 + 4 = 9\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 4 = 9\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 204", "Answer": "A: 749", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 4 = 44\n700 + 44 = 744\n744 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 270", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 70 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n9 + 8 = 17\n1300 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 448", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 40 = 130\n8 + 8 = 16\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n19 + 40 = 59\n1000 + 59 = 1059\n1059 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 180", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 80 = 160\n200 + 160 = 360\n360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1827", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 50 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 4 = 1824\n1824 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 416", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n9 + 6 = 15\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n10 + 90 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n1 + 50 = 51\n1300 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 448", "Answer": "A: 606", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 40 = 90\n8 + 8 = 16\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1371", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 294", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7\n1110 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 412", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n900 + 20 = 920\n920 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 5 = 12\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1748", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 60 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n28 + 40 = 68  \n1600 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n11 + 90 = 101\n1000 + 101 = 1101\n1101 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1507", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1589", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 90 = 180\n1400 + 180 = 1580\n1580 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1484", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1587", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 10 = 80\n4 + 3 = 7\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n40 + 50 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 253", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n2 + 50 = 52\n1100 + 52 = 1152\n1152 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1738", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 90 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 693", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1416", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 10 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8\n8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 30 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 309", "Answer": "A: 536", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 9 = 29\n500 + 29 = 529\n529 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 481", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 206", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 6 = 56\n900 + 56 = 956\n956 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 5 = 1395"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 267", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 3\n820 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 360", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 8 = 68\n1200 + 68 = 1268\n1268 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 512", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n10 + 10 = 20  \n7 + 2 = 9  \n1400 + 20 = 1420  \n1420 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 423", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 3 = 6\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 522", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 170", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 541", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n2 + 40 = 42\n800 + 42 = 842\n842 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 8 = 1038"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 335", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 325", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 20 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 561", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 355", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 553", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n8 + 90 = 98\n1200 + 98 = 1298\n1298 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 437", "Answer": "A: 678", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 30 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 1 = 671\n671 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 742", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n1 + 40 = 41\n800 + 41 = 841\n841 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 80 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n5 + 7 = 12\n1500 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 362", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 60 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 10 = 960"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 380", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 167", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 60 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 7 \n630 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n5 + 80 = 85\n1500 + 85 = 1585\n1585 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1518", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n18 + 0 = 18\n1500 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 783", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3 = 1023\n1023 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 432", "Answer": "A: 712", "Explanation": "280 + 400 = 680  \n32 + 0 = 32  \n680 + 32  "}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 176", "Answer": "A: 451", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 6 = 11\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 103", "Answer": "A: 280", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n70 + 3 = 73\n200 + 73 = 273\n273 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 50 = 70\n5 + 1 = 6\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1709", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 20 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n7 + 2 = 9\n1700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 354", "Answer": "A: 590", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 6 = 586\n586 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 542", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 7 + 2 = 819"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 171", "Answer": "A: 341", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n70 + 70 = 140\n200 + 140 = 340\n340 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 0 = 60\n3 + 5 = 8\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 415", "Answer": "A: 558", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 10 = 50\n3 + 5 = 8\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 330", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n9 + 30 = 39\n900 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 249", "Answer": "A: 402", "Explanation": "150 + 200 = 350\n3 + 40 = 43\n350 + 43 = 393\n393 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n13 + 1 = 14\n1300 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 3 + 1 = 1324"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n3 + 30 = 33\n1000 + 33 = 1033\n1033 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 349", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 40 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 178", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 10 = 690"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 271", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n6 + 70 = 76\n600 + 76 = 676\n676 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 185", "Answer": "A: 679", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 80 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 9 = 679\n679 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 192", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n2 + 2 = 4\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1805", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 40 = 100\n3 + 2 = 5\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 140", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n5 + 40 = 45\n600 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 209", "Answer": "A: 368", "Explanation": "150 + 200 = 350\n9 + 9 = 18\n350 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 420", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 412 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1673", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 20 = 60\n4 + 9 = 13\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 708", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 8 = 98\n1200 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 397", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 90 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6 + 7 = 913"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 1 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 249", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 40 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 247", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n9 + 40 = 49  \n1000 + 49 = 1049\n1049 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 601", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n24 + 1 = 25\n1400 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 213", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n10 + 10 = 20\n2 + 3 = 5\n700 + 20 = 720\n720 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1679", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 60 = 70\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 457", "Answer": "A: 577", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n20 + 50 = 70  \n500 + 70 = 570  \n570 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 553", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 432", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 450", "Answer": "A: 955", "Explanation": "500 + 450 = 950\n950 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 240", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n25 + 40 = 65\n500 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 134", "Answer": "A: 335", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n1 + 30 = 31\n300 + 31 = 331\n331 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 594", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n900 + 130 = 1030  \n1030 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 449", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1405", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 20 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6\n1396 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 819", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n900 + 20 = 920\n920 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 210", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 10 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 323", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 147", "Answer": "A: 301", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 40 = 90\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 269", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 161", "Answer": "A: 474", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 60 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 473", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 70 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1654", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 80 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 676", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n700 + 90 = 790  \n790 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 381", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 = 921\n921 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 447 + 331", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 30 = 70\n7 + 1 = 8\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 537", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 30 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8 \n1290 + 7 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 6 = 86\n86 + 6 = 92\n1100 + 92"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 90 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 511 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n10 + 40 = 50  \n1200 + 50 = 1250  \n1250 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 167", "Answer": "A: 551", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 60 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 466", "Answer": "A: 871", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n5 + 60 = 65\n800 + 65 = 865\n865 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1488", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n6 + 80 = 86  \n1400 + 86 = 1486  \n1486 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 421", "Answer": "A: 993", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 436", "Answer": "A: 809", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6 = 806\n806 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n5 + 13 = 18\n1000 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 610 + 242", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n10 + 40 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300  \n19 + 8 = 27  \n1300 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 535", "Answer": "A: 1138", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n3 + 30 = 33\n1100 + 33 = 1133\n1133 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 280", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 80 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 361", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 103", "Answer": "A: 327", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n20 + 3 = 23\n300 + 23 = 323\n323 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 375", "Answer": "A: 484", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n9 + 70 = 79\n400 + 79 = 479\n479 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n2 + 20 = 22\n1500 + 22 = 1522\n1522 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 106", "Answer": "A: 630", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n24 + 6 = 30\n600 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1368", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 0 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 641", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1774", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 80 = 170\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n2 + 5 = 7  \n1000 + 150 = 1150  \n1150 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 105", "Answer": "A: 543", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 5 = 35\n500 + 35 = 535\n535 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 422", "Answer": "A: 559", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 20 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n40 + 20 = 60  \n7 + 8 = 15  \n1200 + 60 = 1260  \n1260 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1764", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 70 = 150\n7 + 7 = 14\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 851", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 211", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 320", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n16 + 40 = 56\n1100 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n7 + 4 = 11\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 528", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 20 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 6\n730 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1664", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1500 + 150 = 1650  \n1650 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 196", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 714", "Answer": "A: 964", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 352", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 50 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9 + 2 = 621"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 704", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 4 = 84\n900 + 84 = 984\n984 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 449", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 7\n950 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1798", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 40 = 90\n2 + 6 = 8\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 111", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n7 + 8 = 15\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 430", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n4 + 30 = 34 \n1200 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 536", "Answer": "A: 687", "Explanation": "150 + 500 = 650\n1 + 30 = 31\n650 + 31 = 681\n681 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n45 + 55 = 100\n1000 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 267", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 60 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9 = 699"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 440", "Answer": "A: 993", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 272", "Answer": "A: 381", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n9 + 70 = 79\n300 + 79 = 379\n379 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1622", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 30 = 110\n7 + 5 = 12\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 8 = 38\n1400 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n1 + 77 = 78\n1300 + 78 = 1378"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 767", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n5 + 7 = 12\n920 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1455", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n10 + 30 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 103", "Answer": "A: 536", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 3 = 33\n500 + 33 = 533\n533 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 865", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n15 + 60 = 75\n900 + 75 = 975\n975 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 432", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 169", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n10 + 60 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 9 + 1 = 1080\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 364", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 60 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1168", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 10 = 20\n1200 + 20 = 1220\n1220 + 9 \n1220 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 121", "Answer": "A: 765", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1290", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n11 + 70 = 81\n1200 + 81 = 1281\n1281 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1322", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1295", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 50 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 194", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 90 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 373", "Answer": "A: 619", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 70 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 7 = 27\n1300 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 140", "Answer": "A: 461", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 40 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 420", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 148", "Answer": "A: 283", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 40 = 70\n5 + 8 = 13\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 251", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n13 + 20 = 33\n1100 + 33 = 1133\n1133 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 247", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n4 + 40 = 44\n700 + 44 = 744\n744 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 499", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n9 + 90 = 99  \n1000 + 99 = 1099  \n1099 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n7 + 50 = 57\n1000 + 57 = 1057\n1057 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1555", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n19 + 30 = 49\n1500 + 49 = 1549\n1549 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 423 + 304", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 4 = 24\n700 + 24 = 724\n724 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 418", "Answer": "A: 871", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n3 + 8 = 11\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 452", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n2 + 2 = 4  \n1000 + 120 = 1120  \n1120 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 411", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 10 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 415 + 376", "Answer": "A: 791", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n5 + 6 = 11\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 476", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 70 = 140\n9 + 6 = 15\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 199", "Answer": "A: 345", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 90 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 6 = 336\n336 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 604", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 4 = 84\n1400 + 84 = 1484\n1484 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 283", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1670", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 70 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 9 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 188", "Answer": "A: 493", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n5 + 80 = 85\n400 + 85 = 485\n485 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1881", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 4 = 11\n1800 + 70 = 1870\n1870 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 490", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 0 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 8 = 1218  \n1218 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 279", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9 = 939\n939 + 6 = 945"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 40 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 10 = 1570"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 131", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 449", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 497", "Answer": "A: 644", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 7\n630 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 90 = 180\n1100 + 180 = 1280\n1280 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1732", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 622", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n6 + 20 = 26\n700 + 26 = 726\n726 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 844", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n20 + 40 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 282", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 80 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 4 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 676", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n16 + 70 = 86\n800 + 86 = 886\n886 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 0 = 70\n1 + 9 = 10\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n17 + 4 = 21\n1000 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 107", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n47 + 7 = 54\n800 + 54 = 854"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 358", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3 \n1110 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1712", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 90 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 1 = 1711\n1711 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 569 + 270", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 20 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 376", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n90 + 70 = 160\n5 + 6 = 11\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 992 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1876", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 80 = 170\n1700 + 170 = 1870\n1870 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 142", "Answer": "A: 519", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 40 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1405", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 226", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5 \n980 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n9 + 8 = 17\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n10 + 30 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 6 = 56\n1200 + 56 = 1256\n1256 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 694", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1629", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 50 = 120\n6 + 3 = 9\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 655", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n19 + 50 = 69\n800 + 69 = 869\n869 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 110", "Answer": "A: 426", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n16 + 10 = 26\n400 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1765", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 1 = 5\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 175", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n5 + 5 = 10\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1867", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n1700 + 150 = 1850  \n1850 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n8 + 6 = 14\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1798", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 0 = 90\n3 + 5 = 8\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1607", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 20 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 641", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n6 + 40 = 46  \n800 + 46 = 846  \n846 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 749", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 612", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n11 + 12 = 23\n800 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 333", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 241", "Answer": "A: 516", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n400 + 110 = 510  \n510 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 240", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 287", "Answer": "A: 836", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 80 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 443", "Answer": "A: 635", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 40 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1154", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n14 + 40 = 54\n1100 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1738", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 70 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 468", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1551", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n1500 + 40 = 1540  \n1540 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1627", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 60 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 346 + 390", "Answer": "A: 736", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 186", "Answer": "A: 512", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 80 = 100\n6 + 6 = 12\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 187", "Answer": "A: 392", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n5 + 80 = 85\n300 + 85 = 385\n385 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 866", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 644", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 352", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n1200 + 130 = 1330  \n1330 + 9  \n1330 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 229", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 20 = 30\n1100 + 30 = 1130\n1130 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 30 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 674", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1762", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 10 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 249", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n3 + 9 = 12\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 329", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 490", "Answer": "A: 617", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 90 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1670", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 312", "Answer": "A: 465", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 10 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1702", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 70 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 671", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n4 + 70 = 74\n1400 + 74 = 1474\n1474 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 368", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 60 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 241", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 1 + 1 = 822"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 584", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 6\n950 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n1200 + 100 = 1300  \n1300 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 631", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 30 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 7 + 9 = 1156"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1567", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 80 = 160\n5 + 2 = 7\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 174", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n10 + 70 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 371", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n48 + 70 = 118  \n600 + 118 = 718  \n718 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 439", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 30 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 146", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "990 + 140 = 1130\n1 + 6 = 7\n1130 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1674", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n8 + 6 = 14\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 376", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 70 = 100\n1 + 6 = 7\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 60 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 596", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 90 = 180\n5 + 6 = 11\n1100 + 180 = 1280\n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1839", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 50 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 351", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 1 = 51\n900 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 4 = 34\n1000 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 342", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 40 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1671", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n2 + 60 = 62  \n1600 + 62 = 1662  \n1662 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1776", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 8 = 68\n1700 + 68 = 1768\n1768 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 323", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 20 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 9 = 1239"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 333", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 765", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n9 + 5 = 14\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n1400 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 206", "Answer": "A: 449", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 6 = 46\n400 + 46 = 446\n446 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 458", "Answer": "A: 693", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n5 + 8 = 13\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 473", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n9 + 70 = 79\n1200 + 79 = 1279\n1279 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 768", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 583", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 455", "Answer": "A: 864", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n9 + 50 = 59\n800 + 59 = 859\n859 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n5 + 1 = 6\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 938 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 80 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 139", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 8\n1028 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 117", "Answer": "A: 365", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 10 = 50\n8 + 7 = 15\n300 + 50 = 350\n350 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 223", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 363", "Answer": "A: 903", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 60 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1936", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 40 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 258", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1416", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 0 = 80\n4 + 8 = 12\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 30 = 100\n6 + 8 = 14\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 176 + 523", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 248", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 519", "Answer": "A: 701", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 10 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n15 + 40 = 55\n1000 + 55 = 1055\n1055 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 454 + 345", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n4 + 5 = 9\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1509", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 40 = 100\n7 + 2 = 9\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 393", "Answer": "A: 950", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 10 = 950"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 532", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 465", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n1000 + 80 = 1080  \n1080 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 390", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 416", "Answer": "A: 717", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n1 + 16 = 17\n700 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 154", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4\n1124 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4 = 1024\n1024 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9 = 999\n999 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 826", "Answer": "A: 944", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n18 + 20 = 38  \n900 + 38 = 938  \n938 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 90 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 475", "Answer": "A: 611", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n6 + 5 = 11  \n500 + 100 = 600  \n600 + 11  "}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 557", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n9 + 7 = 16\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900  \n10 + 80 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 6  \n990 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 684", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 597", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 20 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 746", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n7 + 6 = 13\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 527", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n8 + 7 = 15\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 181", "Answer": "A: 309", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n200 + 100 = 300  \n300 + 8 + 1 = 309"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n20 + 50 = 70  \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 441", "Answer": "A: 1354", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 40 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 428", "Answer": "A: 934", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n6 + 20 = 26\n900 + 26 = 926\n926 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 238", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n3 + 30 = 33\n1100 + 33 = 1133\n1133 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 450", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 405", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n10 + 5 = 15\n700 + 15 = 715\n715 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n1400 + 110 = 1510  \n1510 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1802", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 70 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 414", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 404", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 4 = 14\n1100 + 14 = 1114\n1114 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 749", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 1 = 941"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 20 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n19 + 11 = 30\n1400 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 418 + 748", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 8\n1150 + 8 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 9 + 5 = 1464"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n50 + 50 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 364", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 60 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1520", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n2 + 18 = 20\n1500 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 50 = 100\n4 + 7 = 11\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 100", "Answer": "A: 243", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 43"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 104", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 4 = 84\n400 + 84 = 484\n484 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 50 = 120\n3 + 5 = 8\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 30 = 100\n8 + 4 = 12\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n60 + 10 = 70  \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n20 + 40 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1723", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 7 = 17\n1700 + 17 = 1717\n1717 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 420", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n7 + 20 = 27\n800 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 485", "Answer": "A: 821", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6\n816 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "990 + 570 = 1560\n4 + 6 = 10\n1560 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 482", "Answer": "A: 942", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 295", "Answer": "A: 614", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n10 + 90 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 9\n600 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 40 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8 \n1410 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1574", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 80 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 389", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n700 + 150 = 850  \n850 + 6 = 856  \n856 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 970", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 259", "Answer": "A: 360", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n1 + 50 = 51\n300 + 51 = 351\n351 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 20 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 30 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n4 + 5 = 9\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 411", "Answer": "A: 637", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 10 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 6\n630 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1523", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 173", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 3 = 5\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n9 + 20 = 29\n1200 + 29 = 1229\n1229 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 700 + 496", "Answer": "A: 1196", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 6 = 96\n1100 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 550", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n5 + 50 = 55\n800 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 172", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 241", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 11\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 70 = 110\n1400 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n15 + 60 = 75\n1200 + 75"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n9 + 9 = 18\n1200 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 714", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 10 = 30\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 648", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n5 + 8 = 13\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1944", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 70 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 446", "Answer": "A: 944", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 40 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 613", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 290", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 433", "Answer": "A: 891", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 30 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n8 + 3 = 11\n880 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 170", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 280", "Answer": "A: 492", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n10 + 80 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 8 = 1118"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n7 + 20 = 27\n1300 + 27 = 1327\n1327 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 267", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n2 + 60 = 62\n700 + 62 = 762\n762 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 80 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1138", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n130 + 1 = 131\n1000 + 131 = 1131\n1131 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 9 + 4 = 1260 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1716", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n8 + 8 = 16\n1700 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 583", "Answer": "A: 741", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n50 + 80 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 3 = 733\n733 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 462", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n19 + 90 = 109\n1600 + 109 = 1709\n1709 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 953 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1679", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n50 + 20 = 70  \n3 + 6 = 9  \n1600 + 70 = 1670  \n1670 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 348", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 8 = 708"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 376", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 590", "Answer": "A: 1551", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 90 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n7 + 50 = 57\n1200 + 57 = 1257\n1257 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 279", "Answer": "A: 416", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 70 = 100\n7 + 9 = 16\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 90 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 283", "Answer": "A: 557", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 80 = 150\n4 + 3 = 7\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 0 = 90\n9 + 3 = 12\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 418", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n18\n600 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 313", "Answer": "A: 750", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 10 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 = 1003\n1003 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 6 = 15\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n6 + 7 = 13\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1864", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 90 = 160\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 327", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n50 + 500 = 550  \n550 + 7  \n550 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1851", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 20 = 40\n6 + 5 = 11\n1800 + 40 = 1840\n1840 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 415", "Answer": "A: 638", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 10 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 199", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 5 + 4 = 1179\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 547", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n10 + 40 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 1 \n650 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 60 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 601", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 1 = 81\n800 + 81 = 881\n881 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 109", "Answer": "A: 349", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 9 = 49\n300 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 505", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 0 = 70\n1 + 5 = 6\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 203", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n7 + 3 = 10\n1000 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 326", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 664", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 60 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 266", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 352 + 321", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n50 + 20 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 3 = 673"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 305", "Answer": "A: 550", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 0 = 40\n5 + 5 = 10\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1287", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n1100 + 170 = 1270  \n1270 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 107", "Answer": "A: 473", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n60 + 7 = 67  \n400 + 67 = 467   \n467 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 267", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 10 = 740"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 256", "Answer": "A: 735", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 50 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 9\n729 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 137", "Answer": "A: 264", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n7 + 7 = 14  \n200 + 50 = 250  \n250 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 374", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 487", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n600 + 100 = 700  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n700 + 11  "}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 507", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 0 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9 = 999"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 481", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 5 = 1045"}
{"Question": "Q: 121 + 183", "Answer": "A: 304", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 80 = 100\n1 + 3 = 4\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 127", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n3 + 7 = 10\n900 + 10 = 910"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 5 = 65\n1200 + 65 = 1265\n1265 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 506", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n60 + 6 = 66  \n800 + 66  "}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 156", "Answer": "A: 552", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 50 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 6\n546 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 665 + 114", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 10 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 4\n770 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 233", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n1100 + 50 = 1150  \n1150 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 561", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 649", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n5 + 40 = 45\n700 + 45 = 745\n745 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1658", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 80 = 140\n9 + 9 = 18\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 70 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 2\n1032 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 173", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 7 + 3 = 1010"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 119", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n5 + 9 = 14\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 487", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n10 + 80 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1759", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 80 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1778", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 50 = 70\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 7 + 1 = 1778"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 339", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n500 + 100 = 600  \n600 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 166", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n18 + 60 = 78\n700 + 78 = 778\n778 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 70 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 10 = 1430"}
{"Question": "Q: 162 + 755", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 387", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n9 + 80 = 89\n800 + 89 = 889\n889 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 213", "Answer": "A: 882", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 10 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 523", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 20 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 414", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n1 + 14 = 15\n800 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 332", "Answer": "A: 558", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n6 + 2 = 8  \n500 + 50 = 550  \n550 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 443", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 710", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 579", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n2 + 80 = 82\n1100 + 82 = 1182\n1182 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n7 + 70 = 77\n1200 + 77 = 1277\n1277 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 174", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n9 + 70 = 79\n700 + 79 = 779\n779 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 423", "Answer": "A: 566", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 3 = 563\n563 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 522", "Answer": "A: 734", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n12 + 20 = 32\n700 + 32 = 732\n732 + 2 = 734"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n8 + 4 = 12\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 544", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 5 + 4 = 769"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 533", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 10 = 920"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 114", "Answer": "A: 473", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 10 = 60\n9 + 4 = 13\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 768", "Answer": "A: 1742", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n6 + 9 = 15\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 403", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n3 + 3 = 6\n1100 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 149", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 40 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 397", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 60 = 140\n7 + 9 = 16\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n5 + 60 = 65\n1400 + 65 = 1465\n1465 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1747", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 90 = 140\n3 + 4 = 7\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n1200 + 100 = 1300  \n1300 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 458", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 50 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 20 = 40\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 323", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n10 + 20 = 30\n1100 + 30 = 1130\n1130 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1453", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 3 = 53\n1400 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 179", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 316", "Answer": "A: 516", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n16  \n500 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 235", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n15 + 30 = 45\n800 + 45 = 845\n845 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 834", "Answer": "A: 1773", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 30 = 60\n9 + 4 = 13\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 145", "Answer": "A: 591", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n40 + 40 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 6\n580 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 424", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 485", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 80 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 717", "Answer": "A: 1200", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 10 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 329", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n7 + 9 = 16\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1598", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 8 = 98\n1500 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n40 + 60 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900 \n45 + 50 = 95 \n900 + 95 = 995 \n995 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 183", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1923", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 40 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 374", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n400 + 120 = 520  \n520 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 426", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n28 + 86 = 114  \n1000 + 114"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 728", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 10 = 990\n990"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 674", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 6 = 1046\n1046 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 70 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n16 + 20 = 36\n1500 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1843", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n8 + 30 = 38\n1800 + 38 = 1838\n1838 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 490", "Answer": "A: 1478", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 90 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n10 + 99 = 109  \n900 + 109"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 333", "Answer": "A: 733", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 222", "Answer": "A: 571", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n9 + 2 = 11\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 164", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n3 + 4 = 7\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 1 = 3\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 155", "Answer": "A: 320", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 50 = 110\n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1950", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 60 = 140\n1800 + 140 = 1940\n1940 + 10 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 454 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 578", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 70 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1525", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n15 + 10 = 25\n1500 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1369", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 80 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 470", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 641", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1665", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 70 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n7 + 8 = 15\n1650 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1322", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n55 + 60 = 115  \n1200 + 115 = 1315  \n1315 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 143", "Answer": "A: 441", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n300 + 130 = 430  \n430 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 388", "Answer": "A: 730", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 80 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 10 + 10 = 730"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1755", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 60 = 140\n7 + 8 = 15\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 488", "Answer": "A: 973", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n85 + 88 = 173  \n800 + 173  "}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "650 + 600 = 1250\n7 + 11 = 18\n1250 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 397", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 90 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 193", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 90 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 260", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n40 + 60 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1457", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n4 + 3 = 7\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1295", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n18 + 70 = 88\n1200 + 88 = 1288\n1288 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 510", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 10 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 415", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 5 = 35\n1000 + 35 = 1035\n1035 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 308", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n40 + 8 = 48  \n800 + 48 = 848  \n848 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 334", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 441", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 10 = 700"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n14 + 40 = 54\n1200 + 54 = 1254\n1254 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 392", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 733", "Answer": "A: 1436", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n3 + 30 = 33\n1400 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1460", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n16 + 40 = 56\n1400 + 56 = 1456\n1456 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 429", "Answer": "A: 597", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 20 = 80\n8 + 9 = 17\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n18 + 30 = 48\n1200 + 48 = 1248\n1248 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 20 = 110\n3 + 4 = 7\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 549", "Answer": "A: 925", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 6 = 916\n916 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 121", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n7 + 5 = 12\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 514", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n8 + 4 = 12\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 550", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1523", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 20 = 110 \n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 342", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 2 = 42\n1100 + 42 = 1142\n1142 + 47\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1629", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n2 + 20 = 22\n1600 + 22\n1600 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 309", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 9 = 39\n800 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n98 + 8 = 106\n1100 + 106"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 800 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n45\n1300 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 286", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 80 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1900", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 60 = 90\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 10 = 1900"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n10 + 10 = 20\n3 + 8 = 11\n1200 + 20 = 1220\n1220 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1548", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 315", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n8 + 15 = 23\n700 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 579", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 70 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 457", "Answer": "A: 694", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 482", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n82  \n600 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 6 = 96\n900 + 96 = 996\n996 + 95"}
{"Question": "Q: 318 + 357", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 50 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n8 + 7 = 15\n660 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1592", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 70 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 152", "Answer": "A: 586", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 250", "Answer": "A: 1082", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 121", "Answer": "A: 239", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n18 + 20 = 38\n200 + 38 = 238\n238 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1840", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 90 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 397", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 90 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n5 + 7 = 12\n510 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 70 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 10 = 1430"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 202", "Answer": "A: 566", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 0 = 60\n4 + 2 = 6\n500 + 60 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1645", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 70 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 130", "Answer": "A: 245", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n15 + 30 = 45\n200 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 149", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 40 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 153", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 3 = 53\n1000 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1079", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n5 + 4 = 9\n1000 + 70 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1701", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 70 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 102", "Answer": "A: 234", "Explanation": "130 + 100 = 230\n2 + 2 = 4\n230 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1848", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n1800 + 40 = 1840   \n1840 + 5 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1852", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 90 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 361", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n600 + 70 = 670  \n670 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 155", "Answer": "A: 637", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n500 + 130 = 630  \n630 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 526", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 434", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 283", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1287", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 141", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n20 + 40 = 60\n1 + 1 = 2\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 10 = 60\n5 + 8 = 13\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 239", "Answer": "A: 385", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 30 = 70\n6 + 9 = 15\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 306", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n15 + 6 = 21\n900 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 519", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n10 + 10 = 20\n1400 + 20 = 1420\n1420 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1657", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 10 = 50\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1929", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n90 + 30 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n1100 + 120 = 1220  \n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1227", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 172", "Answer": "A: 360", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 70 = 150\n200 + 150 = 350\n350 + 10 = 360"}
{"Question": "Q: 610 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n10 + 1 = 11\n1300 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 427", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 6 \n910 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 130", "Answer": "A: 551", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 292", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 90 = 170\n4 + 2 = 6\n300 + 170 = 470\n470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 1 = 31\n1300 + 31 = 1331\n1331 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 487", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n600 + 110 = 710  \n710 + 8 = 718  \n718 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 516", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1866", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 60 = 150\n7 + 9 = 16\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 90 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 10 = 1150"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 221", "Answer": "A: 916", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 6 = 916"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 224", "Answer": "A: 638", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 20 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 273", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 126", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 30 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 799 + 332", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 464", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 60 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1263", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1848", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 7 = 8\n1800 + 40 = 1840\n1840 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1970", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 90 = 160\n1800 + 160 = 1960\n1960 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 429", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n1 + 20 = 21\n500 + 21 = 521\n521 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n2 + 30 = 32\n1500 + 32 = 1532\n1532 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 355", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n47 + 50 = 97  \n800 + 97  \n800 + 97 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 653", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 348", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 40 = 80\n4 + 8 = 12\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n7 + 60 = 67\n1000 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 567", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n7 + 7 = 14\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 181", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n75 + 80 = 155  \n600 + 155 = 755  \n755 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9 = 1029\n1029 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 551", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 596", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 329", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 20 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 5 = 875\n875 + 4 = 879\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 753", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 5 = 7\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 460", "Answer": "A: 733", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n600 + 130 = 730  \n730 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 686", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n78 + 80 = 158  \n1000 + 158 = 1158  \n1158 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1639", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 3 = 33\n1600 + 33 = 1633\n1633 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 358", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 50 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 8 + 2 = 1270"}
{"Question": "Q: 700 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 6 = 36\n1500 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1509", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 40 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 1\n1500 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 90 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 478", "Answer": "A: 628", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 733", "Answer": "A: 1685", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 30 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 5 = 1685\n1685 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 287", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 80 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 7 = 807\n807 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 576", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n6 + 70 = 76\n600 + 76 = 676\n676 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 196", "Answer": "A: 674", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 90 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 6\n660 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 234", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n6 + 4 = 10\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 112", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n76 + 12 = 88  \n1000 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 135", "Answer": "A: 507", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n2 + 5 = 7\n500 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n8 + 6 = 14\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 108 + 668", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n8 + 60 = 68\n700 + 68 = 768\n768 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 312", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n50 + 10 = 60  \n7 + 2 = 9  \n900 + 60 = 960  \n960 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 257", "Answer": "A: 942", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 187", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n7 + 7 = 14  \n1000 + 160 = 1160  \n1160 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 162", "Answer": "A: 1112", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 346 + 325", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 20 = 60\n6 + 5 = 11\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 177", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 70 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n6 + 8 = 14\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 418", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n1 + 10 = 11\n900 + 11 = 911\n911 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 301", "Answer": "A: 451", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 1 = 51\n400 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 287", "Answer": "A: 552", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n400 + 140 = 540  \n540 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 80 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 495", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 90 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 160", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n45 + 60 = 105  \n900 + 105"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1807", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 20 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n6 + 1 = 7\n1800 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 497", "Answer": "A: 1453", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n1300 + 140 = 1440  \n1440 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 331", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n5 + 30 = 35\n600 + 35 = 635\n635 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 180", "Answer": "A: 361", "Explanation": "180 + 180 = 360\n360 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 80 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1610", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 90 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 364", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 746", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 40 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 311", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 0 = 50\n1000 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 480", "Answer": "A: 722", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 80 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 142", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n3 + 40 = 43\n900 + 43 = 943\n943 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 544", "Answer": "A: 681", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 40 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n70 + 20 = 90  \n1400 + 90 = 1490  \n1490 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 458", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 50 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 336", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n1200 + 50 = 1250  \n1250 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 463", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n9 + 60 = 69\n1100 + 69 = 1169\n1169 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1545", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 60 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1561", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n11 + 50 = 61\n1500 + 61"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1789", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 50 = 80\n5 + 4 = 9\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 266", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n700 + 70 = 770  \n770 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 185", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n6 + 80 = 86  \n600 + 86 = 686  \n686 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 504", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n54 + 4 = 58\n1000 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 40 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 317", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n20 + 8 = 28\n900 + 28 = 928\n928 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 283", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 154", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1814", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 90 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n6 + 9 = 15\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 320", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n56 + 20 = 76\n1000 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 758", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 843 + 372", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1715", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 70 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 763", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n5 + 60 = 65\n900 + 65 = 965\n965 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1775", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n1 + 70 = 71\n1700 + 71 = 1771\n1771 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 0 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 659", "Answer": "A: 1572", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n10 + 50 = 60\n3 + 9 = 12\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1637", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 60 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 7 = 1637"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1568", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1695", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 90 = 180\n1500 + 180 = 1680\n1680 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 174", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n7 + 4 = 11\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 609", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 0 = 10\n4 + 9 = 13\n800 + 10 = 810\n810 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 153", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 429", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n50 + 20 = 70  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n900 + 70 = 970  \n970 + 13  "}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 190", "Answer": "A: 420", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 90 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 30 = 40\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 0 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 470", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 306", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n80 + 0 = 80  \n9 + 6 = 15  \n1000 + 80 = 1080  \n1080 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n6 + 8 = 14\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 537", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 447 + 428", "Answer": "A: 875", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 8 = 15\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 40 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1 + 7 = 8\n1800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1543", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 50 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 177", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n15 + 70 = 85\n1000 + 85 = 1085\n1085 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 352 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5 \n1220 + 5 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 239", "Answer": "A: 474", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 9 = 14\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 349", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1372", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n1 + 70 = 71\n1300 + 71 = 1371\n1371 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 185", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 537", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 7 = 11\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 422", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n16 + 20 = 36\n1200 + 36 = 1236\n1236 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 331", "Answer": "A: 775", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 30 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 527", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 540", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n10 + 40 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8\n1410 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 443", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n4 + 6 = 10\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 246", "Answer": "A: 567", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 40 = 60\n1 + 6 = 7\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 650", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 50 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 666", "Answer": "A: 797", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n700 + 90 = 790  \n790 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1668", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 0 = 60\n7 + 1 = 8\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 348", "Answer": "A: 585", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 294", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 90 = 120\n1 + 4 = 5\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 177", "Answer": "A: 350", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n3 + 7 = 10  \n200 + 140 = 340  \n340 + 10 = 350"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 500", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 0 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 197", "Answer": "A: 821", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 4 \n810 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 243", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1761", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 90 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 384", "Answer": "A: 763", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n600 + 150 = 750  \n750 + 9  \n750 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 0 = 90\n1 + 7 = 8\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 616 + 399", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n16 + 90 = 106\n900 + 106 = 1006\n1006 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 554", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1498", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 30 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7 + 1 = 1498"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 588", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 8 = 848\n848 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 333", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n7 + 3 = 10  \n1000 + 90 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1447", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1640", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 2 = 32\n1600 + 32 = 1632\n1632 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 10 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 409", "Answer": "A: 610", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n1 + 9 = 10\n600 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 489", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 80 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 225", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n9 + 5 = 14\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1645", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 90 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 5 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 315", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 329", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9 + 5 = 1444"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 429", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n2 + 9 = 11\n700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 219", "Answer": "A: 973", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 335", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 30 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1864", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 90 = 160\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 553", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n15 + 20 = 35\n1200 + 35 = 1235\n1235 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 736", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 367", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1200", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n16 + 80 = 96\n1100 + 96 = 1196\n1196 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 90 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 535", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1698", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n1600 + 80 = 1680  \n1680 + 9  \n1680 + 9 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 331", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 30 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 466", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 60 = 140\n5 + 6 = 11\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 632", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n7 + 2 = 9  \n700 + 80 = 780  \n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 281", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 30 = 80\n9 + 8 = 17\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 243", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n1 + 40 = 41\n500 + 41 = 541\n541 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 376", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 559", "Answer": "A: 934", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n5 + 9 = 14\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 70 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 8 = 1808"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 309", "Answer": "A: 446", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 9 = 39\n400 + 39 = 439\n439 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1814", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 80 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n9 + 5 = 14\n1800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1154", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n7 + 8 = 15\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 129", "Answer": "A: 272", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 9 = 12\n200 + 60 = 260\n260 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 10 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 686", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1595", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 40 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 783", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 694", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 430", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n11 + 30 = 41\n1100 + 41"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1254", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 30 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 226", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 6 = 7\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n7 + 2 = 9\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 388", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 80 = 160\n5 + 8 = 13\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 191", "Answer": "A: 360", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n200 + 150 = 350  \n350 + 10 = 360"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1587", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 2 = 7\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 658", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n8 + 5 = 13\n1200 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 245", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n2 + 40 = 42\n1000 + 42 = 1042\n1042 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 9 = 69\n1500 + 69"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 748", "Answer": "A: 1736", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n1600 + 120 = 1720  \n1720 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 545", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 40 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 380", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 80 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 142", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 3 = 43\n800 + 43 = 843\n843 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 489", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 80 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1379", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n10 + 60 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 324", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000 \n60 + 20 = 80 \n7 + 4 = 11 \n1000 + 80 = 1080 \n1080 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n1000 + 140 = 1140  \n1140 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 647", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 1 + 7 = 818"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 597", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n700 + 150 = 850  \n850 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1743", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 50 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 50 = 60\n1000 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 128", "Answer": "A: 245", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 20 = 30\n7 + 8 = 15\n200 + 30 = 230\n230 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1713", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n8 + 5 = 13\n1700 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 687", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n9 + 7 = 16\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 305", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n2 + 5 = 7\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n20 + 10 = 30  \n1000 + 30 = 1030  \n1030 + 10 = 1040"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 198", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 353", "Answer": "A: 469", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 50 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 355", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 469", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9 + 3 = 1032"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 789", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 80 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n9 + 9 = 18\n960 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 10 = 20\n1100 + 20 = 1120\n1120 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 458", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 630", "Answer": "A: 805", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 660", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 255", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n9 + 40 = 49\n1300 + 49 = 1349\n1349 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 70 = 140\n7 + 5 = 12\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 484", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1366", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 80 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 588 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 70 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1780", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 40 = 70\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 10 = 1780"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 328", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 10 = 770"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n9 + 40 = 49\n1100 + 49 = 1149 \n1149 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 610", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 7 = 77\n1600 + 77 = 1677\n1677 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 30 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 380", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n1200 + 160 = 1360  \n1360 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 146", "Answer": "A: 326", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 40 = 120\n200 + 120 = 320\n320 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 190 + 380", "Answer": "A: 570", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n400 + 170"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n10 + 80 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 564", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 60 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 338", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 6 \n820 + 8 = 834"}
{"Question": "Q: 467 + 427", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 671", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n8 + 5 = 13\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 121", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 379", "Answer": "A: 950", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 180", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 132", "Answer": "A: 494", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 30 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 615", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n1200 + 80 = 1280  \n1280 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 8 = 11\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1709", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n10 + 90 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 360", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n8 + 20 = 28\n1300 + 28 = 1328\n1328 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8 "}
{"Question": "Q: 107 + 137", "Answer": "A: 244", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n7 + 30 = 37\n200 + 37 = 237\n237 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 552", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "490 + 550 = 1040  \n1 + 2 = 3  \n1040 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 70 = 80\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 162", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 60 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 123", "Answer": "A: 468", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 3 = 8\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 166", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n1000 + 80 = 1080  \n1080 + 10 = 1090  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 844", "Answer": "A: 1770", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 40 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 10 = 1770"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 274", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 70 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 3 \n600 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 401", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n2 + 1 = 3\n1300 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 631", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 7 + 1 = 908"}
{"Question": "Q: 412 + 279", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 15\n1270 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 112", "Answer": "A: 283", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1 + 2 = 3\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 30 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 254", "Answer": "A: 736", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n9 + 9 = 18\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 567", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 60 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n6 + 8 = 14\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 0 = 40\n7 + 9 = 16\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 793", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n800 + 130 = 930  \n930 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 481", "Answer": "A: 1431", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 216", "Answer": "A: 594", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 788 + 203", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n88 + 3 = 91\n900 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1561", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n18 + 40 = 58\n1500 + 58 = 1558\n1558 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 180", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 624", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 20 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 470", "Answer": "A: 1432", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 254 + 202", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n54 + 2 = 56\n400 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 148", "Answer": "A: 599", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 40 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 1\n590 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 200", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 0 = 10\n1000 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n55 + 80 = 135\n900 + 135 = 1035\n1035 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1574", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 0 = 60\n7 + 7 = 14\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 266", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 653", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 119", "Answer": "A: 738", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n19 + 19 = 38\n700 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 113", "Answer": "A: 508", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 10 = 100\n5 + 3 = 8\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9\n1009 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 571", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 70 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n1200 + 120 = 1320  \n1320 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 130", "Answer": "A: 705", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n75 + 30 = 105\n600 + 105"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n19 + 40 = 59\n1100 + 59"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1 + 8 = 9\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 245", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n5 + 5 = 10\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1889", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n9 + 80 = 89\n1800 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 646", "Answer": "A: 955", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n9 + 40 = 49\n900 + 49 = 949\n949 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n1200 + 180 = 1380  \n1380 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 315", "Answer": "A: 681", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 571", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 150", "Answer": "A: 332", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n200 + 130 = 330  \n330 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 404", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 4 = 54\n800 + 54 = 854\n854 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1393", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n1300 + 80 = 1380  \n1380 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 168", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 8 = 1138\n1138 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1581", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 90 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1247", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n19 + 20 = 39\n1200 + 39 = 1239\n1239 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n8 + 70 = 78\n1100 + 78 = 1178\n1178 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 313", "Answer": "A: 440", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 10 = 30\n400 + 30 = 430\n430 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 452", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 50 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n7 + 9 = 16\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1660", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n3 + 50 = 53\n1600 + 53 = 1653\n1653 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 183", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 80 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 190", "Answer": "A: 416", "Explanation": "200 + 20 = 220\n6 + 190 = 196\n220 + 196 = 416"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 90 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 40 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 341", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n7 + 40 = 47  \n1000 + 47 = 1047  \n1047 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 475", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n75 + 75 = 150  \n700 + 150"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 782", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n800 + 120 = 920  \n920 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 575", "Answer": "A: 787", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 125", "Answer": "A: 347", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n20 + 20 = 40\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 5 = 345\n345 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 723", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "250 + 700 = 950\n2 + 20 = 22\n950 + 22 = 972\n972 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1467", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n19 + 40 = 59\n1400 + 59 = 1459\n1459 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 325", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 0 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 495", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n45 + 10 = 55\n1200 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n6 + 8 = 14\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 148", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 40 = 70\n70 + 5 = 75\n75 + 8\n700 + 83"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 30 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 550", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 50 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 576", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 70 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 7 = 77\n1200 + 77 = 1277\n1277 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 10 = 1160"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1725", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 50 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 586 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 10 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 443", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n6 + 3 = 9\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n16 + 25 = 41\n1000 + 41"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 668", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 411", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5 = 985"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 449", "Answer": "A: 620", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 40 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 10 = 620"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1459", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n10 + 40 = 50   \n1400 + 50 = 1450  \n1450 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 425", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n7 + 20 = 27\n1200 + 27 = 1227\n1227 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 237", "Answer": "A: 366", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 30 = 50\n9 + 7 = 16\n300 + 50 = 350\n350 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n6 + 90 = 96\n1100 + 96 = 1196\n1196 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 180", "Answer": "A: 606", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 80 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 191", "Answer": "A: 800", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n9 + 90 = 99\n700 + 99 = 799\n799 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 40 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 905 + 659", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n5 + 50 = 55\n1500 + 55 = 1555\n1555 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 165", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 538", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 8\n840 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 116", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1821", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 30 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 700 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1644", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n700 + 944 = 1600 + 44"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 113", "Answer": "A: 612", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 10 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n9 + 3 = 12\n600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1698", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 50 = 90\n7 + 1 = 8\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 287", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 10 = 760"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 80 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 274", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600   \n9 + 70 = 79  \n600 + 79 = 679  \n679 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1772", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 20 = 60\n4 + 8 = 12\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 10 = 90\n4 + 8 = 12\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1839", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n50 + 80 = 130  \n1700 + 130 = 1830  \n1830 + 9 = 1839"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 372", "Answer": "A: 611", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n500 + 100 = 600  \n9 + 2 = 11  \n600 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 290", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n5 + 6 = 11\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1619", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n20 + 90 = 110  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 104", "Answer": "A: 685", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n80 + 4 = 84\n600 + 84 = 684\n684 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1663", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n8 + 50 = 58\n1600 + 58 = 1658\n1658 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 7 = 37\n1200 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 499", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 90 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 498", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "480 + 490 = 970\n2 + 8 = 10\n970 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 793", "Answer": "A: 947", "Explanation": "150 + 790 = 940\n4 + 3 = 7\n940 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 312", "Answer": "A: 733", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 10 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 288", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n18 + 80 = 98\n1100 + 98 = 1198\n1198 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 140", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n16 + 40 = 56\n900 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 445", "Answer": "A: 747", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n2 + 40 = 42\n700 + 42 = 742\n742 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 649 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 0 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 785", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 80 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 9 = 949\n949 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 261", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "990 + 260 = 1250  \n6 + 1 = 7  \n1250 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 196", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n17 + 90 = 107\n500 + 107 = 607\n607 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 517", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 7\n790 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1843", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 60 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 50 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 5 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 560", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 132", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n10 + 30 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 277", "Answer": "A: 793", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 16 \n16 - 10 = 6\n780 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 60 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1642", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n50 + 80 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1299", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n2 + 7 = 9\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 307", "Answer": "A: 486", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 0 = 70\n9 + 7 = 16\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 186", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n19 + 80 = 99\n800 + 99 = 899\n899 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n19 + 40 = 59\n1100 + 59"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 682", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1518", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n14 + 4 = 18\n1500 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 234", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 283", "Answer": "A: 747", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 80 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 425", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n2 + 5 = 7\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 151", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 348", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 40 = 70\n2 + 8 = 10\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 333", "Answer": "A: 617", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 266", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n900 + 70 = 970  \n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 113", "Answer": "A: 430", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n17 + 13 = 30\n400 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 169", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n91 + 60 = 151\n600 + 151\n+ 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 393", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 10 = 830"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 300", "Answer": "A: 442", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 \n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n7 + 80 = 87\n1100 + 87 = 1187\n1187 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 784", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n6 + 80 = 86\n900 + 86 = 986\n986 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 0 = 70\n3 + 9 = 12\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 135", "Answer": "A: 282", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 30 = 70\n7 + 5 = 12\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 674", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n3 + 70 = 73\n800 + 73 = 873\n873 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n8 + 40 = 48\n1300 + 48 = 1348\n1348 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n4 + 8 = 12\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 686", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + (5 + 6)"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1596", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 60 = 80\n9 + 7 = 16\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 197", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n8 + 90 = 98\n1000 + 98 = 1098\n1098 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n1 + 50 = 51\n1100 + 51 = 1151\n1151 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 564", "Answer": "A: 826", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 199", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n99 + 99 = 198  \n1000 + 198"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 207", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 7 = 37\n1000 + 37 = 1037\n1037 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 161", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 269", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1459", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n7 + 2 = 9  \n1300 + 150 = 1450  \n1450 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 141", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n40 + 40 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 8 = 18\n1100 + 18 = 1118\n1118 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1070", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 80 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 511", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 157", "Answer": "A: 313", "Explanation": "150 + 150 = 300\n6 + 7 = 13\n300 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 134", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 30 = 90\n9 + 4 = 13\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 439", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n9 + 9 = 18\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 106", "Answer": "A: 298", "Explanation": "100 + 90 = 190\n190 + 2 = 192\n190 + 100 = 290\n290 + 6 = 296\n296 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1515", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n6 + 9 = 15\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1642", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 70 = 130\n7 + 5 = 12\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 804", "Answer": "A: 907", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n3 + 4 = 7\n900 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 504", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 4 = 94\n600 + 94 = 694\n694 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 543", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 40 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 433", "Answer": "A: 697", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 0 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 230", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 444", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 334", "Answer": "A: 842", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n8 + 30 = 38\n800 + 38 = 838\n838 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 295", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 425", "Answer": "A: 773", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n8 + 5 = 13\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 1 = 31\n1300 + 31 = 1331\n1331 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n12 + 50 = 62\n1200 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 267", "Answer": "A: 437", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 60 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 420", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n14 + 20 = 34\n1300 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 338", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n7 + 30 = 37\n700 + 37 = 737\n737 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 419", "Answer": "A: 521", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n2 + 19 = 21\n500 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 405", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 5 = 15\n900 + 15 = 915\n915 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 323 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 7 = 27\n1200 + 27 = 1227\n1227 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 129", "Answer": "A: 377", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n8 + 9 = 17\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 581", "Answer": "A: 1287", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n6 + 80 = 86\n1200 + 86 = 1286\n1286 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 50 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n10 + 30 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000   \n44 + 30 = 74  \n1000 + 74 = 1074  \n1074 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 375", "Answer": "A: 714", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 70 = 100\n9 + 5 = 14\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n16 + 5 = 21\n1000 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 197", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 10 = 1580"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 709", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 9 = 69\n900 + 69"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 346", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n8 + 6 = 14\n1100 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000 \n40 + 40 = 80 \n8 + 3 = 11 \n1000 + 80 = 1080 \n1080 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n7 + 60 = 67\n1200 + 67 = 1267\n1267 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 159", "Answer": "A: 307", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 50 = 90\n8 + 9 = 17\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 312", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 843 + 103", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 3 = 43\n900 + 43 = 943\n943 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 538", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 8 = 1166"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1543", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 70 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 351", "Answer": "A: 474", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1457", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 90 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 60 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1503", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 20 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n9 + 9 = 18\n1400 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 452", "Answer": "A: 1154", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n2 + 50 = 52\n1100 + 52 = 1152\n1152 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1668", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 80 = 160\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n3 + 5 = 8\n1660 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1527", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 40 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1632", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 80 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n7 + 5 = 12\n1620 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 106", "Answer": "A: 670", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 6 = 66\n600 + 66 = 666\n666 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 401", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n2 + 1 = 3\n600 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 543", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 237", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8 = 1058\n1058 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 495", "Answer": "A: 1463", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 90 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 502", "Answer": "A: 775", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 0 = 70\n3 + 2 = 5\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1413", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 20 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 451", "Answer": "A: 581", "Explanation": "130 + 450 = 580\n580 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 708", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 8 = 58\n800 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 70 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n3 + 60 = 63\n1000 + 63 = 1063\n1063 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 402", "Answer": "A: 624", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n22 + 2 = 24  \n600 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 339", "Answer": "A: 1227", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 443", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n1300 + 70 = 1370  \n1370 + 9 + 3  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1000 + 150 = 1150  \n1150 + 5 + 6  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 606", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 6 = 66\n900 + 66 = 966\n966 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 342", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 323 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3\n1003 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 50 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 7 + 5 = 1452"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n97 + 1 = 98\n1200 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 469", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 5 + 9 = 1024\n1024"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 539", "Answer": "A: 737", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 30 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 364", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 242", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 40 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 532", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 40 = 120\n2 + 3 = 5\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 440", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 40 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1525", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n4 + 1 = 5\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 80 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1 + 2 = 3\n1300 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100  \n50 + 80 = 130  \n1100 + 130 = 1230  \n1230 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 335", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 214", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n9 + 4 = 13\n900 + 13 = 913\n913 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 324 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n16 + 9 = 25\n1400 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 515", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 5 = 7\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 106", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 6 = 86\n700 + 86 = 786\n786 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 604", "Answer": "A: 1046", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 4 = 44\n1000 + 44 = 1044\n1044 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 187", "Answer": "A: 458", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 80 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 8 = 458\n458 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 30 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 50 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8 + 2 = 1230"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 280", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n1 + 48 = 49\n1200 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1668", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n5 + 60 = 65  \n1600 + 65 = 1665  \n1665 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 265", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 8 = 828\n828 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 567", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 338", "Answer": "A: 479", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 30 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 448", "Answer": "A: 612", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n500 + 100 = 600  \n600 + 12 = 612"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 992 + 223", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n18 + 70 = 88\n1300 + 88 = 1388\n1388 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 225", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1717", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n90 + 20 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 214", "Answer": "A: 584", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 105", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 5 = 45\n800 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 189", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 10 = 850\n850 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 388", "Answer": "A: 1227", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 137", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n10 + 30 = 40\n9 + 7 = 16\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n19 + 11 = 30\n1100 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 6 = 26\n1000 + 26 = 1026\n1026 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1 + 2 = 3\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 285", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n900 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 9 = 14\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 107 + 219", "Answer": "A: 326", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n7 + 19 = 26\n300 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 604", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 4 = 94\n1400 + 94 = 1494\n1494 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 415 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 50 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 249", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6\n996 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 513", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 10 = 70\n9 + 3 = 12\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1611", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 90 = 100\n5 + 6 = 11\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 411", "Answer": "A: 882", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9 = 1029"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1518", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 50 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 8 = 1518"}
{"Question": "Q: 667 + 242", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 673", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 8 = 908\n908 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n5 + 7 = 12\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 127", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n1 + 20 = 21\n800 + 21 = 821\n821 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n1 + 80 = 81  \n1300 + 81 = 1381  \n1381 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1704", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 50 = 90\n9 + 5 = 14\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 273", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1499", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 693", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 476", "Answer": "A: 775", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 70 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 9 \n760 + 6 \n760 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 2 = 7\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 430 + 365", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 60 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 162", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 60 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 40 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 6 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 280", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 80 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 116", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n38 + 16 = 54\n900 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 678 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 2 = 72\n1300 + 72 = 1372\n1372 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 148", "Answer": "A: 638", "Explanation": "490 + 100 = 590  \n40 + 8 = 48  \n590 + 48  "}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 351", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 396", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 90 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 2 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 308", "Answer": "A: 616", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n8 + 8 = 16\n600 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 568", "Answer": "A: 697", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 60 = 80\n9 + 8 = 17\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 159", "Answer": "A: 450", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 50 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 9 + 1 = 450"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 3 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 217", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n40 + 10 = 50  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n1000 + 50 = 1050  \n1050 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 138", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 330", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n76 + 30 = 106  \n900 + 106  "}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 195", "Answer": "A: 639", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n4 + 5 = 9\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n5 + 20 = 25  \n1200 + 25 = 1225  \n1225 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n1300 + 70 = 1370  \n1370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 277", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "450 + 250 = 700\n1 + 70 = 71\n700 + 71 = 771\n771 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 139", "Answer": "A: 629", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 30 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n1 + 5 = 6  \n1500 + 80 = 1580  \n1580 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 9 = 99\n1300 + 99 = 1399\n1399 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 253", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 7 = 1017\n1017 - 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 207", "Answer": "A: 791", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 7 = 87\n700 + 87 = 787\n787 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 253", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 128", "Answer": "A: 458", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n400 + 50 = 450  \n450 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 567", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 634", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 8 = 12\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 278", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n7 + 8 = 15\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 116", "Answer": "A: 479", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 10 = 70\n3 + 6 = 9\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 120", "Answer": "A: 403", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 20 = 100\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1545", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 4 = 44\n1500 + 44 = 1544\n1544 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 157", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n1000 + 140 = 1140  \n1140 + 10 = 1150  \n1150 -"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 119", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 10 = 900"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 1 = 51\n1300 + 51 = 1351\n1351 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n10 + 30 = 40  \n1200 + 40 = 1240  \n1240 + 6  \n1240 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 335", "Answer": "A: 512", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n7 + 5 = 12\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1371", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 178", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n10 + 70 = 80\n4 + 8 = 12\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1559", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n10 + 40 = 50\n2 + 7 = 9\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 626", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 6  \n800 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 440", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n1300 + 90 = 1390  \n1390 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1507", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n3 + 4 = 7\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 4 = 11\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 112", "Answer": "A: 650", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 8 + 2\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 473", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n5 + 70 = 75\n1000 + 75 = 1075\n1075 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 475", "Answer": "A: 803", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n8 + 5 = 13  \n700 + 90 = 790  \n790 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 322", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n20 + 7 = 27  \n20 + 2 = 22  \n1000 + 27 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 447", "Answer": "A: 705", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 537", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n2 + 7 = 9\n760 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n5 + 40 = 45\n1100 + 45 = 1145\n1145 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n3 + 3 = 6\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 60 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 9 = 1059\n1059 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1607", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n12 + 90 = 102\n1500 + 102 = 1602\n1602 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1632", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n4 + 20 = 24\n1600 + 24 = 1624\n1624 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 212", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 375", "Answer": "A: 767", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n600 + 160 = 760  \n760 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 16 = 36\n1200 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 552", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n7 + 2 = 9\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 364", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n7 + 60 = 67\n1100 + 67 = 1167\n1167 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 20 = 30\n5 + 6 = 11\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 671", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 155", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n400 + 130 = 530  \n530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 515", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 10 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1576", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 30 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 497", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 232", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 9 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 410", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 10 = 100\n600 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1581", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 40 = 70\n4 + 7 = 11\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 312", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n8 + 12 = 20\n900 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 241", "Answer": "A: 454", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n10 + 40 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1397", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n70 + 20 = 90  \n1300 + 90 = 1390  \n1390 + 4   \n1390 + 3   "}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n12 + 40 = 52\n1100 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 666", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n800 + 130 = 930  \n930 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 212", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 128", "Answer": "A: 674", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 20 = 60\n6 + 8 = 14\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1636", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 50 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 420", "Answer": "A: 578", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 20 = 70\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 749", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 40 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n11 + 40 = 51  \n1500 + 51 = 1551  \n1551 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 321", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 20 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 107 + 791", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n7 + 90 = 97\n800 + 97 = 897\n897 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 211", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 454 + 387", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1822", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 60 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 154", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 504", "Answer": "A: 809", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n5 + 4 = 9\n800 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 423 + 426", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 20 = 40\n3 + 6 = 9\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 116", "Answer": "A: 293", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n7 + 6 = 13  \n200 + 80 = 280  \n280 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n9 + 6 = 15\n1400 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 485", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 7 + 5 = 1262"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 70 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 597", "Answer": "A: 1560", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 90 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 10 = 1560"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 336", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 30 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 2 + 6 = 1008"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 218", "Answer": "A: 398", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 18 = 98\n300 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1725", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 40 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 243", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n88 + 40 = 128\n1200 + 128 = 1328\n1328 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1263", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 410", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 511", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n4 + 1 = 5\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 251", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n1 + 50 = 51\n900 + 51 = 951\n951 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 477", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 198", "Answer": "A: 346", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 90 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 313", "Answer": "A: 811", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 10 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n91\n1000 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 615", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 10 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n3 + 20 = 23\n1100 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 60 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n6 + 70 = 76\n1300 + 76 = 1376\n1376 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n14 + 0 = 14\n1000 + 14 = 1014\n1014 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 4 + 8 = 1262"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 311", "Answer": "A: 665", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n50 + 10 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1685", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 123", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n4 + 20 = 24\n1000 + 24 = 1024\n1024 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 710 + 332", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 30 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 3 = 73\n1600 + 73 = 1673\n1673 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n15 + 50 = 65\n1300 + 65 = 1365\n1365 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 139", "Answer": "A: 299", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 30 = 90\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 40 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1675", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 40 = 70\n4 + 1 = 5\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 425", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n3 + 20 = 23\n1100 + 23 = 1123\n1123 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 591", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 1 = 91\n900 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 761", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n10 + 60 = 70\n7 + 1 = 8\n800 + 70 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 970", "Answer": "A: 1894", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 70 = 90\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n55 + 0 = 55\n1100 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 649", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 975 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 30 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 5 = 1805\n1805 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1138", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 174", "Answer": "A: 318", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 70 = 110 \n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 8 = 318"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 714", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 40 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 843", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n5 + 40 = 45\n1200 + 45 = 1245\n1245 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 733 + 237", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n3 + 7 = 10\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 479", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 170", "Answer": "A: 630", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 70 = 130\n500 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 615", "Answer": "A: 773", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 10 = 60\n8 + 5 = 13\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1798", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 60 = 90\n2 + 6 = 8\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 291", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 1 + 1 = 632"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1 + 8 = 9\n1400 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 508", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n40 + 0 = 40\n6 + 8 = 14\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 806", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 6 = 66\n900 + 66 = 966\n966 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1560", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 40 = 60\n1500 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1601", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 10 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 621", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 20 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 331", "Answer": "A: 875", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 30 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 4 \n870 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 4 = 84\n1000 + 84 = 1084\n1084 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 7 = 47\n1400 + 47 = 1447\n1447 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 305", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 0 = 40\n1 + 5 = 6\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 378", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n2 + 70 = 72\n600 + 72 = 672\n672 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 713", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n900 + 10 = 910\n910 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1143", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 6 = 13\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 30 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 = 1375\n1375 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 432", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n4 + 30 = 34\n900 + 34 = 934\n934 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 0 = 20\n7 + 8 = 15\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 550", "Answer": "A: 1012", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 684", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 = 896"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 104", "Answer": "A: 916", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n12 + 4 = 16\n900 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n2 + 80 = 82\n1300 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 80 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 309", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n80 + 9 = 89  \n1000 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 826", "Answer": "A: 1520", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1400 + 110 = 1510  \n1510 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 406", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n4 + 6 = 10\n1300 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1148", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 3 = 43\n1100 + 43 = 1143\n1143 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 20 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n8 + 40 = 48\n1100 + 48 = 1148\n1148 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 814", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 10 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n12 + 50 = 62\n1000 + 62 = 1062\n1062 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 314", "Answer": "A: 657", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n3 + 4 = 7\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 0 = 10\n1300 + 10 = 1310\n1310 + 2\n1310 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n1400 + 50 = 1450  \n1450 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 209", "Answer": "A: 767", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 0 = 50\n8 + 9 = 17\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1632", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 50 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 116", "Answer": "A: 394", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n78 + 16 = 94\n300 + 94"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 108", "Answer": "A: 445", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n30 + 8 = 38\n400 + 38 = 438\n438 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 261", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 60 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 339", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 9 = 13\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 209", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n6 + 9 = 15\n800 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 304 + 612", "Answer": "A: 916", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n4 + 10 = 14\n900 + 14 = 914\n914 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1537", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 189", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9 = 1039\n1039 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 258", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n17 + 50 = 67\n1000 + 67 = 1067\n1067 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 392", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 2 = 92\n700 + 92"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1322", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1977", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 90 = 170\n1800 + 170 = 1970\n1970 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 2 = 52\n1300 + 52 = 1352\n1352 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 328", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 3\n910 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060 \n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 20 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 7 + 4 = 1151"}
{"Question": "Q: 467 + 169", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 = 627\n627 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 208 + 319", "Answer": "A: 527", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n8 + 10 = 18\n500 + 18 = 518\n518 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 379", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n3 + 9 = 12  \n800 + 80 = 880  \n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 441", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n19 + 40 = 59\n1000 + 59 = 1059\n1059 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 10 = 20\n1100 + 20 = 1120\n1120 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 318", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n18 + 40 = 58\n1200 + 58 = 1258\n1258 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 662", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 60 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 191", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 90 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n15 + 50 = 65\n1000 + 65 = 1065\n1065 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1698", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 60 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 191", "Answer": "A: 494", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n3 + 90 = 93\n400 + 93 = 493\n493 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9 = 1289\n1289 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 104", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n5 + 4 = 9\n700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1466", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1615", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 10 = 100\n8 + 7 = 15\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 430", "Answer": "A: 664", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 30 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n8 + 9 = 17\n1400 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1611", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 90 = 100\n4 + 7 = 11\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1750", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 20 = 40\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 182", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n18 + 80 = 98\n800 + 98 = 898\n898 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 299", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 90 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 278", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 270", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 204", "Answer": "A: 323", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n19 + 4 = 23  \n300 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 323", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1707", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 5 = 1705\n1705 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 380", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 363", "Answer": "A: 759", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n600 + 150 = 750  \n750 + 9 = 759  \n759 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 466", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 60 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 4 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 142", "Answer": "A: 455", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 40 = 50\n3 + 2 = 5\n400 + 50 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 288", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 80 = 170\n5 + 8 = 13\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 177", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 70 = 140\n9 + 7 = 16\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 166", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9 = 929"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 205", "Answer": "A: 306", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n1 + 5 = 6\n300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 452", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 50 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 3 = 1383"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 499", "Answer": "A: 735", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n600 + 120 = 720  \n720 + 9  \n6 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 154", "Answer": "A: 339", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n200 + 130 = 330  \n330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 322", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 5 \n1300 + 5 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 178", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 382", "Answer": "A: 482", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 459", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 547", "Answer": "A: 832", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 5\n825 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 239", "Answer": "A: 574", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 9 = 14\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 292", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 2 \n820 + 2 = 824"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 106", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n80 + 6 = 86\n900 + 86 = 986\n986 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1636", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 40 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n7 + 2 = 9\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1629", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 10 = 20\n1600 + 20 = 1620\n1620 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 610 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 50 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 156", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1 + 4 = 5\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1606", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 80 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 3 = 1603\n1603 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1563", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1154", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n19 + 30 = 49\n1100 + 49 = 1149\n1149 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 632", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 519", "Answer": "A: 1391", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 10 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 6\n1370 + 5 "}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1434", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 341", "Answer": "A: 483", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n2 + 1 = 3  \n400 + 80 = 480  \n480 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 655", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n7 + 5 = 12\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1588", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n1500 + 80 = 1580  \n1580 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 109", "Answer": "A: 509", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 125", "Answer": "A: 452", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 20 = 40\n7 + 5 = 12\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 336", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n10 + 30 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 183", "Answer": "A: 466", "Explanation": "200 + 80 = 280\n3 + 80 = 83\n280 + 83 = 363\n363 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1493", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1750", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 10 = 50\n1700 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n7 + 20 = 27\n1200 + 27 = 1227\n1227 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n16 + 50 = 66\n1200 + 66 = 1266\n1266 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 497", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n500 + 120 = 620  \n620 + 12 = 632"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 105", "Answer": "A: 641", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 5 = 35\n600 + 35 = 635\n635 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 303", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 3 = 73\n1200 + 73 = 1273\n1273 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 156", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 50 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 247", "Answer": "A: 616", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 40 = 100\n9 + 7 = 16\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 100", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "894 + 100 = 994"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 475", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 = 627\n627 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 838", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 30 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n5 + 8 = 13\n1100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 382", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n1100 + 160 = 1260  \n1260 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1809", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 60 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n7 + 2 = 9\n1800 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 516", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n2 + 6 = 8\n1300 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 648", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 652", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 313", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 399", "Answer": "A: 599", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n500 + 99 = 599"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n19 + 5 = 24\n1000 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 262", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 120", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 20 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 195", "Answer": "A: 566", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 90 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 188", "Answer": "A: 478", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 80 = 170\n300 + 170 = 470\n470 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 161", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n8 + 1 = 9\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 128", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 20 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 839", "Answer": "A: 1822", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 30 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1637", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n3 + 30 = 33\n1600 + 33 = 1633\n1633 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n99 + 20 = 119\n1000 + 119"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 311", "Answer": "A: 441", "Explanation": "130 + 300 = 430\n430 + 11 = 441"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1597", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 10 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 50 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 3\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 691", "Answer": "A: 1687", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 90 = 180\n6 + 1 = 7\n1500 + 180 = 1680\n1680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 236", "Answer": "A: 438", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n2 + 30 = 32\n400 + 32 = 432\n432 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 20 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n5 + 2 = 7\n1400 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 496", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 9 = 29\n1300 + 29 = 1329\n1329 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 399", "Answer": "A: 848", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 105", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n97 + 5 = 102\n600 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 304", "Answer": "A: 460", "Explanation": "150 + 300 = 450\n6 + 4 = 10\n450 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 763", "Answer": "A: 1565", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n2 + 60 = 62\n1500 + 62 = 1562\n1562 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 569 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 637", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n2 + 7 = 9\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 277", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n6 + 70 = 76  \n800 + 76 = 876  \n876 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 612", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1758", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 0 = 50\n7 + 1 = 8\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 186", "Answer": "A: 757", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n600 + 150 = 750  \n750 + 7 = 757  \n757 - 1 = 756  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 216", "Answer": "A: 342", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 10 = 30\n300 + 30 = 330\n330 + 6\n330 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1771", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 40 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 491", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n1 + 90 = 91\n800 + 91 = 891\n891 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 7 + 7 = 1364"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 590", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "160 + 590 = 750  \n750 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 153", "Answer": "A: 365", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n10 + 50 = 60\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 80 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 221", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 603", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 3 = 23\n1300 + 23 = 1323\n1323 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n1700 + 100 = 1800  \n1800 + 5 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 311", "Answer": "A: 452", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 10 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 715", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 10 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1 + 2 = 3\n1550 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 727", "Answer": "A: 836", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n9 + 20 = 29\n800 + 29 = 829\n829 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 7 = 17\n1300 + 17 = 1317\n1317 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 117", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n8 + 7 = 15\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 445", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1 + 5 = 6\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 112", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n50 + 10 = 60  \n500 + 60 = 560  \n560 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 643", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 437", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n8 + 7 = 15  \n1300 + 120 = 1420  \n1420 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 187", "Answer": "A: 336", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 80 = 120\n9 + 7 = 16\n200 + 120 = 320\n320 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1200", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 10 = 1200"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 493", "Answer": "A: 693", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n93\n600 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 147", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n3 + 7 = 10\n900 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1805", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 30 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 118", "Answer": "A: 224", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n6 + 18 = 24\n200 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 116", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n6 + 6 = 12\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 989", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n2 + 20 = 22\n1400 + 22 = 1422\n1422 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 2 = 7\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 116", "Answer": "A: 541", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n5 + 6 = 11\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 198", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 90 = 140\n7 + 8 = 15\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 363", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n50 + 60 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 80 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1507", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 40 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 399", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 394 + 161", "Answer": "A: 555", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n400 + 150 = 550  \n550 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 409", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 0 = 50\n1 + 9 = 10\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 309", "Answer": "A: 749", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 9 = 49\n700 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 574", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 666", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n9 + 6 = 15\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 490", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n6 + 90 = 96\n600 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n2 + 80 = 82\n1100 + 82 = 1182\n1182 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 588 + 335", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5 + 8 = 923"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 496", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1623", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 90 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3 + 9 = 1622\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 119", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 80 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 214", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 4 = 14\n1100 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 203", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 3 = 13\n600 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 654 + 246", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n4 + 6 = 10\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 771", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n1 + 70 = 71\n800 + 71 = 871\n871 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 352", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 119", "Answer": "A: 310", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 10 = 100\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 10 = 310\n310 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 8 = 1328\n1328 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 378", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n60 + 70 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 6\n1036 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1498", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n1 + 90 = 91\n90 + 7 = 97\n1400 + 97 = 1497\n1497 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 0 = 30\n2 + 9 = 11\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n6 + 20 = 26\n1300 + 26 = 1326\n1326 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 487", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n2 + 80 = 82\n800 + 82 = 882\n882 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n1200 + 80 = 1280  \n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 159", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9\n939 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1411", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 10 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1992", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n96 + 96 = 192  \n1800 + 192"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1911", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 80 = 100\n1800 + 100 = 1900\n1900 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1685", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 80 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1467", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 0 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 352", "Answer": "A: 634", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 50 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n92 + 8 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n52\n1100 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1694", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n11 + 80 = 91\n1600 + 91 = 1691\n1691 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 70 = 140\n6 + 1 = 7\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1751", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n6 + 5 = 11  \n1600 + 140 = 1740  \n1740 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 80 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 7 = 1137\n1137 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 434", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n10 + 30 = 40  \n3 + 4 = 7  \n800 + 40 = 840  \n840 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 595", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 90 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 360", "Answer": "A: 494", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 60 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 479", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n6 + 70 = 76\n1100 + 76 = 1176\n1176 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 269", "Answer": "A: 678", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n9 + 60 = 69\n600 + 69 = 669\n669 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n14 + 88 = 102\n1000 + 102 = 1102"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 392", "Answer": "A: 669", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 90 = 160\n7 + 2 = 9\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 6 = 96\n1200 + 96 = 1296\n1296 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 250", "Answer": "A: 862", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n12 + 50 = 62\n800 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 306", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n51 + 6 = 57\n900 + 57"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 571", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 449", "Answer": "A: 1397", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 799 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1759", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n99 + 60 = 159\n1600 + 159"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 277", "Answer": "A: 750", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 70 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 482", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n1 + 80 = 81\n800 + 81 = 881\n881 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n2 + 20 = 22\n1100 + 22 = 1122\n1122 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 175", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 5\n1000 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 267", "Answer": "A: 810", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 60 = 100\n3 + 7 = 10\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 256", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 675", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 406", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 6 = 76\n900 + 76 = 976\n976 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 302", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 2 = 82\n900 + 82 = 982\n982 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 492", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 90 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 200", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 209", "Answer": "A: 654", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 0 = 40\n5 + 9 = 14\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 60 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 324", "Answer": "A: 620", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 605", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 5 = 55\n800 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 279", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 70 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 8\n630 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 20 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1618", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n12 + 6 = 18\n1600 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n5 + 4 = 9\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 60 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8 + 1 = 1049"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 2 = 22\n1400 + 22 = 1422\n1422 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 164", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 524", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n50 + 20 = 70\n3 + 4 = 7\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 772", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n900 + 9 = 909  \n909 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 566", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 3\n730 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1411", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 432", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 150", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 444", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n10 + 40 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 336", "Answer": "A: 597", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 30 = 90\n1 + 6 = 7\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 5 = 35\n1000 + 35 = 1035\n1035 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 625", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n75 + 25 = 100\n800 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 320", "Answer": "A: 611", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 20 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1787", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 40 = 80\n2 + 5 = 7\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 553", "Answer": "A: 891", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 309", "Answer": "A: 737", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 9 = 29\n700 + 29 = 729\n729 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 120", "Answer": "A: 720", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 130", "Answer": "A: 438", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n8 + 30 = 38\n400 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 651", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n10 + 50 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 277", "Answer": "A: 399", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 70 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1532", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n4 + 8 = 12\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 597", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 90 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 540", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 40 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7\n1120 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 30 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 786", "Answer": "A: 1247", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 191", "Answer": "A: 489", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 90 = 180\n300 + 180 = 480\n480 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 140", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1550", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n46 + 4 = 50\n1500 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1401", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n4 + 6 = 10\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 566", "Answer": "A: 746", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 300", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n20 + 3 = 23  \n900 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 591", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 90 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 325", "Answer": "A: 934", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n9 + 20 = 29\n900 + 29 = 929\n929 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1030", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n17 + 13 = 30\n1000 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n3 + 8 = 11\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n5 + 20 = 25\n1100 + 25 = 1125\n1125 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 362", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 50 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600 \n7 + 9 = 16\n1600 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 316", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n600 + 100 = 700  \n5 + 6 = 11  \n700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 359", "Answer": "A: 746", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 9 = 16\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 704", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 4 = 74\n900 + 74 = 974\n974 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 173", "Answer": "A: 536", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 70 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 3 = 533\n533 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 290", "Answer": "A: 393", "Explanation": "100 + 290 = 390\n390 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1683", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n50 + 20 = 70  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n1600 + 70 = 1670  \n1670 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n19 + 60 = 79\n1300 + 79 = 1379\n1379 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 208", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n8 + 8 = 16\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 153", "Answer": "A: 312", "Explanation": "100 + 50 = 150\n50 + 100 = 150\n150 + 150 = 300\n9 + 3 = 12\n300 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 669", "Answer": "A: 942", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 571", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 70 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 196", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 4 = 74\n900 + 74 = 974\n974 + 5 = 979\n979 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 410", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 10 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 396", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 8 = 848  \n848 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 211", "Answer": "A: 444", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 10 = 40\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 112", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n10 + 40 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1414", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n7 + 7 = 14\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 191", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 90 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1896", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 30 = 90\n4 + 2 = 6\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 20 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 217", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n6 + 7 = 13\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 50 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n2 + 7 = 9  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 181", "Answer": "A: 384", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n3 + 80 = 83\n300 + 83 = 383\n383 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 300", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n34\n800 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 366", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n1000 + 31 = 1031"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 206", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 6 = 36\n500 + 36 = 536\n536 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 199", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 168", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 119", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 10 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n5 + 9 = 14\n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 336", "Answer": "A: 1280", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 615", "Answer": "A: 717", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n2 + 15 = 17\n700 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 248", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 168", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 60 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n9 + 8 = 17\n900 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1490", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n10 + 70 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 668", "Answer": "A: 1576", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n8 + 60 = 68\n1500 + 68 = 1568\n1568 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 569", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 510", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n9 + 10 = 19\n1200 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 675", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 70 = 140\n9 + 5 = 14\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 139", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 30 = 100\n5 + 9 = 14\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 9 = 49\n1100 + 49 = 1149\n1149 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 143", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n40 + 40 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 385", "Answer": "A: 715", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 80 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 188", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n80 + 8 = 88  \n1000 + 88 = 1088  \n1088 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 288", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n4 + 80 = 84\n800 + 84 = 884\n884 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 396", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 129", "Answer": "A: 494", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 20 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 166", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 90 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1683", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 60 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 489", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n1200 + 170 = 1370  \n1370 + 7 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1368", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 4 = 8\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 490", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n1100 + 140 = 1240  \n1240 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 371", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 70 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 453", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n4 + 50 = 54\n1100 + 54 = 1154\n1154 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1651", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 50 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 0 = 90\n6 + 8 = 14\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 553", "Answer": "A: 812", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 50 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 9 = 809\n809 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 230", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 "}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 268", "Answer": "A: 382", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n10 + 60 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1436", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 6 = 1436"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1606", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 70 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 318", "Answer": "A: 1295", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 109", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n97 + 9 = 106\n600 + 106 = 706"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1559", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 90 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 521", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 109", "Answer": "A: 417", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n8 + 9 = 17\n400 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 108", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n88 + 8 = 96\n700 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 390", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n11 + 90 = 101\n1200 + 101"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 280", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n15 + 80 = 95\n700 + 95"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 383", "Answer": "A: 1322", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1200 + 110 = 1310  \n1310 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 0 = 50\n3 + 7 = 10\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 941", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 40 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 275", "Answer": "A: 880", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n5 + 70 = 75\n800 + 75 = 875\n875 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60\n1300 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 611", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 10 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 274", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 140", "Answer": "A: 283", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 40 = 80\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 285", "Answer": "A: 567", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 5 = 7\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1030", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n9 + 6 = 15\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 639", "Answer": "A: 842", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n3 + 30 = 33\n800 + 33 = 833\n833 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 30 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 317", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "640 + 300 = 940\n940 + 10 = 950\n950 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 333", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 348", "Answer": "A: 837", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1704", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n88 + 16 = 104  \n1600 + 104"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 519", "Answer": "A: 726", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n7 + 10 = 17\n700 + 17 = 717\n717 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 700", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n14  \n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n7 + 4 = 11\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 453", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 402", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 2 = 9\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 251", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n18 + 50 = 68\n1100 + 68 = 1168\n1168 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 516", "Answer": "A: 646", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 128", "Answer": "A: 836", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n8 + 20 = 28\n800 + 28 = 828\n828 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 347", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 137", "Answer": "A: 256", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n19 + 30 = 49  \n200 + 49 = 249  \n249 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 516", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n2 + 16 = 18\n1400 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 158", "Answer": "A: 317", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 8 = 17\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 506", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 6 = 26\n700 + 26 = 726\n726 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 70 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 244", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n8 + 40 = 48\n800 + 48 = 848\n848 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 694", "Answer": "A: 1655", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1 + 4 = 5\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 80 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 2 = 42\n1300 + 42 = 1344\n1344 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 70 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 352 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 8 = 1348"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n6 + 9 = 15\n1200 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 149", "Answer": "A: 438", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n9 + 9 = 18\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 174", "Answer": "A: 457", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 70 = 150\n3 + 4 = 7\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n89 + 10 = 99\n1100 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 123", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 20 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 176", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1281", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 250", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n28 + 50 = 78\n1000 + 78"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 323", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 3 = 6\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 310", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 522", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 4 = 994"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 4 = 1174\n1174 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 345", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 40 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1575", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n74 + 1 = 75\n1500 + 75"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 161", "Answer": "A: 881", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1520", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 475", "Answer": "A: 737", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 70 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 7 = 737"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 502", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n16 + 2 = 18\n1300 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 3 = 83\n1300 + 83 = 1383\n1383 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 261", "Answer": "A: 380", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n10 + 60 = 70\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n1400 + 50 = 1450  \n1450 + 1   "}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1565", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n3 + 2 = 5\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 433", "Answer": "A: 610", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 30 = 100\n7 + 3 = 10\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 217", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 6\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 253", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n10 + 50 = 60  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 60 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1826", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n10 + 6 = 16\n1800 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 144", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 160", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n1 + 60 = 61\n800 + 61"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 152", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n22 + 50 = 72  \n800 + 72 = 872  \n872 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 381", "Answer": "A: 518", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 80 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 373", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3 \n3 + 3 = 6\n900 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 100", "Answer": "A: 265", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 65 = 265\n265"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 466", "Answer": "A: 659", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 60 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 9 = 659\n659 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1831", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 9 = 29\n1800 + 29 = 1829\n1829 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 304", "Answer": "A: 447", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 0 = 40\n3 + 4 = 7\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 711", "Answer": "A: 907", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 10 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n5 + 3 = 8\n1000 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 153", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9 = 849\n849 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 238", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 8 = 13\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 387", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 318 + 138", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 30 = 40\n8 + 8 = 16\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 517", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 17 = 27\n900 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 233", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 30 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 304 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n4 + 30 = 34\n1200 + 34 = 1234\n1234 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 90 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 544", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n42 + 30 = 72\n1300 + 72 = 1372\n1372 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 40 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n2 + 8 = 10\n1100 + 120 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n1 + 1 = 2\n1000 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n57  \n1000 + 57"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 111", "Answer": "A: 1099", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n88 + 11 = 99\n1000 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 50 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 744", "Answer": "A: 1735", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n90 + 40 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 655", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 40 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7 = 1317"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 395", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 365", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 278", "Answer": "A: 538", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 70 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 532", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n4 + 30 = 34\n900 + 34 = 934\n934 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 50 = 60\n1100 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 227", "Answer": "A: 446", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n19 + 20 = 39\n400 + 39 = 439\n439 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1707", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 70 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 454 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 215", "Answer": "A: 345", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 15 = 45\n300 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1281", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 80 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 20 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 538", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 10 = 820"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1543", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 60 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1903", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 30 = 100\n1800 + 100 = 1900\n1 + 2 = 3\n1900 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n25 + 60 = 85\n1000 + 85 = 1085\n1085 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 50 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1920", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 70 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1847", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 3 = 43\n1800 + 43 = 1843\n1843 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1663", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n60 + 0 = 60  \n1600 + 60 = 1660  \n1660 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 235", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n2 + 30 = 32\n1000 + 32 = 1032\n1032 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 189", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1750", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 20 = 40\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 295", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 543", "Answer": "A: 817", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 122", "Answer": "A: 574", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 20 = 70\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 2 = 572\n572 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 295", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 90 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 50 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 632", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n4 + 2 = 6\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 235", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 5 = 35\n900 + 35 = 935\n935 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1 + 2 = 3\n1000 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 439", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 289", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n1 + 80 = 81\n600 + 81 = 681\n681 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 292", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1532", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 4 = 24\n1500 + 24 = 1524\n1524 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 612", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n5 + 12 = 17\n900 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n17 + 80 = 97\n1200 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1641", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n39 + 2 = 41\n1600 + 41"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 452", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 50 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1566", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 20 = 50\n9 + 7 = 16\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 459", "Answer": "A: 679", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n20 + 50 = 70  \n600 + 70 = 670  \n670 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1746", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n4 + 2 = 6  \n1600 + 140 = 1740  \n1740 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 325", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n5 + 25 = 30\n800 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1379", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 50 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 989", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 80 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 245", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1741", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n20 + 10 = 30  \n1700 + 30 = 1730  \n1730 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1695", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 10 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 356", "Answer": "A: 541", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 50 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 6\n530 + 5 = 535\n535 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 365", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n9 + 60 = 69\n1100 + 69 = 1169\n1169 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 552", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1550", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n7 + 40 = 47\n1500 + 47 = 1547\n1547 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 265", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 358", "Answer": "A: 563", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n5 + 50 = 55\n500 + 55 = 555\n555 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 306", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n34 + 6 = 40\n1000 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 90 = 140\n9 + 7 = 16\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 20 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 304", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 4 = 84\n500 + 84 = 584\n584 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 60 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 126", "Answer": "A: 306", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 20 = 100\n6\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 459", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 323", "Answer": "A: 705", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n2 + 3 = 5\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 476", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 70 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 413", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 10 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1427", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 90 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 694", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n26 + 3 = 29\n1300 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 262", "Answer": "A: 533", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 60 = 130\n1 + 2 = 3\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 372", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n4 + 2 = 6\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n11 + 9 = 20\n1500 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 124", "Answer": "A: 1000", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6\n996 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 4 = 24\n1100 + 24 = 1124\n1124 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1831", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 60 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n6 + 4 = 10\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1812", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 70 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n5 + 7 = 12\n1800 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 227", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 401", "Answer": "A: 772", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n71 + 1 = 72\n700 + 72"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 538", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n8 + 30 = 38\n900 + 38 = 938\n938 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 798", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1609", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 288", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1670", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 7 = 67\n1600 + 67 = 1667\n1667 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1952", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n90 + 60 = 150\n1800 + 150 = 1950\n1950 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n60 + 20 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 197", "Answer": "A: 788", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600 \n90 + 90 = 180 \n600 + 180 = 780 \n780 + 1 + 7 = 788"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1813", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n1700 + 100 = 1800  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n1800 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300    \n70 + 30 = 100    \n9 + 6 = 15    \n1300 + 100 = 1400    \n1400 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 60 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 585", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n8 + 5 = 13\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 552", "Answer": "A: 669", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n17 + 50 = 67\n600 + 67 = 667\n667 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1911", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 70 = 100\n3 + 8 = 11\n1800 + 100 = 1900\n1900 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3 = 1353\n1353 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1170", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 10 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 351", "Answer": "A: 554", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n3 + 50 = 53\n500 + 53 = 553\n553 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n2 + 90 = 92\n1200 + 92 = 1292\n1292 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 256", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 50 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 418", "Answer": "A: 641", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 10 = 30\n3 + 8 = 11\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 641", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 40 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 512", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 276", "Answer": "A: 405", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 70 = 90\n9 + 6 = 15\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 731", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1797", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n11 + 80 = 91\n1700 + 91 = 1791\n1791 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1319", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n7 + 10 = 17\n1300 + 17 = 1317\n1317 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 660", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 242", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 178", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 70 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 10 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 321", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 242", "Answer": "A: 465", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 40 = 60\n3 + 2 = 5\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n74 + 40 = 114\n1000 + 114 = 1114\n1114 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 759", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n2 + 50 = 52\n900 + 52 = 952\n952 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 106", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n90 + 6 = 96\n800 + 96 = 896\n896 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 575", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n600 + 80 = 680  \n680 + 5  \n680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n7 + 15 = 22\n1000 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n7 + 5 = 12\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 485", "Answer": "A: 1154", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 286", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 0 = 60\n9 + 7 = 16\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n60 + 0 = 60  \n6 + 8 = 14  \n1100 + 60 = 1160  \n1160 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 60 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 416", "Answer": "A: 695", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n9 + 6 = 15\n680 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 9 = 1549"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 194", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 543", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 40 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 299", "Answer": "A: 538", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 9 \n520 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1300 + 150 = 1450  \n1450 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 550", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "200 + 550 = 750\n750 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 216", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n19 + 16 = 35\n1100 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 616", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 400", "Answer": "A: 1046", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n46 + 0 = 46\n1000 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1770", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 70 = 1600\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 10 = 1770\n1770"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 463", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 60 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 577", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 126", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n15 + 20 = 35\n800 + 35 = 835\n835 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 40 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n4 + 5 = 9\n1400 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 640", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 447", "Answer": "A: 752", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n5 + 40 = 45\n700 + 45 = 745\n745 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 8 = 88\n1300 + 88 = 1388\n1388 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n6 + 30 = 36\n1200 + 36 = 1236\n1236 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1598", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 20 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1450", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1704", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 30 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 159", "Answer": "A: 318", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 514", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n9 + 4 = 13\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1882", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 9 = 89\n1700 + 89 = 1789\n1789 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 50 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 660", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n97 + 60 = 157  \n800 + 157  "}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 50 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 10 = 1270\n1270 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 352 + 542", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 304", "Answer": "A: 944", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 4 = 44\n900 + 44"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 398", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n90 + 8 = 98\n1200 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 415 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5\n1200 + 5 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 311", "Answer": "A: 581", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 390", "Answer": "A: 826", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 6 = 36\n700 + 36 = 736\n736 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 594", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1254", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 4 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n16 + 50 = 66\n1300 + 66 = 1366\n1366 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 234", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 168", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n1000 + 70 = 1070  \n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 60 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 612", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n19 + 20 = 39\n1300 + 39 = 1339\n1339 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1664", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 30 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 607", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n7 + 7 = 14  \n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1747", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 20 = 40\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1706", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 30 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1 + 5 = 6\n1700 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 603", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 0 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n9 + 3 = 12\n750 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 224", "Answer": "A: 759", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 20 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 4\n750 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1867", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n17 + 50 = 67\n1800 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 476", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 70 = 150\n7 + 6 = 13\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 273", "Answer": "A: 454", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n300 + 150 = 450  \n450 + 3  \n450 + 1 = 451  \n451 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 313", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 5 + 3 = 1008"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 60 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n4 + 5 = 9\n1440 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1786", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 20 = 80\n4 + 2 = 6\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n3 + 9 = 12\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1428", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1709", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 50 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1 + 8 = 9\n1700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 90 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 108 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n8 + 70 = 78\n1000 + 78 = 1078\n1078 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 455", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 410", "Answer": "A: 832", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 10 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 564", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 60 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 314", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 6 = 986"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n18 + 30 = 48  \n1000 + 48 = 1048  \n1048 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 30 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n9 + 30 = 39\n1000 + 39 = 1039\n1039 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1399", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 60 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 167", "Answer": "A: 812", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 60 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 5 \n800 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n99 + 80 = 179\n1300 + 179 = 1479\n1479 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 10 = 1330"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 164", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 486", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 231", "Answer": "A: 588", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 1 = 8\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 712", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "900 + 10 = 910\n\n190 + 700 = 890\n8 + 2 = 10\n890 + 10 = 900\n900 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 114", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 469", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n9 + 9 = 18\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 167 + 151", "Answer": "A: 318", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 50 = 110\n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 7 + 1 = 318"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1523", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 10 = 20\n1500 + 20 = 1520\n1520 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 428", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 591", "Answer": "A: 1458", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 90 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 363", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5\n1080 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1703", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 20 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 10 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 6 \n1230 + 6 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 536", "Answer": "A: 736", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 6 = 36\n700 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 336", "Answer": "A: 605", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 30 = 90\n9 + 6 = 15\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 733 + 348", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n3 + 8 = 11\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 327", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1548", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 6  \n1480 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 165", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 60 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n4 + 40 = 44\n1200 + 44"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 457", "Answer": "A: 609", "Explanation": "150 + 450 = 600\n2 + 7 = 9\n600 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 605", "Answer": "A: 741", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 5 = 35\n700 + 35 = 735\n735 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 656", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1490", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 10 = 1490"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n71 + 20 = 91\n1400 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 505", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 5 = 25\n1100 + 25 = 1125\n1125 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 235", "Answer": "A: 661", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1931", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n1800 + 120 = 1920  \n1920 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1703", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n11 + 90 = 101\n1600 + 101 = 1701\n1701 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 117", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 185", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 215", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 236", "Answer": "A: 627", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 30 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1 + 2 = 3\n1400 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n1 + 3 = 4\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 288", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n7 + 8 = 15  \n900 + 160 = 1060  \n1060 + 15  "}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1597", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 0 = 80\n8 + 9 = 17\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 984", "Answer": "A: 1863", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 80 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1578", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 90 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 7 = 1157\n1157 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 591", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 557", "Answer": "A: 726", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n10 + 6 = 16\n1000 + 16 = 1016\n1016 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 600", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70\n800 + 70"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 360", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 140", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 40 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 357", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n48 + 50 = 98  \n1100 + 98 = 1198  \n1198 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 286", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 80 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 319", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 682", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 30 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 838", "Answer": "A: 1721", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 30 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 424", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n18 + 20 = 38\n1000 + 38 = 1038\n1038 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 70 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 668", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n16 + 60 = 76\n900 + 76 = 976\n976 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 174", "Answer": "A: 642", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 70 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 837", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 313", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 10 = 20\n1200 + 20 = 1220\n1220 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n5 + 90 = 95\n900 + 95 = 995\n995 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 239", "Answer": "A: 510", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n1 + 9 = 10\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 216", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n11 + 6 = 17\n1100 + 17 = 1117\n1117 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 744", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n9 + 9 = 18  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 333", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n29 + 30 = 59\n1000 + 59 = 1059\n1059 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 330", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n28 + 30 = 58\n1100 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 627", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 558", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 6 + 8 = 744"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 114", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1 + 4 = 5\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 736", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n6 + 6 = 12\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n1400 + 80 = 1480  \n1480 + 7  \n1480 + 8 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 9\n1469 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 145", "Answer": "A: 384", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 40 = 70\n9 + 5 = 14\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 284", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n90 + 80 = 170\n300 + 170 = 470\n470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 511", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n4 + 10 = 14\n1400 + 14\n1400 + 14 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n93\n1100 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1851", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 8 = 48\n1800 + 48 = 1848\n1848 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 324 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1466", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 180", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1651", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 70 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 343", "Answer": "A: 528", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 40 = 120\n5 + 3 = 8\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 267 + 408", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 0 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 843 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1604", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1792", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 40 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 142", "Answer": "A: 590", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n40 + 40 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 156", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 318", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 10 = 40\n5 + 8 = 13\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 559", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 195", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5 = 1125\n1125 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n4 + 10 = 14\n1600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 50 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1728", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 18 = 28\n1700 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 10 = 70\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1478", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 50 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 479", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 4\n1154 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1070", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n14 + 50 = 64\n1000 + 64 = 1064\n1064 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 374", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n8 + 70 = 78  \n600 + 78 = 678  \n678 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 766", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1400 + 110 = 1510  \n1510 + 8 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1631", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n31 + 0 = 31  \n1600 + 31  "}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 453", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 3 = 33\n1000 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 130", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 30 = 60\n600 + 60 "}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 427", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n600 + 40 = 640  \n640 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 714", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 105", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 5 = 75\n500 + 75 = 575\n575 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 335", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 8 = 828\n828 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 324", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n8 + 90 = 98\n1000 + 98 = 1098\n1098 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n9 + 9 = 18  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 481", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n9 + 70 = 79\n1000 + 79 = 1079\n1079 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1760", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 0 = 60\n1700 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 50 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1304", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n40 + 60 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 281", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 80 = 100\n3 + 1 = 4\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 546", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 40 = 130\n6 + 6 = 12\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 70 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 351", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n11 + 50 = 61\n600 + 61 = 661\n661 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 476", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 312", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n2 + 2 = 4  \n1000 + 40 = 1040  \n1040 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 104", "Answer": "A: 642", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n30 + 4 = 34  \n600 + 34 = 634  \n634 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n3 + 9 = 12\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1722", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 80 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1926", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 80 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 5\n1925 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n1000 + 100 = 1100  \n1100 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 269", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n500 + 70 = 570  \n570 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n4 + 3 = 7\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 242", "Answer": "A: 521", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n400 + 110 = 510  \n510 + 9  \n510 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 543", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1519", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1400 + 110 = 1510  \n1510 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 407", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 0 = 60\n5 + 7 = 12\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 323", "Answer": "A: 424", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n1 + 20 = 21\n400 + 21 = 421\n421 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 40 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n72 + 30 = 102  \n1300 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 252", "Answer": "A: 444", "Explanation": "190 + 250 = 440  \n2 + 2 = 4  \n440 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 166", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 60 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 848", "Answer": "A: 1593", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 8 = 13\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 347", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 7 = 827  \n827 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1838", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 2 = 32\n1800 + 32 = 1832\n1832 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 436", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 30 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 30 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 461", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 207", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n40 + 7 = 47\n800 + 47"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 386", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n600 + 170 = 770  \n770 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 40 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 290", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n55 + 90 = 145\n500 + 145"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 300", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 0 = 40\n1100 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 = 1215"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 339", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 489", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 9 + 6 = 885"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 179", "Answer": "A: 741", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 70 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9 = 739\n739 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 247", "Answer": "A: 457", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n10 + 40 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1791", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n1700 + 80 = 1780  \n1780 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 236", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8\n1110 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 328", "Answer": "A: 614", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 20 = 100\n6 + 8 = 14\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 297", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 90 = 180\n2 + 7 = 9\n600 + 180 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1696", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n8 + 80 = 88\n1600 + 88 = 1688\n1688 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n4 + 50 = 54  \n1200 + 54 = 1254  \n1254 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 123", "Answer": "A: 628", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n5 + 20 = 25\n600 + 25 = 625\n625 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 306", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 6 = 66\n600 + 66 = 666\n666 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n6 + 7 = 13\n1500 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1752", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 10 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1612", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 50 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n6 + 6 = 12\n1600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1428", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1 + 7 = 8\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 439", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 9\n800 + 5\n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 100", "Answer": "A: 206", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n2 + 7 = 9\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 139", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n19 + 30 = 49\n1000 + 49 = 1049\n1049 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 248", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 424", "Answer": "A: 1372", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 20 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 678", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n3 + 70 = 73\n700 + 73 = 773\n773 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 105", "Answer": "A: 242", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 5 = 35\n200 + 35 = 235\n235 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 526", "Answer": "A: 747", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 20 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 252", "Answer": "A: 627", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n75 + 50 = 125  \n500 + 125 = 625  \n625 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1885", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 0 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n1800 + 70 = 1870\n1870 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 432", "Answer": "A: 1393", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 474", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 4 = 6\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 433", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 30 = 120\n5 + 3 = 8\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n75 + 50 = 125  \n1000 + 125 = 1125  \n1125 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 706", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 6 = 36\n1400 + 36 = 1436\n1436 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 349", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n8 + 9 = 17  \n800 + 60 = 860  \n860 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 182", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 834", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1200 + 100 = 1300  \n1300 + 8 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1 + 6 = 7\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 1\n1221 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 185", "Answer": "A: 598", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n10 + 80 = 90\n3 + 5 = 8\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 216", "Answer": "A: 591", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 104", "Answer": "A: 526", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 4 = 24\n500 + 24 = 524\n524 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 40 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 10 = 1580"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 480", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n2 + 80 = 82\n600 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 383", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 5 = 1335\n1335 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 465", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n10 + 60 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n6 + 80 = 86\n1100 + 86 = 1186\n1186 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 121", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 20 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 179", "Answer": "A: 667", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n500 + 150 = 650  \n650 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1460", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n5 + 50 = 55\n1400 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 241", "Answer": "A: 344", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n3 + 40 = 43\n300 + 43 = 343\n343 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1576", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n10 + 50 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1718", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 80 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1943", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 80 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 642", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 10 = 1160"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 714", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n900 + 20 = 920\n920 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1450", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n10 + 40 = 50\n1400 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1369", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 20 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 281", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 9 = 59\n1300 + 59"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 454 + 204", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600  \n50 + 4 = 54  \n54 + 200 = 254  \n600 + 54 = 654  \n654 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 616 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n16 + 80 = 96\n1400 + 96 = 1496\n1496 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1717", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 60 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n8 + 9 = 17\n1700 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n15 + 80 = 95\n1300 + 95 = 1395\n1395 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 112", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n27 + 10 = 37\n800 + 37 = 837\n837 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 413", "Answer": "A: 903", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1809", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 90 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 410", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 457", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n5 + 7 = 12\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 460", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n3 + 60 = 63  \n800 + 63  "}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n19 + 8 = 27\n1000 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n4 + 3 = 7\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 691", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n10 + 90 = 100\n4 + 1 = 5\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 524", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 199", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n600 + 160 = 760  \n760 + 7 + 9 = 776  "}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 207", "Answer": "A: 826", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n19 + 7 = 26\n800 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 315", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1646", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n6 + 40 = 46\n1600 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 424", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n9 + 4 = 13\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 167", "Answer": "A: 350", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 60 = 140\n3 + 7 = 10\n200 + 140 = 340\n340 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 383", "Answer": "A: 666", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 80 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n10 + 80 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 523", "Answer": "A: 1290", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 529", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n9 + 8 = 17\n900 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 140", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n14 + 40 = 54\n800 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n5 + 1 = 6\n1000 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 210", "Answer": "A: 907", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n6 + 6 = 12\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n6 + 18 = 24\n1000 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 204", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n90 + 4 = 94  \n1000 + 94 = 1094  \n1094 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 381", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 80 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1533", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 6 = 13\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 516", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n17 + 50 = 67\n1200 + 67 = 1267\n1267 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 395", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 90 = 180\n800 + 180 = 980\n980 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 463", "Answer": "A: 644", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 60 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 625", "Answer": "A: 848", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 20 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 452", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n1 + 50 = 51\n600 + 51 = 651 \n651 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 687", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 701", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n60 + 0 = 60  \n800 + 60 = 860  \n860 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 193", "Answer": "A: 402", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n9 + 90 = 99  \n300 + 99 = 399  \n399 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 505", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n50 + 5 = 55  \n1000 + 55 = 1055  \n1055 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 406", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n4 + 6 = 10\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n5 + 2 = 7\n1300 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 30 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n11 + 30 = 41\n1000 + 41 = 1041\n1041 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 707", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 7 = 77\n900 + 77 = 977\n977 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 602", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n19 + 2 = 21\n700 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 232", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 30 = 70\n4 + 2 = 6\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1662", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 60 = 150\n5 + 7 = 12\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 539", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 6\n910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 158", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n90 + 50 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n4 + 1 = 5\n1100 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 574", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 4 = 9\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1886", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 40 = 70\n9 + 7 = 16\n1800 + 70 = 1870\n1870 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1434", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 182", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 3 = 1163\n1163 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 702", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 2 = 82\n900 + 82 = 982\n982 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 172", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 70 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 338", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n7 + 8 = 15  \n900 + 70 = 970  \n970 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n1400 + 100 = 1500  \n1500 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 198", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 90 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1591", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 10 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1447", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n40 + 1 = 41  \n1400 + 41 = 1441  \n1441 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 503", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 0 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 40 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7 = 1437\n1437 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 4 = 6\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 109", "Answer": "A: 421", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 9 = 19\n400 + 19 = 419\n419 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8 + 9 = 1310 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 249", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n4 + 40 = 44\n600 + 44 = 644\n644 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1888", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n8 + 80 = 88\n1800 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1162", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 349", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 133", "Answer": "A: 541", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n8 + 30 = 38\n500 + 38 = 538\n538 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 367", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9\n1010 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 746", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 40 = 70\n6 + 6 = 12\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 137", "Answer": "A: 687", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 30 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 10 = 20\n1300 + 20 = 1320\n1320 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 343", "Answer": "A: 891", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n8 + 3 = 11\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 636", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n7 + 10 = 17\n1200 + 17 = 1217\n1217 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 783", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n19 + 80 = 99\n1000 + 99 = 1099\n1099 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 350", "Answer": "A: 687", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n4 + 2 = 6\n1100 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 7 = 47\n1300 + 47 = 1347\n1347 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 312", "Answer": "A: 585", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 145", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n10 + 40 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 7 + 5\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 763", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 905 + 322", "Answer": "A: 1227", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n5 + 20 = 25\n1200 + 25 = 1225\n1225 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 240", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 354", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n7 + 50 = 57\n700 + 57 = 757\n757 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 335", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1845", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 60 = 140\n1700 + 140 = 1840\n1840 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1522", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n8 + 14 = 22\n1500 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 708", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n15 + 8 = 23\n1300 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 398", "Answer": "A: 615", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n17 + 90 = 107  \n500 + 107 = 607  \n607 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1789", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 10 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 10 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 132", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n4 + 30 = 34\n900 + 34 = 934\n934 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n15 + 9 = 24\n1400 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 127", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 7 = 947\n947 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 173", "Answer": "A: 678", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n5 + 70 = 75\n600 + 75 = 675\n675 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 114", "Answer": "A: 800", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 6\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 554", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 50 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 5\n720 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n17 + 30 = 47\n1000 + 47"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 410", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1724", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 90 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 324", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n1 + 20 = 21\n1000 + 21 = 1021\n1021 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n9 + 4 = 13  \n1300 + 40 = 1340  \n1340 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 394 + 141", "Answer": "A: 535", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n400 + 130 = 530  \n530 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 359", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n600 + 140 = 740  \n740 + 9 + 2 = 751  "}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 8 = 38\n1200 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 60 = 140\n7 + 5 = 12\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1762", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 70 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 570", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 409", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 9 = 19\n900 + 19 = 919\n919 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 992 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1878", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 80 = 170\n1700 + 170 = 1870\n1870 + 8 = 1878"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n1000 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 313", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n900 + 20 = 920\n920 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n\n60 + 40 = 100\n\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n\n1200 + 1\n\n1200 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 678 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n1300 + 110 = 1410  \n1410 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n18 + 50 = 68\n1400 + 68 = 1468\n1468 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 60 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 203", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 3 = 93\n1000 + 93 = 1093\n1093 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 241", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 10 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1899", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 70 = 90\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 9 = 1899"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 491", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 566", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1642", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 60 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 437", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n2 + 7 = 9\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 257", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 20 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 20 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1585", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n5 + 80 = 85\n1500 + 85"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 295", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 393", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n1100 + 180 = 1280  \n1280 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 113", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 107 + 501", "Answer": "A: 608", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n7 + 1 = 8\n600 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1689", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 90 = 180\n1500 + 180 = 1680\n1680 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 10 = 1240\n1240"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 290", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 90 = 180\n500 + 180 = 680\n680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 40 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 294", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 4 = 74\n1000 + 74 = 1074\n1074 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 949 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 101", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n71 + 1 = 72\n600 + 72"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1620", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 20 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 610 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 393", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 90 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 311", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 1 = 8\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 992 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1771", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n90 + 70 = 160\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 447 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 7 = 14\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 100", "Answer": "A: 251", "Explanation": "150 + 100 = 250\n250 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1374", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 50 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1490", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 30 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 10 = 1490"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 358", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n6 + 8 = 14\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n1200 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n6 + 20 = 26\n1200 + 26 = 1226\n1226 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 213", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 80 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 303", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 3 = 53\n1200 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n60 + 90 = 150   \n1000 + 150 = 1150  \n1150 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 357", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n8 + 7 = 15\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1853", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n3 + 50 = 53\n1800 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 703", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 3 = 53\n800 + 53 = 853\n853 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 646", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n3 + 6 = 9\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 333", "Answer": "A: 457", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 30 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1545", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 5 + 7 = 1542\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 285", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n1000 + 170 = 1170  \n1170 + 5 = 1175  \n1175 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 342", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 158", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 8 = 718\n718 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1686", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 50 = 80\n4 + 2 = 6\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1767", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n7 + 60 = 67\n1700 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 658", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 596", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3\n813 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1280", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 125", "Answer": "A: 473", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 20 = 60\n8 + 5 = 13\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 491", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n8 + 6 = 14\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 254 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1812", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n1700 + 110 = 1810  \n1810 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1000 + 100 = 1100  \n8 + 9 = 17  \n1100 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010 \n1010 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n8 + 6 = 14\n1150 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1788", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 10 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 542", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 296", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 90 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 4 = 44\n1100 + 44 = 1144\n1144 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 30 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 497 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1488", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n1300 + 180 = 1480  \n1480 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 408", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 0 = 30\n7 + 8 = 15\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 700 + 436", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 6 = 36\n1100 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 577", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 686", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 80 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 926", "Answer": "A: 1925", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n90 + 20 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 372", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 70 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 3 = 823\n823 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 574", "Answer": "A: 825", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 409", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 0 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 675", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 70 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 750", "Answer": "A: 880", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 184", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 266", "Answer": "A: 595", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 60 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 9 \n580 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 155", "Answer": "A: 275", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 50 = 70\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 212", "Answer": "A: 397", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 10 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 174", "Answer": "A: 452", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 70 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1856", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 60 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 1 + 5 = 1856"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n8 + 10 = 18 \n1000 + 18 = 1018\n1018 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1801", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 30 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 166", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 9 = 959  \n959 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n8 + 70 = 78  \n1400 + 78 = 1478  \n1478 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1784", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 90 = 180\n3 + 1 = 4\n1600 + 180 = 1780\n1780 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 90 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 104", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n99 + 4 = 103\n1000 + 103"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 40 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 373", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 9 = 1269\n1269 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 235", "Answer": "A: 655", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 40 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 623", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 1 = 31\n1200 + 31 = 1231\n1231 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n3 + 30 = 33\n1100 + 33 = 1133\n1133 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 584", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3\n1020 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 168", "Answer": "A: 628", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 953 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1825", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 70 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 5 = 1825\n1825 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 473", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1735", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 90 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n8 + 30 = 38\n1300 + 38 = 1338\n1338 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 602", "Answer": "A: 1304", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n2 + 2 = 4\n1300 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 50 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1622", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n6 + 16 = 22\n1600 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1765", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n7 + 50 = 57\n1700 + 57 = 1757\n1757 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 176", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n5 + 6 = 11\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 346", "Answer": "A: 604", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n50 + 40 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 8 = 598\n598 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 319", "Answer": "A: 890", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n2 + 2 = 4\n1200 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 614", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 568", "Answer": "A: 712", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 60 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 8\n700 + 4 = 704\n704 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 3 = 33\n1000 + 33 = 1033\n1033 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 257", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 7 + 7 = 1054"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 348", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 439", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 108", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n29 + 8 = 37  \n1000 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 766", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 149", "Answer": "A: 749", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n49 \n700 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 155", "Answer": "A: 330", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n75 + 50 = 125\n200 + 125 = 325\n325 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 346 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n6 + 8 = 14\n50 + 14 = 64\n1000 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n10 + 10 = 20\n1100 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 256", "Answer": "A: 372", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n16 + 50 = 66\n300 + 66 = 366\n366 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 422", "Answer": "A: 597", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 20 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 975 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1503", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 20 = 90\n5 + 8 = 13\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 8 = 15\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 435", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 30 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 182", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 205", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 5 = 25\n700 + 25 = 725\n725 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 70 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1567", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 460", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n8 + 60 = 68\n700 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 224", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 7\n1000 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n8 + 1 = 9\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 421", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 10  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 90 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n2 + 4 = 6\n1300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 147", "Answer": "A: 436", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n9 + 7 = 16\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 153", "Answer": "A: 402", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 50 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 397", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n90 + 90 = 180\n2 + 7 = 9\n600 + 180 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 353", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 2\n782 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 230", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n50 + 30 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 224", "Answer": "A: 567", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 4 = 7\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1138", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 304", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n83 + 4 = 87   \n800 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 363", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 484", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n50 + 80 = 130  \n1200 + 130 = 1330  \n1330 + 8 "}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 744", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 12 = 102\n1400 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 624", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 20 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1100 + 100 = 1200  \n1200 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1633", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 80 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1447", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n2 + 5 = 7\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 50 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n20 + 30 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1803", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 50 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 368", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 185", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 80 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 489", "Answer": "A: 1397", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n8 + 80 = 88\n1300 + 88 = 1388\n1388 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 561", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1639", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n18 + 20 = 38\n1600 + 38 = 1638\n1638 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 491", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n1 + 90 = 91\n1200 + 91 = 1291\n1291 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 136", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n17 + 30 = 47\n900 + 47 = 947\n947 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 9 = 69\n1400 + 69"}
{"Question": "Q: 953 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 0 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n9 + 4 = 13\n1100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 13  "}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 600", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n35 + 0 = 35\n900 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6 = 1146"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 102", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n8 + 2 = 10\n900 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 683", "Answer": "A: 842", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 263", "Answer": "A: 616", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 60 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 3 = 613\n613 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1721", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n70 + 40 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8 = 1338"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 351", "Answer": "A: 502", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 50 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1563", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 2 = 7\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 119", "Answer": "A: 807", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 497 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7\n1220 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 135", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n4 + 30 = 34\n700 + 34 = 734\n734 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 70 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6\n1180 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 5 \n1230 + 5 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 437", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 9 = 1359\n1359 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 479", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 671", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1508", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n50 + 50 = 100  \n1400 + 100 = 1500  \n1500 + 7  \n1500 + 7 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 2 = 22\n1300 + 22 = 1322\n1322 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 492", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 207", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n4 + 7 = 11\n900 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 419", "Answer": "A: 694", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 560", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n17 + 60 = 77\n600 + 77"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1841", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 1 = 41\n1800 + 41"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 313", "Answer": "A: 622", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n9 + 3 = 12\n600 + 12 = 612\n612 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 80 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 759", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 + 9 = 930"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n20 + 5 = 25  \n1200 + 25 = 1225  \n1225 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 474", "Answer": "A: 615", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 566", "Answer": "A: 714", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 60 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n8 + 6 = 14\n700 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 402", "Answer": "A: 615", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n13 + 2 = 15\n600 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1552", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 6\n1540 + 6 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 464", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n44 + 60 = 104  \n700 + 104 = 804  \n804 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 641", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1782", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 40 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n6 + 50 = 56\n1300 + 56 = 1356\n1356 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1689", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 90 = 180\n4 + 5 = 9\n1500 + 180 = 1680\n1680 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 764", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n7 + 60 = 67\n900 + 67 = 967\n967 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 327", "Answer": "A: 623", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 20 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n7 + 40 = 47\n1300 + 47 = 1347\n1347 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 459", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1 + 9 = 10\n1300 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 646", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n9 + 40 = 49\n800 + 49 = 849\n849 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 218", "Answer": "A: 393", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 10 = 80\n5 + 8 = 13\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 275", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 0 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 9\n1369 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 592", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n9 + 90 = 99\n700 + 99 = 799\n799 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 7 = 1337\n1337 -"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 401", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n28 + 1 = 29\n1200 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1148", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n2 + 6 = 8\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 683", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 3 = 853\n853 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 669", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 60 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 531", "Answer": "A: 916", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 40 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 381", "Answer": "A: 525", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 80 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 5 = 525"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 718", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n3 + 18 = 21\n900 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 540", "Answer": "A: 695", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100  \n55 + 50 = 105  \n1100 + 105 = 1205  \n1205 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1828", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 30 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 7 + 1 = 1828"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 105", "Answer": "A: 797", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 0 = 90\n2 + 5 = 7\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 350", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n400 + 140 = 540  \n540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 190", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 443", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n5 + 3 = 8\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 205", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 5 = 25\n1100 + 25 = 1125\n1125 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 511", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n900 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 7 = 67\n1200 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 324", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 4 = 13\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 519", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n2 + 19 = 21\n700 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 349", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n15 + 40 = 55  \n500 + 55 = 555  \n555 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 176", "Answer": "A: 288", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 70 = 80\n2 + 6 = 8\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 60 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n5 + 60 = 65\n1000 + 65 = 1065\n1065 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 185", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n4 + 5 = 9\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 277", "Answer": "A: 560", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 70 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 10 = 560"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 490", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n6 + 8 = 14\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 246", "Answer": "A: 717", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 179", "Answer": "A: 385", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n6 + 70 = 76\n300 + 76 = 376\n376 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 563", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 531", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1684", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 20 = 80\n3 + 1 = 4\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100 \n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 7 = 1007\n1007 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1369", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 80 = 160\n4 + 5 = 9\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 335", "Answer": "A: 736", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n1 + 30 = 31\n700 + 31 = 731\n731 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 3 = 23\n1300 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 609", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 0 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 9 = 969\n969 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 327", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n800 + 80 = 880  \n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 50 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 177", "Answer": "A: 611", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 70 = 100\n100 + 4 = 104\n104 + 77 = 181\n500 + 181"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 109", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n50 + 0 = 50  \n2 + 9 = 11  \n700 + 50 = 750  \n750 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n19 + 9 = 28\n1000 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 534", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1718", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 20 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090 \n1090 + 9 + 8 "}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 510", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400   \n44 + 10 = 54  \n1400 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n4 + 9 = 13\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 145", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n7 + 50 = 57\n1100 + 57 = 1157\n1157 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 60 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 4 + 7 = 1341"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 145", "Answer": "A: 316", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n\n70 + 40 = 110\n\n200 + 110 = 310\n\n310 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 70 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 457", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n5 + 7 = 12\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 303", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 3 = 33\n900 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 602", "Answer": "A: 1399", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n97 + 2 = 99\n1300 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 400", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n76\n700 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 502", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 0 = 70\n4 + 2 = 6\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 459", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 7 \n1340 + 9 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1558", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n1 + 50 = 51\n1500 + 51 = 1551\n1551 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 403", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 3 = 33\n900 + 33 = 933\n933 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 443", "Answer": "A: 705", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 524", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 187", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 80 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 9\n449 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 60 = 120\n5 + 8 = 13\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1379", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 189", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n2 + 80 = 82\n900 + 82 = 982\n982 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 371", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n  80 + 70 = 150  \n  600 + 150 = 750  \n  750 + 5 = 755  \n  "}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1623", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 80 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 363", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n5 + 3 = 8\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 554", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 442", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n14 + 20 = 34\n1300 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 429", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 395", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 10  "}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1628", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 0 = 20\n7 + 1 = 8\n1600 + 20 = 1620\n1620 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 131", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1538", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 9 = 99\n1400 + 99 = 1499\n1499 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 102", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n2 + 2 = 4\n500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 414", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 10 = 60\n7 + 4 = 11\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 262", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n\n10 + 60 = 70\n\n900 + 70 = 970\n\n970 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 100", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "900 + 90 = 990\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 456", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 162", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "800 + 160 = 960\n10 + 2 = 12\n960 + 12 "}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 639", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n9 + 9 = 18\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 264", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 6 = 56\n1300 + 56 = 1356\n1356 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 286", "Answer": "A: 542", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n50 + 80 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 6 = 536\n536 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 134", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n6 + 4 = 10\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 605", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 0 = 50\n9 + 5 = 14\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n3 + 8 = 11\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1627", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n27 + 0 = 27\n1600 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 767", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 30 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n4 + 80 = 84\n1500 + 84 = 1584\n1584 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 6 = 13\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 657", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n1 + 50 = 51\n800 + 51 = 851\n851 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 151", "Answer": "A: 450", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n300 - 1 = 299\n299 + 1 = 300\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 - 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1683", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 70 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1627", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 80 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 160", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 60 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 4 + 5 = 1159"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 306", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n54 + 6 = 60\n600 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 292", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 90 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 603", "Answer": "A: 729", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 3 = 23\n700 + 23 = 723\n723 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n8 + 50 = 58\n1200 + 58 = 1258\n1258 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 105", "Answer": "A: 503", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n98 + 5 = 103\n400 + 103"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 305", "Answer": "A: 577", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 0 = 70\n2 + 5 = 7\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1583", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 6 = 13\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 297", "Answer": "A: 642", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 7 = 12\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 766", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 10 = 1260\n1260 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1617", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n15 + 2 = 17\n1600 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 926", "Answer": "A: 1603", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 20 = 90\n7 + 6 = 13\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 376", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 70 = 140\n8 + 6 = 14\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 496", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n20 + 90 = 110  \n1200 + 110 = 1310  \n1310 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1515", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 504", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 4 = 64\n1000 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 90 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 514", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 4 = 14\n1300 + 14 = 1314\n1314 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 332", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n7 + 30 = 37\n500 + 37 = 537\n537 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 427", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 20 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1615", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 80 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 318", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 2\n750 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 440", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 207", "Answer": "A: 596", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 0 = 80\n9 + 7 = 16\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1755", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 70 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 370", "Answer": "A: 526", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n400 + 120 = 520  \n520 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 113", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 3 = 973\n973 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 562", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 10 = 990"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1946", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 70 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 228", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n4 + 8 = 12\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 454", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 309", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 4 = 94\n900 + 94 = 994\n994 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1739", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 10 = 30\n1700 + 30 = 1730\n1730 + 9 = 1739"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 283", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 3 = 5\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200 \n7 + 5 = 12\n1200 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 573", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n10 + 70 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6 = 1186"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n6 + 7 = 13\n1500 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 162", "Answer": "A: 305", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 60 = 100\n3 + 2 = 5\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 900 = 970\n970 + 7 = 977\n977 + 200"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1525", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 5 = 1525"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 0 = 50\n4 + 9 = 13\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 251", "Answer": "A: 377", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 50 = 70\n6 + 1 = 7\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 50 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 131", "Answer": "A: 441", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 30 = 40\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130 \n\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1299", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 30 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 134", "Answer": "A: 338", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n4 + 30 = 34\n300 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 90 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1522", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1365", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 90 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 402", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n4 + 2 = 6  \n800 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 134", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 30 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 4 = 684\n684 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5\n1200 + 6 \n\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1511", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 412", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n60 + 80 = 140   \n900 + 140 = 1040   \n1040 + 3   "}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 409", "Answer": "A: 809", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n800 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n6 + 9 = 15\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 30 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 9 + 4 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 40 = 50\n1000 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 517", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 10 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 5 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 309", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n90 + 9 = 99\n1200 + 99 = 1299\n1299 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 10 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1552", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 6 + 6 = 1552"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1714", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n5 + 9 = 14\n1700 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 457", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 10 = 940"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 469", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n3 + 3 = 6\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n60 + 4 = 64  \n1400 + 64  "}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 346", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 40 = 60\n5 + 6 = 11\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 665 + 405", "Answer": "A: 1070", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n5 + 5 = 10\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 162", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 7 = 27\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 27 = 887\n887 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 184", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n900 + 160 = 1060  \n1060 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n50 + 0 = 50  \n2 + 9 = 11  \n1400 + 50 = 1450  \n1450 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 334", "Answer": "A: 566", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n2 + 4 = 6\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n5 + 5 = 10\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1845", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n6 + 30 = 36\n1800 + 36 = 1836\n1836 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100  \n8 + 40 = 48  \n1100 + 48 = 1148  \n1148 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 511", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n24 + 1 = 25  \n1000 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 174", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 70 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 153", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3 = 1013\n1013 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n1500 + 13  "}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 221", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 332", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n2 + 30 = 32\n1100 + 32 = 1132\n1132 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 475", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 70 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n10 + 70 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 355", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 50 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 116", "Answer": "A: 638", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n22 + 16 = 38\n600 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1546", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 70 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n5 + 50 = 55\n1000 + 55 = 1055\n1055 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 288", "Answer": "A: 410", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n300 + 100 = 400  \n400 + 10 = 410  \n410 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 435", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 30 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 396", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 9\n829 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1498", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 10 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n2 + 50 = 52\n1100 + 52 = 1152\n1152 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n14 + 30 = 44\n1000 + 44 = 1044\n1044 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 363", "Answer": "A: 914", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 155", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 609", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n90 + 0 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 355", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 603", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 3 = 33\n1300 + 33 = 1333\n1333 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 281", "Answer": "A: 385", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n4 + 80 = 84\n300 + 84 = 384\n384 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 7 = 1397\n1397 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 700", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n15\n900 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 453", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 440", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n79 + 40 = 119   \n1000 + 119"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1840", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 90 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 743", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 20 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 471", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 70 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 641", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 8 + 1 = 1009"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 653", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 80 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n5 + 2 = 7\n1300 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1190", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 10 = 1190"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 529", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n700 + 40 = 740  \n740 + 9 = 749  \n749 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 262", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 60 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 148", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n99 + 48 = 147\n1000 + 147 = 1147"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 230", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 970", "Answer": "A: 1742", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n70 + 70 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 799 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1600", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n99 + 1 = 100\n1500 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 326", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n3 + 20 = 23  \n800 + 23 = 823  \n823 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 756", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n15 + 50 = 65\n900 + 65 = 965\n965 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 126", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000 \n70 + 20 = 90 \n9 + 6 = 15 \n1000 + 90 = 1090 \n1090 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 331", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 1 + 1 = 822"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 139", "Answer": "A: 441", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n2 + 30 = 32\n400 + 32 = 432\n432 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 641", "Answer": "A: 1489", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 497 + 405", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 0 = 90\n7 + 5 = 12\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 591", "Answer": "A: 800", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n9 + 90 = 99\n700 + 99 = 799\n799 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1419", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 9\n1030 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 327", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 20 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1857", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 70 = 150\n2 + 5 = 7\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n5 + 40 = 45\n1600 + 45 = 1645\n1645 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1677", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 90 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 4 \n1300 + 4 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 592", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n7 + 90 = 97\n900 + 97 = 997\n997 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 358", "Answer": "A: 669", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n11 + 50 = 61  \n600 + 61 = 661  \n661 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 124", "Answer": "A: 326", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n2 + 20 = 22\n300 + 22 = 322\n322 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 150", "Answer": "A: 477", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 941", "Answer": "A: 1699", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 40 = 90\n8 + 1 = 9\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 152", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 131", "Answer": "A: 438", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n7 + 30 = 37\n400 + 37 = 437\n437 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n80  \n1500 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 708", "Answer": "A: 1667", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 0 = 50\n9 + 8 = 17\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1883", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 20 = 80\n1800 + 80 = 1880\n1880 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 309", "Answer": "A: 629", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 9 = 29\n600 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 305", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n48 + 5 = 53\n1000 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 745", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n10 + 40 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 5 = 855\n855 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 590", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 90 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1720", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 30 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n1100 + 130 = 1230  \n1230 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1457", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n9 + 7 = 16\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 172", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 70 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n9 + 20 = 29\n1400 + 29 = 1429\n1429 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1757", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n9 + 8 = 17  \n1700 + 40 = 1740  \n1740 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 844", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 308", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n60 + 8 = 68  \n800 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n10 + 10 = 20\n1200 + 20 = 1220\n1220 + 4 \n1220 + 4 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 325", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n6 + 20 = 26\n1000 + 26 = 1026\n1026 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1629", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 90 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 9 = 1629"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 304", "Answer": "A: 455", "Explanation": "150 + 300 = 450\n1 + 4 = 5\n450 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n1500 + 90 = 1590  \n1590 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 304", "Answer": "A: 506", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n2 + 4 = 6\n500 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n7 + 9 = 16\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 198", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n700 + 150 = 850  \n850 + 10 = 860  \n860 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n2 + 5 = 7  \n1400 + 80 = 1480  \n1480 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 8 = 48\n1400 + 48 = 1448\n1448 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 376", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 490", "Answer": "A: 816", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 9 = 11\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 128", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n70 + 20 = 90\n8 + 8 = 16\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 517", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 10 = 20\n800 + 20 = 820\n820 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 138", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n6 + 8 = 14\n860 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 316", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 10 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 10 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 80 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1099", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n3 + 6 = 9\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 567", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 771", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n5 + 1 = 6\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 733 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1645", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n8 + 30 = 38\n1600 + 38 = 1638\n1638 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 354", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 304 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n4 + 80 = 84  \n1000 + 84 = 1084  \n1084 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n17 + 70 = 87\n1000 + 87 = 1087\n1087 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 60 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 1 = 10\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 10 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1484", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n17 + 60 = 77\n1400 + 77 = 1477\n1477 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 631", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 30 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 136", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 366", "Answer": "A: 631", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n5 + 6 = 11\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 30 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 30 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 8\n1308 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 390", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n78 + 90 = 168  \n700 + 168 = 868  "}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 463", "Answer": "A: 925", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n2 + 3 = 5\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n2 + 40 = 42\n1000 + 42 = 1042\n1042 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 164", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 7 = 917\n917 - 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1657", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 70 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1943", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 80 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 240", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "796 + 200 = 996\n996 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1344", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 60 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 219", "Answer": "A: 434", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n15 + 19 = 34\n400 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 423 + 437", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 477", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n3 + 70 = 73\n900 + 73 = 973\n973 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 267", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1773", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n10 + 50 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 750", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n28 + 50 = 78\n800 + 78"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 139", "Answer": "A: 499", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 30 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 421", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 20 = 40\n3 + 1 = 4\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1891", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 90 = 180\n1700 + 180 = 1880\n4 + 7 = 11\n1880 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 456", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 336", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1 + 6 = 7\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 781", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 4 \n920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 317", "Answer": "A: 821", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n4 + 10 = 14\n800 + 14 = 814\n814 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 301", "Answer": "A: 430", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 1 = 21\n400 + 21 = 421\n421 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1650", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n4 + 6 = 10\n40 + 10 = 50\n1600 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 553", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n5 + 20 = 25\n1000 + 25 = 1025\n1025 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 248", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 40 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 10 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 300", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n4 + 0 = 4\n800 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230  \n1230 + 6 = 1236"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1738", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 50 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 8 = 1738\n1738 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1358", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n1 + 7 = 8\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 235", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 5 = 35\n1000 + 35 = 1035\n1035 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 302", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 2 = 42\n700 + 42"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 454", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n50 + 7 = 57  \n1000 + 57 = 1057  \n1057 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 337", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 467 + 511", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n7 + 1 = 8\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 340", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 40 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 898", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n19 + 98 = 117  \n900 + 117 = 1017"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 164", "Answer": "A: 1030", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n8 + 6 = 14\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1665", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 70 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1610", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1522", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 595", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 90 = 120\n8 + 5 = 13\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1626", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n9 + 7 = 16  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 398", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n800 + 160 = 960  \n960 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 20 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 254", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 50 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1471", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n2 + 60 = 62\n1400 + 62 = 1462\n1462 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 556", "Answer": "A: 973", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 50 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 90 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 303", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n16 + 3 = 19\n700 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 636", "Answer": "A: 816", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 396", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 298", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n60 + 90 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 9 \n450 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 435", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 30 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 364", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 60 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 367", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1 + 7 = 8\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 580", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 80 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 10 = 50\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 324", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n5 + 4 = 9\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 610 + 274", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n10 + 70 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1633", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 2 = 32\n1600 + 32 = 1632\n1632 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n6 + 9 = 15\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 666", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 779", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 70 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 305", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 5 = 12\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 450", "Answer": "A: 555", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n5 + 50 = 55\n500 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 367", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 4 = 824\n824 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n1 + 6 = 7\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 639", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n4 + 30 = 34\n700 + 34 = 734\n734 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 162", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 60 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n7 + 9 = 16\n1000 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 140", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n54 + 40 = 94\n1000 + 94"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 493", "Answer": "A: 716", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 698", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 90 = 180\n5 + 8 = 13\n1100 + 180 = 1280\n1280 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1807", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 90 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 103", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 3 = 63\n300 + 63 = 363\n363 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1731", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n1600 + 120 = 1720  \n1720 + 9  \n1720 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 553", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 180", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n19 + 80 = 99\n900 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1422", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n15 + 7 = 22\n1400 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 70 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 251", "Answer": "A: 871", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1591", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 20 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 276", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 70 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 180", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n90 + 7 = 97\n800 + 97 = 897\n897 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 10 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 4\n1264 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 40 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1618", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 90 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 258", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 138", "Answer": "A: 349", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n10 + 30 = 40\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 1 + 8 = 340 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 699", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 90 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 3 \n950 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 389", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1872", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 90 = 160\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n6 + 6 = 12\n1860 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 280", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 208 + 274", "Answer": "A: 482", "Explanation": "200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 200 = 470\n470 + 8 = 478\n478 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n5 + 90 = 95\n1100 + 95 = 1195\n1195 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n28 + 90 = 118  \n1400 + 118 = 1518  \n1518 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 3 = 73\n1100 + 73 = 1173\n1173 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 291", "Answer": "A: 526", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n400 + 120 = 520  \n520 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 132", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n600 + 100 = 700  \n700 + 8  \n700 + 8 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n5 + 6 = 11\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 302", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 0 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 589", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n8 + 80 = 88\n800 + 88 = 888\n888 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 430", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 30 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 502", "Answer": "A: 1436", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 2 = 32\n1400 + 32 = 1432\n1432 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1703", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 60 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 326", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n2 + 20 = 22\n700 + 22 = 722\n722 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 615", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n15 + 15 = 30\n1100 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 525", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 5 = 705\n705 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 426", "Answer": "A: 590", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 20 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 10 = 590"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 296", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 90 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 15 = 975"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 262", "Answer": "A: 460", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n90 + 60 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 10 = 460\n460 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 251", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 898", "Answer": "A: 1807", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n9 + 90 = 99  \n1700 + 99 = 1799  \n1799 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 614", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 10 = 20\n7 + 4 = 11\n1100 + 20 = 1120\n1120 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 7 = 87\n1100 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n2 + 6 = 8\n1430 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 329", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 20 = 30\n5 + 9 = 14\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1608", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 70 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 195 + 426", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "195 + 426\n\n100 + 400 = 500\n\n90 + 20 = 110\n\n5 + 6 = 11\n\n500 + 110 = 610\n\n610 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 30 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 752", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 386", "Answer": "A: 549", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 80 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 3\n540 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1927", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 90 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 527", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n9 + 7 = 16\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 40 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 70 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 497", "Answer": "A: 1299", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n2 + 90 = 92  \n1200 + 92 = 1292  \n1292 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 9 = 49\n49 + 50 = 99\n1100 + 99 = 1199\n1199 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 203", "Answer": "A: 520", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n17 + 3 = 20\n500 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 396", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 185", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 80 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 409", "Answer": "A: 624", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600 \n15 + 9 = 24 \n600 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1583", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 90 = 180\n2 + 1 = 3\n1400 + 180 = 1580\n1580 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 141", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 40 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 212", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 570", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 366", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 490", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140"}
{"Question": "Q: 431 + 183", "Answer": "A: 614", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 80 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1755", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 60 = 140\n8 + 7 = 15\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 238", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 295", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n1100 + 160 = 1260  \n1260 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1626", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 70 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 252", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9 = 999"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 301", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 1 = 41\n500 + 41 = 541\n541 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 347", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 40 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n1 + 7 = 8\n650 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 781", "Answer": "A: 925", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 282", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n8 + 80 = 88\n1000 + 88 = 1088\n1088 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 416", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 10 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 30 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 673", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n4 + 70 = 74\n1400 + 74 = 1474\n1474 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1740", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 10 = 30\n1700 + 30 = 1730\n1730 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 402", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 0 = 90\n6 + 2 = 8\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n2 + 50 = 52\n1400 + 52 = 1452\n1452 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 159", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 30 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 238", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n5 + 30 = 35\n700 + 35 = 735\n735 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1460", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n1300 + 160"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 326", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 206", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 6 = 56\n800 + 56 = 856\n856 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 646", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 738", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n9 + 8 = 17\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 167", "Answer": "A: 366", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 60 = 150\n200 + 150 = 350\n9 + 7 = 16\n350 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 468", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n10 + 60 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n4 + 2 = 6\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 716", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 20 = 70\n8 + 4 = 12\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 105", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 5 = 45\n600 + 45 = 645\n645 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1460", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 10 = 1460"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 241", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n4 + 40 = 44\n700 + 44 = 744\n744 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 485", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 218", "Answer": "A: 891", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 334", "Answer": "A: 676", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 30 = 70\n2 + 4 = 6\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1518", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 503", "Answer": "A: 735", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 0 = 30\n2 + 3 = 5\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 249", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 197", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7 = 1127\n1127 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 80 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 294", "Answer": "A: 755", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 90 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 1 + 4 = 755"}
{"Question": "Q: 121 + 279", "Answer": "A: 400", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n300 + 90 = 390  \n390 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 305", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 5 = 45\n500 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1411", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n60 + 50 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 385", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1666", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 30 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 654 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n54 + 8 = 62\n1400 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1858", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 0 = 50\n1 + 7 = 8\n1800 + 50 = 1850\n1850 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 274", "Answer": "A: 503", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 70 = 90\n9 + 4 = 13\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 264", "Answer": "A: 816", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n4 + 8 = 12\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 267 + 395", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 90 = 150\n7 + 5 = 12\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 267", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 60 = 140\n9 + 7 = 16\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 270", "Answer": "A: 381", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n10 + 70 = 80\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 6 = 36\n1200 + 36 = 1236\n1236 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1584", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 544", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n2 + 4 = 6\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 311", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n98 + 11 = 109\n600 + 109 = 709"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 146", "Answer": "A: 663", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n17 + 40 = 57\n600 + 57 = 657\n657 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 553", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "190 + 550 = 740\n1 + 3 = 4\n740 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 566", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 102", "Answer": "A: 272", "Explanation": "100 + 70 = 170\n100 + 2 = 102\n170 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 715", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 5 = 7\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 230", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n19 + 30 = 49\n1100 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1695", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 60 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 379", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 7 = 77\n70 + 9 = 79\n77 + 79 = 156\n800 + 156 = 956"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 694", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900  \n5 + 90 = 95  \n900 + 95 = 995  \n995 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 317", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 10 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 583", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n10 + 80 = 90  \n600 + 90 = 690  \n690 + 7  \n690 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 245", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 40 = 120\n4 + 5 = 9\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n7 + 50 = 57\n1300 + 57 = 1357\n1357 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 232", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n800 + 120 = 920  \n920 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 10 = 30\n1100 + 30 = 1130\n1130 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 611", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 3  \n800 + 1  \n800 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1432", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 454 + 267", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 60 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 4 + 3 = 717\n717 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 525", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 5 = 805\n805 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 513", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 110", "Answer": "A: 249", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 10 = 40\n200 + 40 = 240\n240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n50 + 80 = 130  \n900 + 130 = 1030  \n1030 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n3 + 7 = 10\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 374", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 70 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 9\n850 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 541", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 8 = 38\n1300 + 38 = 1338\n1338 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 40 = 70\n1 + 5 = 6\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 416", "Answer": "A: 1247", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1646", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 2 = 42\n1600 + 42 = 1642\n1642 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1638", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 80 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 294", "Answer": "A: 448", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n50 + 90 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1741", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n9 + 30 = 39\n1700 + 39 = 1739\n1739 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 265", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 50 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 205", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n90 + 0 = 90\n6 + 5 = 11\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 397", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1391", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n2 + 9 = 11\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 672", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 70 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5 + 2 = 917"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1 + 2 = 3\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 158", "Answer": "A: 665", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n7 + 50 = 57  \n600 + 57 = 657  \n657 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 415", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6 = 906\n906 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 527", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n4 + 7 = 11\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 224", "Answer": "A: 342", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n18 + 20 = 38\n300 + 38 = 338\n338 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 119", "Answer": "A: 661", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n40 + 10 = 50  \n2 + 9 = 11  \n600 + 50 = 650  \n650 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n4 + 70 = 74\n1600 + 74 = 1674\n1674 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 219", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 20 = 70\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 200", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n25 + 0 = 25\n700 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 117", "Answer": "A: 302", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 7 = 12\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1061", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n7 + 2 = 9\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 460", "Answer": "A: 566", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n6 + 60 = 66\n500 + 66"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 135", "Answer": "A: 443", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n\n8 + 30 = 38\n\n400 + 38 = 438\n\n438 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 295", "Answer": "A: 521", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n20 + 90 = 110  \n400 + 110 = 510  \n510 + 6 = 516  \n516 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 608", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 8 = 48\n900 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 582", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 80 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 230", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1861", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 80 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 3\n1850 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1767", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n7 + 60 = 67\n1700 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1148", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 5 = 8\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9\n1230 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 404", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 4 = 44\n800 + 44 = 844\n844 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 584", "Answer": "A: 757", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n5 + 30 = 35\n1400 + 35 = 1435\n1435 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 484", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 80 = 100\n5 + 4 = 9\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1522", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n19 + 10 = 29\n1400 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n5 + 6 = 11  \n1100 + 50 = 1150  \n1150 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 552", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n4 + 50 = 54\n700 + 54 = 754\n754 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 218", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n15 + 18 = 33\n800 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 262", "Answer": "A: 640", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n70 + 60 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 10 = 640"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 517", "Answer": "A: 648", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 7 = 647\n647 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 443", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1747", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n1600 + 130 = 1730  \n1730 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 181", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 8 = 1048"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n2 + 70 = 72\n1200 + 72 = 1272\n1272 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 337", "Answer": "A: 772", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 7 = 12\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 306", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 6 = 36\n900 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 229", "Answer": "A: 433", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n4 + 20 = 24  \n400 + 24 = 424  \n424 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n4 + 5 = 9  \n1100 + 130 = 1230  \n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 228", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 511 + 237", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n10 + 30 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 50 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 418", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 10 = 70\n70 + 6 + 8 = 84\n800 + 84"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1661", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 10 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n19 + 30 = 49\n1100 + 49 = 1149\n1149 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 550", "Answer": "A: 821", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 50 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 449", "Answer": "A: 686", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 9 = 16\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 101", "Answer": "A: 295", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n94 + 1 = 95\n200 + 95"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 5 + 1 = 1456"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1551", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 10 = 40\n4 + 7 = 11\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 705", "Answer": "A: 888", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 5 = 85\n800 + 85 = 885\n885 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 177", "Answer": "A: 574", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 70 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 327", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n9 + 7 = 16\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 273", "Answer": "A: 421", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 70 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 8 \n410 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 431 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 1 = 31\n1300 + 31 = 1331\n1331 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n4 + 90 = 94\n1100 + 94 = 1194\n1194 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 658", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1566", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n9 + 50 = 59\n1500 + 59 = 1559\n1559 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 362", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9\n999 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 138", "Answer": "A: 257", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 30 = 40\n9 + 8 = 17\n200 + 40 = 240\n240 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 196", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 90 = 180\n4 + 6 = 10\n500 + 180 = 680\n680 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 446", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 6 = 866\n866 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 161", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n16 + 60 = 76\n600 + 76 = 676\n676 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 70 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 425", "Answer": "A: 800", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n75 + 25 = 100\n700 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 293", "Answer": "A: 531", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 8\n520 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 371", "Answer": "A: 681", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1302", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 70 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n24 + 80 = 104  \n1000 + 104 = 1104  \n1104 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1302", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1869", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 40 = 60\n1800 + 60 = 1860\n1860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 395", "Answer": "A: 890", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 363", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 = 921\n921 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 217", "Answer": "A: 604", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 10 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 7 \n7 + 7 = 14\n590 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1642", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n41 + 1 = 42  \n1600 + 42"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n1200 + 50 = 1250  \n1250 + 6 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 427", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n10 + 20 = 30  \n700 + 30 = 730  \n730 + 10  "}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 30 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n2 + 6 = 8\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1500", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 60 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1467", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n3 + 60 = 63\n1400 + 63 = 1463\n1463 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1319", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 9 = 19\n1300 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 638", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n18 + 30 = 48\n800 + 48 = 848\n848 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 271", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 420", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n4 + 20 = 24\n500 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 124", "Answer": "A: 520", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n96 + 20 = 116\n400 + 116 = 516\n516 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 293", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n6 + 90 = 96\n1100 + 96 = 1196\n1196 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 277", "Answer": "A: 391", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n10 + 70 = 80\n4 + 7 = 11\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 432", "Answer": "A: 716", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n5 + 6 = 11  \n1600 + 100 = 1700  \n1700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1934", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 60 = 130\n3 + 1 = 4\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n19 + 7 = 26\n1500 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 113", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1508", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 30 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 7 + 1 = 1508"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n7 + 40 = 47\n1200 + 47 = 1247\n1247 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 505", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n1 + 5 = 6\n800 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 375", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n9 + 5 = 14\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 121", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 652", "Answer": "A: 774", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 50 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 629", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 3 + 9 = 962"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1875", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 90 = 160\n9 + 6 = 15\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1649", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n4 + 5 = 9  \n1500 + 140 = 1640  \n1640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1783", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700 \n50 + 20 = 70 \n6 + 7 = 13 \n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 80 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6\n1316 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 300", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n74\n1000 + 74"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 392", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 2 = 7\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 230", "Answer": "A: 734", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n4 + 30 = 34\n700 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n25 + 50 = 75\n1100 + 75 = 1175\n1175 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 306", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 7 = 67\n600 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 367", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 517", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 0 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 353", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n1300 + 80 = 1380  \n1380 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 5\n1235 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n4 + 60 = 64\n1200 + 64 = 1264\n1264 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 314", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 533", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 205", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 0 = 90\n6 + 5 = 11\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 492", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 298", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n9 + 90 = 99\n500 + 99 = 599\n599 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 666", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 553", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n7 + 50 = 57\n800 + 57 = 857\n857 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 678 + 170", "Answer": "A: 848", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 70 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 110", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n83 + 70 = 153  \n1000 + 153"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 361", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 138", "Answer": "A: 429", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 30 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 673", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1836", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 60 = 120\n9 + 7 = 16\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 449", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n4 + 9 = 13\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 478", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 613", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 289", "Answer": "A: 582", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n90 + 80 = 170\n3 + 9 = 12\n400 + 170 = 570\n570 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 906", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n2 + 6 = 8\n1800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 687", "Answer": "A: 1541", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n40 + 60 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n2 + 5 = 7\n1300 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n17 + 0 = 17\n1500 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 326", "Answer": "A: 627", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n1 + 20 = 21\n600 + 21 = 621\n621 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 238", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 30 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1629", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 40 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 326", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 20 = 70\n9 + 6 = 15\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1880", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n15 + 60 = 75\n1800 + 75 = 1875\n1875 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 185", "Answer": "A: 469", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 80 = 160\n4 + 5 = 9\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 373", "Answer": "A: 572", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n400 + 160 = 560  \n560 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 147", "Answer": "A: 392", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n300 + 80 = 380  \n380 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 399", "Answer": "A: 670", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 90 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 10 = 670"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 549", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n80 + 3 = 83\n600 + 83 = 683\n683 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 554", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5 + 4 = 1029"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 153", "Answer": "A: 350", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 50 = 140\n7 + 3 = 10\n200 + 140 = 340\n340 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 290", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 90 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 12 = 92\n1400 + 92"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 382", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 289", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "450 + 200 = 650\n50 + 80 = 130\n650 + 130 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 273", "Answer": "A: 664", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 639", "Answer": "A: 752", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 30 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 310", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 150", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1612", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n12 + 0 = 12\n1600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1753", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n13 + 40 = 53\n1700 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 385", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n5 + 5 = 10\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 80 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 306", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n12 + 6 = 18\n1000 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 2 = 4\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 247", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n1000 + 120 = 1120  \n1120 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1654", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 20 = 50\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 350", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 0 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1662", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 362", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n6 + 60 = 66  \n1000 + 66 = 1066  \n1066 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 843", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 491", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 9 = 869\n869 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 372", "Answer": "A: 572", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n72 \n500 + 72"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 291", "Answer": "A: 612", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 90 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 173", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 70 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 8 = 498\n498 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1628", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 7 + 1 = 1628"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1691", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 10 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1892", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 90 = 180\n1700 + 180 = 1880\n1880 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 418 + 146", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n\n18 + 40 = 58\n\n500 + 58 = 558\n\n558 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1594", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 360", "Answer": "A: 477", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n17 + 60 = 77  \n400 + 77"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 285", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n99 + 80 = 179\n500 + 179 = 679\n679 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 400", "Answer": "A: 881", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 766", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 366", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 60 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n8 + 4 = 12\n1300 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 433", "Answer": "A: 574", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 30 = 70\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 137", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 506", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 6 = 26\n900 + 26 = 926\n926 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 269", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1196", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n45 + 50 = 95\n1100 + 95 = 1195\n1195 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 949 + 294", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1729", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 90 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 70 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n6 + 5 = 11\n1200 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 507", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 7 = 37\n700 + 37 = 737\n737 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 267", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 127", "Answer": "A: 630", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n3 + 20 = 23\n600 + 23 = 623\n623 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 573", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n7 + 70 = 77  \n700 + 77 = 777  \n777 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 477", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 219", "Answer": "A: 362", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 10 = 50\n50 + 9 = 59\n300 + 59 = 359\n359 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 800 + 414", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n14 + 0 = 14\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1595", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 10 = 90\n2 + 3 = 5\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 337", "Answer": "A: 810", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1766", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n50 + 9 = 59  \n1700 + 50 + 9 = 1759  \n1759 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 438", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 9 = 99\n800 + 99 = 899\n899 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 8 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1778", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n1700 + 70 = 1770  \n1770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 416", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n40 + 10 = 50  \n900 + 50 = 950  \n950 + 6  \n950 + 6 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 0 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 70 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 9\n1460 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n1 + 25 = 26\n1000 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 341", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n6 + 1 = 7\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 450", "Answer": "A: 665", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n15 + 50 = 65\n600 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1254", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n6 + 40 = 46\n1200 + 46 = 1246\n1246 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1767", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n50 + 10 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 371", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 70 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 679", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 70 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 5\n890 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 318 + 131", "Answer": "A: 449", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n18 + 30 = 48  \n400 + 48 = 448  \n448 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n94 + 11 = 105\n1200 + 105"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 274", "Answer": "A: 606", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 4 = 6\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 181", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 186", "Answer": "A: 593", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n7 + 80 = 87\n500 + 87 = 587\n587 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 271", "Answer": "A: 417", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 70 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 6 + 1 = 417"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1722", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 90 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 371", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1082", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 357", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n2 + 50 = 52\n800 + 52 = 852\n852 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 498", "Answer": "A: 667", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500   \n60 + 90 = 150   \n500 + 150 = 650   \n650 + 8 + 9 = 667   "}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 446", "Answer": "A: 701", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n9 + 10 = 19\n1000 + 19 = 1019  \n1019 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 7 = 87\n1100 + 87 = 1187\n1187 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 636", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n7 + 6 = 13\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 583", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1783", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n1700 + 80 = 1780  \n1780 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 193", "Answer": "A: 384", "Explanation": "190 + 190 = 380\n1 + 3 = 4\n380 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 523", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "320 + 500 = 820\n20 + 20 = 40\n820 + 40 = 860\n860 - 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 392", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 525", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1660", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 60 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 839", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 537", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n\n70 + 30 = 100\n\n800 + 100 = 900\n\n5 + 7 = 12\n\n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 670", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1704", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n90 + 9 = 99  \n1600 + 99 = 1699  \n1699 + 5 "}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 550", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n6 + 30 = 36\n1100 + 36 = 1136\n1136 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 348", "Answer": "A: 579", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 40 = 70\n1 + 8 = 9\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 321", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 1 = 10\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 187", "Answer": "A: 327", "Explanation": "100 + 80 = 180  \n40 + 7 = 47  \n180 + 47 = 227  \n227 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 640", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 662", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 4 = 1404"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 4 = 54\n1300 + 54 = 1354\n1354 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 616", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 10 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 832", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 478", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n7 + 8 = 15  \n1300 + 160 = 1460  \n1460 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1577", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n7 + 70 = 77  \n1500 + 77  "}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 10 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 2 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 843", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 3 = 10\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 614", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 10 = 20\n700 + 20 = 720\n720 + 4\n720 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 649 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n9 + 2 = 11\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 318 + 317", "Answer": "A: 635", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 10 = 20\n8 + 7 = 15\n600 + 20 = 620\n620 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 7 = 67\n1200 + 67 = 1267\n1267 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1671", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n6 + 5 = 11\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 570", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n6 + 70 = 76  \n700 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 141", "Answer": "A: 448", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n7 + 40 = 47\n400 + 47 = 447\n447 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n9 + 6 = 15\n1330 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 7 = 67\n1100 + 67 = 1167\n1167 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 100", "Answer": "A: 803", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n38 + 20 = 58\n1200 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 408", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 5 = 45\n800 + 45 = 845\n845 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n1 + 67 = 68\n1000 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1699", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 30 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 656", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 50 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1800", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 30 = 90\n5 + 5 = 10\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1696", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n9 + 80 = 89\n1600 + 89 = 1689\n1689 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n3 + 2 = 5\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n4 + 4 = 8\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 363", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n400 + 80 = 480  \n480 + 5 + 3   "}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7\n1310 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 478", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 70 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3\n1200 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n4 + 50 = 54\n1300 + 54 = 1354\n1354 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 9 = 29\n1100 + 29 = 1129\n1129 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 101", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n71 + 1 = 72\n600 + 72"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 337", "Answer": "A: 507", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n400 + 100 = 500  \n500 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 786", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n8 + 80 = 88\n1300 + 88 = 1388\n1388 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 205", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 5 = 45\n900 + 45 = 945\n945 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 865", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n65 \n900 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 445", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 40 = 50\n9 + 5 = 14\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 145", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7\n867 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 499", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1548", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 412", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 776", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "180 + 770 = 950\n1 + 6 = 7\n950 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 142", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n3 + 40 = 43\n1000 + 43 = 1043\n1043 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1670", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n45 + 20 = 65  \n1600 + 65  "}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 706", "Answer": "A: 1702", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n96 + 6 = 102  \n1600 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 384", "Answer": "A: 627", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 80 = 120\n3 + 4 = 7\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1705", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 563", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 60 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 835", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1365", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n3 + 60 = 63\n1300 + 63 = 1363\n1363 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 118", "Answer": "A: 630", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n12 + 18 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 70 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 158", "Answer": "A: 282", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 50 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 356", "Answer": "A: 538", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 50 = 130\n2 + 6 = 8\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1466", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n9 + 7 = 16\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 617", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 2 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 2 = 32\n1000 + 32 = 1032\n1032 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n5 + 40 = 45\n1400 + 45 = 1445\n1445 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1830", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 60 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n5 + 9 = 14\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 484", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 80 = 100\n9 + 4 = 13\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 220", "Answer": "A: 457", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 20 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 16 = 56\n1000 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 654 + 154", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 50 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 4 = 804\n804 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 345", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n4 + 5 = 9\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 342", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 30 = 70\n1 + 2 = 3\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 309", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 0 = 10\n4 + 9 = 13\n900 + 10 = 910\n910 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 482", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1542", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 50 = 130\n3 + 9 = 12\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1371", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 40 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 406", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 6 = 36\n1300 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 20 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 3 \n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 208", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 0 = 10\n900 + 10 = 910\n910 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 213", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 368", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 6 = 46\n1100 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 680", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 476", "Answer": "A: 791", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n5 + 6 = 11\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1905", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 40 = 100\n1800 + 100 = 1900\n1900 + 2\n1900 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 340", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 40 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 40 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 697", "Answer": "A: 944", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 90 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 206", "Answer": "A: 503", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n90 + 6 = 96\n400 + 96 = 496\n496 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 298", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 90 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 277", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 70 = 90\n7 + 7 = 14\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 388", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 520", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 527", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 20 = 50\n7 + 7 = 14\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 495", "Answer": "A: 729", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n600 + 120 = 720  \n720 + 9  \n720 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 691", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 90 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9\n9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n2 + 1 = 3  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 331", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 163", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1819", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 80 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1927", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n1800 + 120 = 1920  \n1920 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n9 + 6 = 15\n1100 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 346", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n2 + 6 = 8\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1774", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 40 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 400", "Answer": "A: 554", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n54 + 0 = 54\n500 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n9 + 7 = 16  \n1400 + 40 = 1440  \n1440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1776", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n50 + 20 = 70  \n1700 + 70 = 1770  \n1770 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 462", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n7 + 2 = 9\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 740", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 229", "Answer": "A: 518", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 384", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 80 = 160\n3 + 4 = 7\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 151", "Answer": "A: 443", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 50 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 224", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n17 + 20 = 37\n800 + 37 = 837\n837 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 341", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n4 + 50 = 54\n1300 + 54 = 1354\n1354 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 749", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 40 = 130\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 239", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n400 + 90 = 490  \n490 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 826", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 6 = 13\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 234", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 474", "Answer": "A: 640", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 70 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 6 = 636\n636 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 431 + 346", "Answer": "A: 777", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 40 = 70\n1 + 6 = 7\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 0 = 80\n9 + 5 = 14\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 285", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n2 + 5 = 7\n1000 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n1100 + 140 = 1240  \n1240 + 4 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 160", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n76 + 60 = 136\n800 + 136"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 487", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 80 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930 \n930 + 8 = 938"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1436", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n26 + 10 = 36\n1400 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 144", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 733 + 332", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n3 + 2 = 5\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 239", "Answer": "A: 386", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 30 = 70\n7 + 9 = 16\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 119", "Answer": "A: 862", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 444", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 40 = 130\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1112", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 499", "Answer": "A: 685", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 90 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 535", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n3 + 30 = 33\n1300 + 33 = 1333\n1333 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 121", "Answer": "A: 424", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n3 + 20 = 23\n400 + 23 = 423\n423 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 595", "Answer": "A: 903", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n8 + 90 = 98\n800 + 98 = 898\n898 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 476", "Answer": "A: 610", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 70 = 100\n4 + 6 = 10\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 10 = 610"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 326", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 1 = 71\n1200 + 71 = 1271\n1271 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1566", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 80 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 568", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1566", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 5 + 1 = 1566"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n10 + 20 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n4 + 5 = 9\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 291", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 155", "Answer": "A: 354", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 50 = 140\n9 + 5 = 14\n200 + 140 = 340\n340 + 14 = 354"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 435", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 603", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 3 = 63\n900 + 63 = 963\n963 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 338", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 30 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 1 + 8 = 879"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1749", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 90 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 9 = 1749"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n3 + 30 = 33\n1200 + 33 = 1233\n1233 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 215", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n7 + 15 = 22\n900 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 234", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n1 + 30 = 31\n1000 + 31 = 1031\n1031 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 10 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 733", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 113", "Answer": "A: 848", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 149", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n2 + 9 = 11\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 488", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 80 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 10 = 780"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 601", "Answer": "A: 1519", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n18 + 1 = 19\n1500 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1344", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 4 = 1344"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 473", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 9 + 3 = 1412"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1061", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 20 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1486", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 2 = 82\n1400 + 82 = 1482\n1482 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 197", "Answer": "A: 397", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n100 + 90 = 190  \n190 + 7 = 197  \n200 + 197"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 316", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n7 + 6 = 13\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n10 + 90 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1608", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 270", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n17 + 70 = 87\n900 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n2 + 8 = 10\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1558", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 80 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 122", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 432", "Answer": "A: 797", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 294 + 422", "Answer": "A: 716", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 322", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 413", "Answer": "A: 609", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 10 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n6 + 3 = 9\n600 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 194", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n11 + 90 = 101\n900 + 101 = 1001\n1001 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1401", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n9 + 90 = 99\n1300 + 99 = 1399\n1399 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 197", "Answer": "A: 439", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 90 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 9 = 439"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1070", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 80 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 10 = 1070"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1730", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 90 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1366", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n75 + 90 = 165\n1200 + 165 = 1365\n1365 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 80 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 541", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 30 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n3 + 90 = 93\n1400 + 93 = 1493\n1493 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 462", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 318", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 10 = 60 \n8 + 8 = 16\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n80 + 30 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 9\n1510 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 378", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 70 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1677", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n1500 + 170 = 1670  \n1670 + 3 + 4  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 713", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 422", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n5 + 2 = 7\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 652", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 390", "Answer": "A: 797", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n7 + 90 = 97\n700 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 394", "Answer": "A: 736", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n1300 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 200", "Answer": "A: 405", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n400 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n3 + 8 = 11\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 293", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 10 = 830\n830 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 332", "Answer": "A: 788", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 198", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 90 = 180\n500 + 180 = 680\n680 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 103", "Answer": "A: 509", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n6 + 3 = 9\n500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 252", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n9 + 70 = 79\n1300 + 79 = 1379\n1379 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 786", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 10 = 20\n4 + 5 = 9\n1500 + 20 = 1520\n1520 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 581", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n7 + 1 = 8  \n1000 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 0 = 10\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 10 = 1210\n1210 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 381", "Answer": "A: 561", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 80 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 147", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n\n40 + 40 = 80\n\n5 + 7 = 12\n\n600 + 80 = 680\n\n680 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 300", "Answer": "A: 666", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n600 + 66"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1190", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 10 = 1190"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 153", "Answer": "A: 511", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 50 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n8 + 3 = 11\n500 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 244", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n12 + 40 = 52\n1100 + 52 = 1152\n1152 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 214", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 10 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 677", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n6 + 70 = 76\n900 + 76 = 976\n976 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1814", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 30 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n9 + 5 = 14\n1800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 336", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n8 + 6 = 14\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 328", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1840", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 80 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 10 = 1840"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 357", "Answer": "A: 628", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 50 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 1 + 7 = 628"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 116", "Answer": "A: 562", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n46 + 16 = 62\n500 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1552", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 20 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 120", "Answer": "A: 450", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n30 + 20 = 50\n400 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 677", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1371", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1771", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 9 = 11\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n1700 + 100 = 1800  \n1800 + 1 + 7 = 1808  "}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 422", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 8 = 808"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 257", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n6 + 50 = 56\n1100 + 56 = 1156\n1156 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1520", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n8 + 40 = 48\n1000 + 48 = 1048\n1048 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n17 + 20 = 37\n1400 + 37 = 1437\n1437 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 20 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1563", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n1 + 60 = 61\n1500 + 61 = 1561\n1561 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 371", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5 = 1225"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 193", "Answer": "A: 496", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n3 + 90 = 93\n400 + 93 = 493\n493 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 300", "Answer": "A: 817", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n17\n800 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1544", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 30 = 40\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 601", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 1 = 21\n1400 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 144", "Answer": "A: 787", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 4 = 7\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 354", "Answer": "A: 566", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 50 = 60\n2 + 4 = 6\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n48 + 1 = 49\n1000 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1821", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 20 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 9 \n9 + 2 = 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6 = 1146\n1146 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 541", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9 + 1 = 910"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 0 = 90\n3 + 3 = 6\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 10 = 60\n4 + 7 = 11\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 517", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 658", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 259", "Answer": "A: 786", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 9 = 16\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 763", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 338", "Answer": "A: 439", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n1 + 38 = 39\n400 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 304 + 523", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n4 + 20 = 24\n800 + 24 = 824\n824 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 252", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n600 + 80 = 680  \n680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 114", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 438", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 10 = 820"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 523", "Answer": "A: 1458", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 20 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 765", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 160", "Answer": "A: 510", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 60 = 110\n400 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 174", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n400 + 80 = 480  \n480 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 475", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 70 = 110\n9 + 5 = 14\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 160", "Answer": "A: 574", "Explanation": "400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 433", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 10 = 820"}
{"Question": "Q: 430 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1581", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 183", "Answer": "A: 623", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n500 + 120 = 620  \n620 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 542", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n2 + 40 = 42  \n800 + 42 = 842  \n842 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 360", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n5 + 60 = 65\n500 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 127", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n19 + 20 = 39\n900 + 39 = 939\n939 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 190 + 273", "Answer": "A: 463", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n90 + 70 = 160\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1801", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n1700 + 90 = 1790  \n1790 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 570", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 \n800 + 70"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1557", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n8 + 40 = 48\n1500 + 48 = 1548\n1548 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 9 + 4 = 1433"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 662", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 720", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 20 = 30\n900 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 687", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 7  \n840 + 4 = 844  \n844 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1920", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 70 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 165", "Answer": "A: 352", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 60 = 140\n7 + 5 = 12\n200 + 140 = 340\n340 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 125", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8 \n1078 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 526", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n6 + 20 = 26\n700 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 433", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 30 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 102", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n10 + 3 = 13\n800 + 13 = 813\n813 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1559", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 70 = 150\n3 + 6 = 9\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 596", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 90 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1672", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 20 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 169", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n8 + 3 = 11\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1528", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n3 + 5 = 8\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 290", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n1 + 90 = 91\n1000 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 953 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1947", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 90 = 140\n3 + 4 = 7\n1800 + 140 = 1940\n1940 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 182", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 80 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 349", "Answer": "A: 875", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 254 + 470", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "250 + 470 = 720  \n4 + 720"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 50 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 218", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n2 + 2 = 4\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 8 = 78\n1100 + 78 = 1178\n1178 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 306", "Answer": "A: 452", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 6 = 46\n400 + 46 = 446\n446 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 40 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 276", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 8 = 38\n1000 + 38 = 1038\n1038 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1579", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 0 = 70\n4 + 5 = 9\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 493", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 10 = 740\n740"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 652", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n50 + 20 = 70  \n7 + 7 = 14  \n1000 + 70 = 1070  \n1070 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1745", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 20 = 30\n1700 + 30 = 1730\n1730 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 257", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 4 = 684\n684 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1579", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 20 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 898", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n16 + 98 = 114\n1000 + 114"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 10 = 70\n3 + 2 = 5\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1590", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 8 = 88\n1500 + 88 = 1588\n1588 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 411", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 454", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 838", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 499", "Answer": "A: 1030", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 407", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 0 = 90\n8 + 7 = 15\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1479", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n1300 + 170 = 1470  \n1470 + 9 = 1479  "}
{"Question": "Q: 586 + 243", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 184", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n700 + 160 = 860  \n860 + 6 = 866"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 5 = 7\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 720", "Answer": "A: 950", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n900 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 282", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 80 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 502", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 2 = 22\n700 + 22 = 722\n722 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1578", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 10 = 70\n1 + 7 = 8\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 10 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 613", "Answer": "A: 716", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n3 + 10 = 13\n700 + 13 = 713\n713 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 153", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 6 = 1026\n1026 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 5 = 1095\n1095 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 171", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 70 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n1 + 70 = 71\n1100 + 71 = 1171\n1171 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 621", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 217", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 3 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 575", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n9 + 70 = 79\n600 + 79 = 679\n679 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 610", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n800 + 40 = 840  \n840 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 30 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 335", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 411", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 595", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 90 = 120\n4 + 5 = 9\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1519", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n17 + 2 = 19\n1500 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 456", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n10 + 50 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1455", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n6 + 9 = 15\n1400 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1842", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 40 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1302", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1401", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 941", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7 + 1 = 1278"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 344", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n1 + 44 = 45\n600 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 826", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 20 = 90\n1 + 6 = 7\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 233", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 30 = 70\n3 + 3 = 6\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 236", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1501", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 60 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 676", "Answer": "A: 1414", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 283", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 80 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 7 \n760 + 10 = 770"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 30 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 40 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 843 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1665", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 2 = 5\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 387", "Answer": "A: 1154", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n7 + 7 = 14\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 774", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n5 + 4 = 9\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1632", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 20 = 30\n1600 + 30 = 1630\n1630 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 362", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 354", "Answer": "A: 518", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 50 = 110\n4 + 4 = 8\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 843 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1550", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 7 = 47\n1500 + 47 = 1547\n1547 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1499", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n2 + 7 = 9  \n1400 + 90 = 1490  \n1490 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 193", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 2\n832 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 615", "Answer": "A: 797", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n700 + 90 = 790  \n790 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 269", "Answer": "A: 559", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n90 + 60 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1610", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 70 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 158", "Answer": "A: 505", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 50 = 90\n7 + 8 = 15\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n9 + 6 = 15\n1100 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 705", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 0 = 80\n9 + 5 = 14\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 50 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1606", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n6 + 0 = 6\n1600 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 602", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n16 + 2 = 18\n800 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1200", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 365", "Answer": "A: 569", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n4 + 60 = 64\n500 + 64 = 564\n564 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 488", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1672", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 5 = 65\n1600 + 65 = 1665\n1665 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 162", "Answer": "A: 615", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 60 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 5 = 615\n615 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 357", "Answer": "A: 538", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 50 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 641", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5 = 795"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 628", "Answer": "A: 1099", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 20 = 90\n1 + 8 = 9\n1000 + 90 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 1 = 1001  \n1001 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n9 + 5 = 14\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1772", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 5 = 12\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 257", "Answer": "A: 416", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 7 = 16\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 800 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1738", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n30 + 8 = 38  \n1700 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 451", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 970", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 422", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 348", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n4 + 8 = 12\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 487", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n44 + 80 = 124\n800 + 124 = 924\n924 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 298", "Answer": "A: 648", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 90 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n6 + 5 = 11\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n17 + 20 = 37\n1000 + 37 = 1037\n1037 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 294", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 90 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 600", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n27 + 0 = 27\n800 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1079", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 369", "Answer": "A: 777", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n8 + 60 = 68\n700 + 68 = 768\n768 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 450", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 112", "Answer": "A: 391", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 10 = 80\n9 + 2 = 11\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 11 "}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 191", "Answer": "A: 513", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 90 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 3 = 513"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 502", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n1 + 2 = 3\n1400 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 255", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 7 + 5 = 982"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1750", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 70 = 140\n8 + 2 = 10\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 814", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 565", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 600", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n9 + 0 = 9\n700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 348", "Answer": "A: 477", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 40 = 60\n9 + 8 = 17\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1494", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 30 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1391", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1354", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4 = 1354"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 544", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 5 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 147", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 40 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 423 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n18 + 700 = 718  \n1300 + 18 = 1318  \n1318 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 50 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 325", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n9 + 20 = 29\n1100 + 29 = 1129\n1129 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n10 + 30 = 40\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 207", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 7 = 47\n1000 + 47 = 1047\n1047 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1365", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n1200 + 150 = 1350  \n1350 + 6 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 571", "Answer": "A: 737", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 70 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 20 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 686", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 199", "Answer": "A: 509", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 90 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 405", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 5 = 25\n1100 + 25 = 1125\n1125 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 154", "Answer": "A: 276", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 50 = 70\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 786", "Answer": "A: 1726", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 80 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1779", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 7 = 9\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 123", "Answer": "A: 1012", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 3 = 12\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n46 + 10 = 56\n1200 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1604", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 50 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 746", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 7\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 366", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 0 = 60\n5 + 3 = 8\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1626", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 20 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 183", "Answer": "A: 468", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 80 = 160\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 5 \n460 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 294", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 90 = 180\n3 + 4 = 7\n800 + 180 = 980\n980 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 184", "Answer": "A: 657", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 80 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 7 = 657\n657 - 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 123", "Answer": "A: 288", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 20 = 80\n5 + 3 = 8\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 528", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 3 + 8 = 981"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 359", "Answer": "A: 601", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 50 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 2\n590 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 182", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n3 + 80 = 83\n800 + 83 = 883\n883 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 688", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 395", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n7 + 2 = 9\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n5 + 9 = 14\n1300 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 1 = 1051\n1051 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 445", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 578", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 8 = 15\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 678 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n8 + 5 = 13\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 246", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 40 = 130\n9 + 6 = 15\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 450", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n48 + 50 = 98\n700 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n7 + 13 = 20\n1200 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 334", "Answer": "A: 447", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 30 = 40\n3 + 4 = 7\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 165", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6 = 996\n996 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 658", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1 + 8 = 9\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 294", "Answer": "A: 420", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 90 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 177", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n12 + 70 = 82  \n700 + 82 = 782  \n782 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 20 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 365", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n55 + 9 = 64\n1300 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n2 + 20 = 22\n1300 + 22 = 1322\n1322 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 \n1003 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 649 + 108", "Answer": "A: 757", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 8 = 48\n700 + 48 = 748\n748 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 276", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n6 + 6 = 12\n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 354", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 4 = 13\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 343", "Answer": "A: 669", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 40 = 60\n6 + 3 = 9\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 212", "Answer": "A: 427", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n15 + 10 = 25\n400 + 25 = 425\n425 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 800 + 573", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 3 = 73\n1300 + 73"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1431", "Explanation": "650 + 700 = 1350\n50 + 30 = 80\n1350 + 80 = 1430\n1430 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 289", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 80 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 9 \n720 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1397", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 10 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 162 + 224", "Answer": "A: 386", "Explanation": "160 + 220 = 380\n2 + 4 = 6\n380 + 6 = 386"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 100", "Answer": "A: 264", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 64\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 639", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 9 = 16\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n4 + 9 = 13\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1577", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1609", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n4 + 5 = 9\n1600 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 257", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n5 + 7 = 12\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1758", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 80 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 4 = 74\n1300 + 74 = 1374\n1374 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 141", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1\n700 + 1 = 702"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 654", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 50 = 70\n4 + 4 = 8\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 425", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1200 + 110 = 1310  \n1310 + 9  \n1310 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n99 + 70 = 169\n1500 + 169 = 1669\n1669 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 104", "Answer": "A: 256", "Explanation": "150 + 100 = 250\n2 + 4 = 6\n250 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 434", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n18 + 17 = 35\n1100 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 176", "Answer": "A: 373", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 70 = 160\n7 + 6 = 13\n200 + 160 = 360\n360 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1724", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 90 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 3\n1720 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 594", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 226", "Answer": "A: 579", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 20 = 70\n3 + 6 = 9\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1793", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 3 = 83\n1700 + 83"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1838", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 90 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 473", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 70 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 103", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n18 + 3 = 21\n700 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 159", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 50 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 504", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n40 + 4 = 44\n700 + 44 = 744\n744 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n5 + 7 = 12\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1655", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 70 = 140\n9 + 6 = 15\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n8 + 7 = 15\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 660", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1391", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 0 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n1300 + 140 = 1440  \n1440 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 4 + 5 + 4 = 1053"}
{"Question": "Q: 511 + 325", "Answer": "A: 836", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n11 + 20 = 31\n800 + 31 = 831\n831 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 360", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 60 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1455", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 40 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 202", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 0 = 90\n9 + 2 = 11\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 926", "Answer": "A: 1797", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 20 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 754", "Answer": "A: 1369", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n15 + 50 = 65\n1300 + 65 = 1365\n1365 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n9 + 70 = 79\n1100 + 79 = 1179\n1179 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6 \n1006 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 848", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 747", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 40 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 634", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 30 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 90 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1792", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 50 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 411", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 8 = 1258"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 180", "Answer": "A: 289", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n9 + 80 = 89\n200 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1250", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 30 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 219", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 518", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960  \n960 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1 + 4 = 5\n1000 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 989", "Answer": "A: 1947", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 80 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n16 + 70 = 86\n1300 + 86"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 153", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n700 + 110 = 810  \n810 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1508", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n7 + 1 = 8\n1500 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1560", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n1500 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1455", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 310", "Answer": "A: 568", "Explanation": "250 + 300 = 550\n8 + 10 = 18\n550 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1754", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 60 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n3 + 1 = 4\n1750 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 332", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n7 + 40 = 47\n1200 + 47 = 1247\n1247 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 419", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 20 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 10 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9\n1100 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6 = 1206\n1206 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 508", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n7 + 8 = 15\n800 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1822", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n20 + 90 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 8 = 28\n1100 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 478", "Answer": "A: 635", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 8 = 15\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 327", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n5 + 20 = 25\n700 + 25 = 725\n725 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n9 + 80 = 89\n1100 + 89 = 1189\n1189 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1562", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 70 = 140\n8 + 6 = 14\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n8 + 5 = 13\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1538", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n6 + 30 = 36\n1500 + 36 = 1536\n1536 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 365", "Answer": "A: 1304", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n7 + 18 = 25  \n1600 + 25  "}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 410", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n15 + 10 = 25\n600 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 637", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1514", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 10 = 100\n8 + 6 = 14\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 259", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n20 + 3 = 23  \n50 + 9 = 59  \n23 + 59 = 82  \n900 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 619", "Answer": "A: 767", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 8 + 9\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 5 = 1105\n1105 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1499", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 0 = 90\n5 + 4 = 9\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1584", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n1500 + 80 = 1580  \n1580 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n10 + 70 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 789", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 80 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n5 + 9 = 14\n1600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 621", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9 + 1 = 910"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 196", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n600 + 160 = 760  \n760 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 196", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n900 + 170 = 1070  \n1070 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 315", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n5 + 9 = 14\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 425", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n70 + 20 = 90  \n1100 + 90 = 1190  \n1190 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 291", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 407", "Answer": "A: 763", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 0 = 50\n6 + 7 = 13\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 468", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 60 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 124", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n40 + 20 = 60  \n7 + 4 = 11  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 700 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n97\n1600 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1538", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 60 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n3 + 4 = 7\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 673", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n1300 + 130 = 1430  \n1430 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1503", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n8 + 90 = 98\n1400 + 98 = 1498\n1498 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n9 + 7 = 16\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1892", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n10 + 80 = 90\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 304 + 514", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n4 + 10 = 14\n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 512", "Answer": "A: 812", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n800 + 12 = 812"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 357", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 205", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 5 = 35\n700 + 35 = 735\n735 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 188", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n97 + 80 = 177  \n800 + 177 = 977  \n977 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 717", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n1300 + 40 = 1340  \n1340 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n6 + 5 = 11\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 218", "Answer": "A: 687", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n9 + 8 = 17\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n87 \n1000 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 468", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n8 + 8 = 16  \n700 + 80 = 780  \n780 + 16  "}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n7 + 90 = 97\n1100 + 97 = 1197\n1197 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 110", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n99 + 10 = 109\n600 + 109 = 709"}
{"Question": "Q: 107 + 153", "Answer": "A: 260", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n7 + 50 = 57  \n200 + 57 = 257  \n257 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 363", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 178", "Answer": "A: 571", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 70 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 3\n563 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n6 + 80 = 86\n1100 + 86 = 1186\n1186 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 408", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 8 = 58\n600 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 343", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 485", "Answer": "A: 729", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 80 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 160", "Answer": "A: 532", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n72 + 60 = 132\n400 + 132"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1615", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 90 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n5 + 10 = 15\n1300 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 6 = 13\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 207", "Answer": "A: 515", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n8 + 7 = 15\n500 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 106", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n86 + 6 = 92  \n800 + 92"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 115", "Answer": "A: 264", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 10 = 50\n9 + 5 = 14\n200 + 50 = 250\n250 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 262", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n6 + 7 = 13\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 642", "Answer": "A: 800", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 6 = 86\n1400 + 86 = 1486\n1486 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 661", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 219", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 10 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 30 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 224", "Answer": "A: 703", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9 = 699\n699 + 4 = 703"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n1 + 20 = 21\n1100 + 21 = 1121\n1121 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 590", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 90 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n15 + 70 = 85\n1200 + 85"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1664", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n10 + 40 = 50\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 90 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 393", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 90 = 180\n9 + 3 = 12\n500 + 180 = 680\n680 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 80 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 232", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3\n1200 + 2\n120"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n3 + 19 = 22\n1200 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 313", "Answer": "A: 479", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 10 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 722", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 176", "Answer": "A: 412", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n6 + 6 = 12  \n300 + 100 = 400  \n400 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 104", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 4 = 54\n600 + 54 = 654\n654 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1593", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n7 + 6 = 13  \n1500 + 80 = 1580  \n1580 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 769 + 423", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1800", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 10 = 100\n1700 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n3 + 60 = 63\n1100 + 63 = 1163\n1163 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n2 + 30 = 32\n1200 + 32 = 1232\n1232 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 852", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n16 + 50 = 66  \n900 + 66 = 966  \n966 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 116", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n2 + 16 = 18\n600 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n7 + 9 = 16\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 406", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n10 + 6 = 16\n600 + 16 = 616\n616 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1876", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 90 = 170\n1700 + 170 = 1870\n1870 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 271", "Answer": "A: 459", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n300 + 150 = 450  \n450 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 447", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n45 + 47 = 92  \n800 + 92 = 892"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 602", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 0 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n9 + 7 = 16\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 264", "Answer": "A: 491", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 60 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 319", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 232", "Answer": "A: 554", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1428", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n5 + 20 = 25\n1400 + 25 = 1425\n1425 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 246", "Answer": "A: 533", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 40 = 120\n7 + 6 = 13\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 440", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n58 + 40 = 98  \n700 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 488", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 109", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n11 + 9 = 20\n1000 + 20 = 1020"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n3 + 9 = 12\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 412", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n900 + 20 = 920\n920 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 454", "Answer": "A: 1372", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n18 + 50 = 68\n1300 + 68 = 1368\n1368 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 5 = 12\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n2 + 1 = 3\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 151", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 50 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 713", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 10 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6 = 876\n876 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 365", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 50 = 100\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 50 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1522", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 50 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1677", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 40 = 60\n9 + 8 = 17\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 255", "Answer": "A: 758", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n3 + 50 = 53\n700 + 53 = 753\n753 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 114", "Answer": "A: 237", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 10 = 30\n3 + 4 = 7\n200 + 30 = 230\n230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 3 \n1240 + 1 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1515", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 10 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1663", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n30 + 30 = 60  \n1 + 2 = 3  \n1600 + 60 = 1660  \n1660 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 234", "Answer": "A: 593", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 30 = 80\n9 + 4 = 13\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1489", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n4 + 5 = 9\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 139", "Answer": "A: 360", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n20 + 30 = 50\n300 + 50 = 350\n350 + 10 = 360\n360 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 230", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 397", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 687", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 80 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1578", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 40 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 582", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 8 = 818\n818 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 117", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "990 + 110 = 1100\n3 + 7 = 10\n1100 + 10 = 1110"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 384", "Answer": "A: 575", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n400 + 170 = 570  \n570 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 108 + 439", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n8 + 30 = 38\n500 + 38 = 538\n538 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 436", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 30 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 685", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 750", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n18 + 50 = 68\n800 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1656", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 238", "Answer": "A: 445", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n7 + 30 = 37\n400 + 37 = 437\n437 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 70 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 665", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1548", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 90 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 7 + 1 = 1548"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 566", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 10 = 1330\n1330"}
{"Question": "Q: 788 + 662", "Answer": "A: 1450", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 60 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 10 = 1450"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 396", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n3 + 19 = 22\n1000 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1427", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7 = 1427\n1427 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 536", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n4 + 30 = 34\n1000 + 34 = 1034\n1034 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 331", "Answer": "A: 450", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n19 + 30 = 49\n400 + 49 = 449\n449 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 393", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n9 + 90 = 99\n700 + 99 = 799\n799 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 137", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1751", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n\n80 + 60 = 140\n\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n\n1740 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 30 = 70\n8 + 8 = 16\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 109", "Answer": "A: 643", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 9 = 39\n600 + 39 = 639\n639 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 464", "Answer": "A: 697", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 60 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 271", "Answer": "A: 695", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 453", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n4 + 50 = 54\n1300 + 54 = 1354\n1354 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 268", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 60 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 220", "Answer": "A: 494", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 20 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 357", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n9 + 7 = 16\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 713", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n15 + 40 = 55\n1100 + 55 = 1155\n1155 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1537", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n4 + 3 = 7  \n1400 + 130 = 1530  \n1530 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 103", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 0 = 80\n1 + 3 = 4\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 352", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 50 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1921", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 80 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n6 + 20 = 26\n1200 + 26 = 1226\n1226 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 631", "Answer": "A: 786", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 530", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 161", "Answer": "A: 1061", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 1 = 61\n1000 + 61"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 428", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 140", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n600 - 1 = 599\n599 + 40 = 639\n639 + 100 = 739"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1463", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 150", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n26 + 50 = 76\n400 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 184", "Answer": "A: 466", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 80 = 160\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1391", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 0 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 108", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 0 = 60\n3 + 8 = 11\n\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n5 + 6 = 11\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n3 + 50 = 53\n1400 + 53 = 1453\n1453 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 300", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 0 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1618", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 8 = 1618"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 373", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 799", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 4 + 9 = 953"}
{"Question": "Q: 423 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350 \n1350 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 40 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 282", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 80 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 736", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n800 + 120 = 920  \n920 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 949 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1924", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 70 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 352", "Answer": "A: 468", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n16 + 50 = 66  \n400 + 66 = 466  \n466 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 161", "Answer": "A: 287", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 60 = 80\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 498", "Answer": "A: 600", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n2 + 98 = 100\n500 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 287", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 594", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n8 + 4 = 12\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 116", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n90 + 10 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n1 + 6 = 7\n700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1725", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 60 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n2 + 3 = 5\n1720 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 374", "Answer": "A: 597", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 70 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1731", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 40 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1898", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 40 = 90\n5 + 3 = 8\n1800 + 90 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 232", "Answer": "A: 424", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n90 + 30 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 4 = 424"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n75 + 45 = 120\n1000 + 120"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 20 = 40\n5 + 9 = 14\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 197", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 524", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 234", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n9 + 20 = 29\n1400 + 29 = 1429\n1429 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1652", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n4 + 40 = 44\n1600 + 44 = 1644\n1644 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 842", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n11 + 50 = 61\n1200 + 61 = 1261\n1261 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 262", "Answer": "A: 712", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 60 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1674", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 10 = 70\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 596", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 90 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 7 = 807\n807 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 162", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 553", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1427", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 136", "Answer": "A: 336", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n36\n300 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n7 + 20 = 27\n1300 + 27 = 1327\n1327 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 424", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n6 + 4 = 10\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 411", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 30 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 10 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n17 + 40 = 57\n1200 + 57 = 1257\n1257 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 161", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n2 + 60 = 62\n800 + 62 = 862\n862 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 10 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n5 + 7 = 12\n1500 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 499", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n4 + 90 = 94\n500 + 94 = 594\n594 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 906", "Answer": "A: 1886", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 6 = 86\n1800 + 86"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1760", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n7 + 50 = 57\n1700 + 57 = 1757\n1757 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 266", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 320", "Answer": "A: 568", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 307", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n27 + 7 = 34\n1000 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 70 = 100\n8 + 3 = 11\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 281", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n1 + 80 = 81\n700 + 81 = 781\n781 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n1100 + 100 = 1200  \n1200 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 422", "Answer": "A: 811", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 2 = 11\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 224", "Answer": "A: 554", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 20 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 10 = 1530"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 391", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 90 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 4 = 564"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 90 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3\n1193 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 331", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 1 + 1 = 792"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n50 + 10 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 532", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 798", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 233", "Answer": "A: 550", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n10 + 30 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 80 = 90\n5 + 2 = 7\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 411", "Answer": "A: 714", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n3 + 11 = 14\n700 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 252", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 50 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 285", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 80 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 559", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 10 = 20\n1200 + 20 = 1220\n1220 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1715", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n3 + 12 = 15\n1700 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 673", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1 + 3 = 4\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 202", "Answer": "A: 864", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n60 + 0 = 60  \n800 + 60 = 860  \n860 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1498", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n48 + 50 = 98\n1400 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 117", "Answer": "A: 568", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 10 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n1 + 90 = 91\n1000 + 91 = 1091\n1091 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 20 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 579", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 70 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1575", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 40 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 628", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n10 + 20 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 167", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1550", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 90 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 10 = 1550"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 9 = 1569"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 8 = 38\n1000 + 38 = 1038\n1038 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 169", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n60 + 60 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 9  \n9 = 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 477", "Answer": "A: 578", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n1 + 70 = 71\n500 + 71 = 571\n571 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 346 + 310", "Answer": "A: 656", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 244", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n4 + 40 = 44\n1000 + 44"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 293", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 198", "Answer": "A: 602", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n4 + 90 = 94\n500 + 94 = 594\n594 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 14 = 24\n1100 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 171", "Answer": "A: 578", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n7 + 70 = 77\n500 + 77 = 577\n577 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n5 + 3 = 8\n1000 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 440", "Answer": "A: 1263", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n2 + 20 = 22  \n1200 + 22 = 1222  \n1222 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 511 + 390", "Answer": "A: 901", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 90 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 150", "Answer": "A: 435", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 50 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6\n1200 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 121", "Answer": "A: 363", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n2 + 1 = 3\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 358", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 546", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 40 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 7\n927 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 383", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n7 + 80 = 87  \n700 + 87 = 787  \n787 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 813", "Answer": "A: 928", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n15 + 13 = 28\n900 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 172", "Answer": "A: 468", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 70 = 160\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 333", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 30 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 314", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 513", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1675", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n10 + 60 = 70\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1756", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 70 = 150\n1 + 5 = 6\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 271", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 7\n900 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 147", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n55 + 40 = 95  \n900 + 95 = 995  \n995 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 175", "Answer": "A: 478", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n3 + 70 = 73\n400 + 73 = 473\n473 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n7 + 50 = 57\n1100 + 57 = 1157\n1157 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 389", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 80 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 384", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 9\n950 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 429", "Answer": "A: 582", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 20 = 70\n3 + 9 = 12\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1819", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 80 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 9 = 1819"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 436", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n2 + 30 = 32  \n1000 + 32 = 1032  \n1032 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 263", "Answer": "A: 540", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 60 = 130\n7 + 3 = 10\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 292", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 511", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 9\n960 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070 \n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n9 + 9 = 18\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 350", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "250 + 350 = 600\n3 + 600 = 603"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 6\n1256 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 768", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8 + 1 = 1229"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 70 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1555", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 60 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 176", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 162", "Answer": "A: 479", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n17 + 60 = 77\n400 + 77 = 477\n477 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 160", "Answer": "A: 479", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n19 + 60 = 79\n400 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 50 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 791", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 5 = 945\n945 - 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 335", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n3 + 5 = 8\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 728", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n1 + 8 = 9\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 311", "Answer": "A: 443", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 10 = 40\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 329", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n1 + 20 = 21\n900 + 21 = 921\n921 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 171", "Answer": "A: 493", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 70 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 3 = 493"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 20 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 60 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 3 = 1373\n1373 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 728", "Answer": "A: 864", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 339", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 30 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 9\n770 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n90 + 2 = 92\n1000 + 92 = 1092\n1092 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 100", "Answer": "A: 646", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n46 \n600 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 363", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 269", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 60 = 100\n4 + 9 = 13\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 183", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "900 + 90 = 990\n100 + 80 = 180\n990 + 180 = 1170\n1170 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1773", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n7 + 60 = 67\n1700 + 67 = 1767\n1767 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 316", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 367", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 125", "Answer": "A: 229", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n4 + 20 = 24\n200 + 24 = 224\n224 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 \n1230 + 9 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 394", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n1 + 90 = 91\n800 + 91 = 891\n891 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1393", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 111", "Answer": "A: 213", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n2 + 10 = 12\n200 + 12 = 212\n212 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 656", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n14 + 50 = 64  \n1500 + 64 = 1564  \n1564 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 475", "Answer": "A: 713", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 70 = 100\n8 + 5 = 13\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 494", "Answer": "A: 864", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 10 = 1260"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1661", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 1 = 61\n1600 + 61"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 30 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 299", "Answer": "A: 561", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 90 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 207", "Answer": "A: 955", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 0 = 40\n8 + 7 = 15\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1562", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 80 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 307", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n19 + 7 = 26\n600 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1565", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n1 + 4 = 5\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 941", "Answer": "A: 1685", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 1 = 41\n1600 + 41 = 1641\n1641 + 44 "}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 301", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 1 = 71\n600 + 71 = 671\n671 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 582", "Answer": "A: 746", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 80 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 121 + 161", "Answer": "A: 282", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n21 + 60 = 81  \n200 + 81 = 281  \n281 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 425", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n2 + 5 = 7\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9 = 1209\n1209 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 434", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 6 = 986"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 60 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 60 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7 + 4 = 1321"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 10 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 345", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1833", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 40 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n7 + 6 = 13\n1820 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 104", "Answer": "A: 366", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 4 = 64\n300 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 604", "Answer": "A: 1170", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 4 = 64\n1100 + 64 = 1164\n1164 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 175", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 60 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 769 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1070", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 0 = 60\n9 + 1 = 10\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 571", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n71 + 0 = 71\n900 + 71"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 330", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 4 = 34\n700 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 671", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n5 + 1 = 6\n1350 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 708", "Answer": "A: 1148", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 8 = 48\n1100 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n6 + 9 = 15\n1000 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1626", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 246", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 6 = 13\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 383", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n50 + 80 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1620", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 40 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 431", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 30 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 195 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n1400 + 70 = 1470  \n1470 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 143", "Answer": "A: 571", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n8 + 3 = 11  \n500 + 60 = 560  \n560 + 11  "}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 40 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1754", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 30 = 40\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1868", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 40 = 60\n1800 + 60 = 1860\n1860 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 603", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n13 + 3 = 16\n1100 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 195", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n16 + 90 = 106\n800 + 106 = 906\n906 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 498", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 90 = 150\n7 + 8 = 15\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1673", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n8 + 5 = 13\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 191", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n900 + 150 = 1050  \n1050 + 4  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 711", "Answer": "A: 934", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 10 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1196", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n3 + 3 = 6\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 351", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 750", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n19 + 30 = 49\n1300 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n7 + 7 = 14\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 191", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n8 + 90 = 98  \n600 + 98 = 698  \n698 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 759", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 257", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n900 + 130 = 1030  \n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n1 + 50 = 51\n1000 + 51 = 1051 \n1051 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 499", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9\n710 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 2 = 9\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 383", "Answer": "A: 695", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 80 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 221", "Answer": "A: 666", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 1 = 6\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 362", "Answer": "A: 881", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 60 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 197", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n10 + 90 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000   \n55 + 50 = 105   \n1000 + 105 = 1105  \n1105 + 1   "}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 0 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 614", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n4 + 5 = 9\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 554", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "150 + 550 = 700\n4 + 54 = 58\n700 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 164", "Answer": "A: 490", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 60 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1822", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 20 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 60 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 752", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5 = 915\n915 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1405", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1300 + 100 = 1400  \n1400 + 4  \n1404 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 468", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 131", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n4 + 1 = 5  \n1000 + 80 = 1080  \n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 473", "Answer": "A: 713", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 70 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 338", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 7 = 97\n1200 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 273", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 70 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 3 \n840 + 3 = 843\n843 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 60 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1365", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n2 + 9 = 11\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 197", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 1 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 810", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n900 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 621", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 20 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 281", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n3 + 80 = 83  \n900 + 83 = 983  \n983 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 417", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n5 + 17 = 22\n800 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 573", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 70 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 229", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 327", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 20 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6 \n870 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 126", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n6 + 20 = 26\n900 + 26 = 926\n926 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 376", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 70 = 110\n1 + 6 = 7\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n8 + 7 = 15\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n14 + 60 = 74\n1000 + 74 = 1074\n1074 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 186", "Answer": "A: 657", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 80 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 357", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n2 + 50 = 52\n1000 + 52 = 1052\n1052 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 178", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 70 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 4 = 724\n724 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 90 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 9 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 90 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 10 = 30\n1500 + 30 = 1530\n1530 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1760", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n4 + 50 = 54\n1700 + 54 = 1754\n1754 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "685 + 450:\n600 + 400 = 1000\n85 + 50 = 135\n1000 + 135"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 70 = 160\n5 + 8 = 13\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 484", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n800 + 170 = 970  \n970 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 225", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 20 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 10 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 398", "Answer": "A: 511", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 90 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n3 + 8 = 11\n500 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 611", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 171", "Answer": "A: 521", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 70 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1576", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n76 + 0 = 76\n1500 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1631", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n5 + 6 = 11\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 717", "Answer": "A: 1457", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 10 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1583", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 80 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n8 + 90 = 98\n1100 + 98 = 1198\n1198 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n16 + 40 = 56  \n1000 + 56 = 1056  \n1056 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1545", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n45 \n1500 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 139", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 7 = 47\n800 + 47 = 847\n847 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 382", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 128", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1591", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n56 + 70 = 126\n1200 + 126 = 1326\n1326"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 194", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n12 + 90 = 102  \n900 + 102 = 1002  \n1002 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 424", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 20 = 90\n5 + 4 = 9\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 520", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n1400 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1714", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 50 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 3 + 1\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 657", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n800 + 120 = 920  \n920 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1572", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n11 + 60 = 71\n1500 + 71 = 1571\n1571 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 230", "Answer": "A: 637", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n7 + 30 = 37\n600 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 1 = 1151\n1151 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1718", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 90 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 8 = 1718"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 230", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 5 = 1135\n1135 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 132", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6 = 806\n806 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1667", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n9 + 8 = 17\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 354", "Answer": "A: 555", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n1 + 50 = 51\n500 + 51 = 551\n551 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 580", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n600 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1891", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n8 + 3 = 11  \n1800 + 80 = 1880  \n1880 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 392", "Answer": "A: 627", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 90 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 313", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 8  \n640 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1730", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n1600 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 283", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 3 = 1123\n1123 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n4 + 40 = 44\n1300 + 44 = 1344\n1344 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 463", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1766", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 90 = 160\n1 + 5 = 6\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1734", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 7 = 14\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n7 + 9 = 16  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 330", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n55 + 30 = 85\n900 + 85"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 50 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 172", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 70 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 741", "Answer": "A: 944", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n3 + 40 = 43\n900 + 43 = 943\n943 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 367", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n2 + 7 = 9\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 658", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 50 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 12 "}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1545", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 10 = 40\n1 + 4 = 5\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 710 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n10 + 20 = 30\n1500 + 30 = 1530\n1530 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 0 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 1 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 358", "Answer": "A: 590", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n2 + 8 = 10\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 110", "Answer": "A: 335", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n25 + 10 = 35\n300 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 149", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 283", "Answer": "A: 411", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 80 = 100\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1573", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n5 + 8 = 13\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 843 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 238", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 372", "Answer": "A: 507", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 70 = 100\n5 + 2 = 7\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 425", "Answer": "A: 600", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n75 + 25 = 100\n500 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 364", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n60 + 60 = 120  \n1200 + 120 = 1320  \n1320 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1650", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 2 = 42\n1600 + 42 = 1642\n1642 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n5 + 60 = 65\n1400 + 65 = 1465\n1465 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1721", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 40 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 110", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n60 + 10 = 70  \n700 + 70 = 770  \n770 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n18 + 30 = 48\n1000 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 422", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n6 + 20 = 26\n700 + 26 = 726\n726 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 239", "Answer": "A: 450", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n11 + 30 = 41\n400 + 41 = 441\n441 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 676", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9 = 1499\n1499 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n17 + 16 = 33\n1300 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1162", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 276", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n1 + 6 = 7\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 7 = 1017"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1500", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 30 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1414", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n50 + 50 = 100  \n8 + 6 = 14  \n1300 + 100 = 1400  \n1400 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 50 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 482", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n3 + 80 = 83\n1200 + 83 = 1283\n1283 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 4 = 94\n1200 + 94 = 1294\n1294 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 797", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 90 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1937", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n90 + 30 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n9 + 8 = 17\n1920 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 292", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 432", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n9 + 10 = 19\n1500 + 19 = 1519\n1519 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 481", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n6 + 80 = 86\n900 + 86 = 986\n986 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 714", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 10 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 342", "Answer": "A: 480", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n400 + 70 = 470  \n470 + 10 = 480"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n15 + 11 = 26\n1200 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 347", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 = 897\n897 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 682", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 10 = 930"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 80 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 641", "Answer": "A: 1615", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 40 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 202", "Answer": "A: 438", "Explanation": "200 + 30 = 230\n230 + 6 = 236\n200 + 2 = 202\n236 + 202"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 135", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n9 + 5 = 14\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1844", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n1700 + 130 = 1830  \n1830 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 247", "Answer": "A: 473", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 40 = 60\n6 + 7 = 13\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 179", "Answer": "A: 323", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 70 = 110\n4 + 9 = 13\n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 713", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n1 + 13 = 14\n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 358", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 5\n845 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 536", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n2 + 6 = 8\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 404", "Answer": "A: 523", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n19 + 4 = 23\n500 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 606", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 6 = 96\n1500 + 96 = 1596\n1596 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 595", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n10 + 90 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 4\n700 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 641", "Answer": "A: 1499", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 40 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 8 \n1490 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3\n1193 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 284", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1631", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 90 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 223", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n9 + 4 = 13\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 174", "Answer": "A: 277", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n3 + 70 = 73\n200 + 73 = 273\n273 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 232", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 267", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 60 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 5\n785 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1634", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 7 = 27\n1600 + 27 = 1627\n1627 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 511 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n11 + 50 = 61\n1000 + 61 = 1061\n1061 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 198", "Answer": "A: 399", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n1 - 2 = -1\n400 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 364", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 498", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7 + 8 = 1135"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n30 + 7 = 37  \n1000 + 37 = 1037  \n1037 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 734", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 30 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 0 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1545", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n18 + 20 = 38\n1500 + 38 = 1538\n1538 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 106", "Answer": "A: 225", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 6 = 16\n200 + 16 = 216\n216 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n5 + 80 = 85\n1300 + 85 = 1385\n1385 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 154", "Answer": "A: 257", "Explanation": "100 + 150 = 250\n3 + 4 = 7\n250 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 477", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700 \n90 + 70 = 160 \n700 + 160 = 860 \n860 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 8 = 78\n1200 + 78 = 1278\n1278 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 295", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 90 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1766", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n1 + 5 = 6\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 461", "Answer": "A: 812", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "1000 + 96\n100 + 900 = 1000"}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 385", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 216", "Answer": "A: 661", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n4 + 30 = 34\n1100 + 34 = 1134\n1134 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1532", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 40 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1295", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n55 + 40 = 95\n1200 + 95"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 512", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 10 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n40 + 20 = 60  \n6 + 9 = 15  \n1300 + 60 = 1360  \n1360 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 180", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n700 + 150 = 850  \n850 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 399", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 90 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9 = 1019\n1019 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1738", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 50 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 256", "Answer": "A: 375", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n19 + 50 = 69\n300 + 69 = 369\n369 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 509", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 9 = 19\n900 + 19 = 919\n919 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 346", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 40 = 90\n8 + 6 = 14\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 372", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 70 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1406", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 769 + 499", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 100", "Answer": "A: 211", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 418", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 468", "Answer": "A: 1370", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n2 + 60 = 62  \n1300 + 62 = 1362  \n1362 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 317", "Answer": "A: 470", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 10 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1542", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 20 = 30\n1500 + 30 = 1530\n1530 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 620", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n3 + 20 = 23\n900 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 9 = 1349"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1486", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n\n40 + 40 = 80\n\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n\n1480 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 202", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 539 + 209", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 9 = 39\n700 + 39 = 739\n739 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 9 = 49\n1100 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 163", "Answer": "A: 447", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 60 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 598", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 984", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 200", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n36\n600 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 670", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 941", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n20 + 40 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 181", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n7 + 1 = 8\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1439", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9 = 1439"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n75 + 70 = 145  \n1300 + 145 = 1445  \n1445 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n1 + 50 = 51\n1400 + 51 = 1451\n1451 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 906", "Answer": "A: 1406", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n1400 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 168", "Answer": "A: 443", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 60 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 5 = 435\n435 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 245", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1 + 5 = 6\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n6 + 50 = 56\n1200 + 56 = 1256\n1256 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 107", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n40 + 7 = 47  \n800 + 47"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 601", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 1 = 31\n1200 + 31 = 1231\n1231 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 165", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n5 + 60 = 65\n700 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n4 + 80 = 84\n1000 + 84 = 1084\n1084 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 431", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 8\n920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1637", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 10 = 30\n1600 + 30 = 1630\n1630 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 984", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 84 = 94\n1100 + 94"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 182", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 80 = 160\n5 + 2 = 7\n300 + 160 = 460\n460 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6\n1000 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 80 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 9 = 1639\n1639 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 393", "Answer": "A: 506", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n400 + 100 = 500  \n500 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 385", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 314", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n99 + 2 = 101\n1200 + 101"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 232", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 30 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n7 + 2 = 9\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n7 + 6 = 13\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 186", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n2 + 80 = 82\n400 + 82 = 482\n482 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 527", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 20 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300  \n6 + 20 = 26  \n1300 + 26 = 1326  \n1326 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n8 + 30 = 38\n1200 + 38 = 1238\n1238 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 135", "Answer": "A: 765", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 231", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 30 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 8 + 1 = 709"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 612", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n1000 + 100 = 1100  \n1100 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n75 + 40 = 115\n1000 + 115 = 1115\n1115 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 178", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n5 + 8 = 13  \n500 + 160 = 660  \n660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 498", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 513", "Answer": "A: 1250", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 7\n1240 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 332", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n1200 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 20 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n2 + 3 = 5\n1600 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 20 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 693", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n9 + 3 = 12\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 265", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n1000 + 100 = 1100  \n1100 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n4 + 90 = 94\n1300 + 94 = 1394\n1394 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 989", "Answer": "A: 1819", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 80 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 330", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n72 + 30 = 102\n600 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 129", "Answer": "A: 472", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 9 = 12\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 206", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 6 = 96\n900 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 633", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 786", "Answer": "A: 928", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 8\n920 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 778", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 16 = 946"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1422", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n9 + 10 = 19\n1000 + 19 = 1019\n1019 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 360", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 60 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 267", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n600 + 140 = 740  \n740 + 7 = 747  \n747 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n9 + 7 = 16\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 599", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n600 + 170 = 770  \n770 + 14  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 518", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 10 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1626", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n1500 + 120 = 1620  \n1620 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 603", "Answer": "A: 1463", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 3 = 63\n1400 + 63"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 372", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n1 + 2 = 3\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n5 + 90 = 95\n1400 + 95 = 1495\n1495 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 229", "Answer": "A: 369", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 243", "Answer": "A: 477", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 40 = 70\n4 + 3 = 7\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1 + 4 = 5\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 633 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 4 = 34\n1400 + 34 = 1434\n1434 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 159", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n9 + 50 = 59\n800 + 59 = 859\n859 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 20 = 30\n6 + 9 = 15\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 316", "Answer": "A: 803", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 7\n797 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 2 = 32\n1300 + 32 = 1332\n1332 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 9 = 19\n1300 + 19 = 1319\n1319 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 471", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 70 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 415", "Answer": "A: 1304", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n9 + 5 = 14\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n8 + 2 = 10\n1200 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 176 + 799", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 90 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 6 + 9 = 975"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 169", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n4 + 9 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 340", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 40 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 236", "Answer": "A: 341", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n5 + 30 = 35\n300 + 35 = 335\n335 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 394 + 197", "Answer": "A: 591", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 90 = 180\n400 + 180 = 580\n580 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1112", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n6 + 6 = 12\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1823", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 3 = 23\n1800 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1777", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 0 = 70\n7 + 0 = 7\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 240", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n76 + 40 = 116  \n1000 + 116"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 20 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 324", "Answer": "A: 641", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n17 + 20 = 37\n600 + 37 = 637\n637 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 217", "Answer": "A: 694", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 7 \n680 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 608", "Answer": "A: 773", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n5 + 8 = 13\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 834", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n5 + 30 = 35\n1200 + 35 = 1235\n1235 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 420", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n1000 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 191", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700   \n30 + 90 = 120   \n700 + 120 = 820   \n820 + 8 = 828   "}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1715", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 550", "Answer": "A: 1399", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n49 + 50 = 99\n1300 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 50 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 208 + 676", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n8 + 70 = 78\n800 + 78 = 878\n878 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 277", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7\n1120 + 7 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1639", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 50 = 130\n5 + 4 = 9\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1783", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n4 + 70 = 74\n1700 + 74 = 1774\n1774 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 70 = 140\n6 + 1 = 7\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 581", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n3 + 80 = 83\n900 + 83 = 983\n983 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 90 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 10 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1571", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 90 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 3 = 10\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 612", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 631", "Answer": "A: 735", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n4 + 30 = 34\n700 + 34 = 734\n734 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 332", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 938 + 839", "Answer": "A: 1777", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 30 = 60\n8 + 9 = 17\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 802", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 2 = 82\n900 + 82 = 982\n982 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 614", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n14 + 14 = 28\n1200 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 615", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 240", "Answer": "A: 417", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 40 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 639", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n9 + 90 = 99\n900 + 99 = 999\n999 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 150", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 411", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 10 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n6 + 7 = 13\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 70 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 514", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n2 + 4 = 6\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 274", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 121", "Answer": "A: 261", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 20 = 60\n200 + 60 = 260\n260 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n7 + 3 = 10\n1400 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 449", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 307", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 345", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 40 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 456", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n7 + 50 = 57\n800 + 57 = 857\n857 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n8 + 50 = 58\n1300 + 58 = 1358\n1358 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 500", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n27\n800 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 389", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 236", "Answer": "A: 640", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n4 + 30 = 34\n600 + 34 = 634\n634 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 6 = 96\n30 + 8 = 38\n96 + 38 = 134\n1000 + 134"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 202", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 0 = 70\n7 + 2 = 9\n900 + 70 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1596", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n3 + 3 = 6\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 90 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 369", "Answer": "A: 757", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n8 + 9 = 17\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 599", "Answer": "A: 871", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 140", "Answer": "A: 337", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 40 = 130\n200 - 3 = 197\n130 + 7 = 137\n197 + 140 = 337"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1748", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 70 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 1 + 7 = 1748"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 498", "Answer": "A: 617", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n19 + 80 = 99\n500 + 99 = 599\n599 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 195", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 125", "Answer": "A: 336", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n11 + 20 = 31\n300 + 31 = 331\n331 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 30 = 40\n4 + 8 = 12\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 217", "Answer": "A: 390", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n73 + 17 = 90  \n300 + 90 = 390"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 113", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 90 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 5 = 35\n1200 + 35 = 1235\n1235 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1841", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 70 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 350", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1658", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n9 + 9 = 18  \n1500 + 140 = 1640  \n1640 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1432", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 123", "Answer": "A: 637", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n10 + 20 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 4\n630 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1557", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1400 + 150 = 1550  \n1550 + 7 = 1557\n1557 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 3 \n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 258", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1411", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 823", "Answer": "A: 993", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 759", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1 + 9 = 930"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 729", "Answer": "A: 947", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 20 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n8 + 9 = 17\n930 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1767", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 307", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 0 = 40\n9 + 7 = 16\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 2\n1200 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n9 + 70 = 79\n1200 + 79 = 1279\n1279 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n4 + 5 = 9\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 227", "Answer": "A: 1000", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n3 + 7 = 10\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 10 "}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 504", "Answer": "A: 679", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 4 = 74\n600 + 74 = 674\n674 + 5 "}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 387", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n10 + 80 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 487", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 389", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 80 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 706", "Answer": "A: 1562", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 6 = 56\n1500 + 56 = 1556\n1556 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 333", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 30 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 4 = 24\n1300 + 24 = 1324\n1324 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9 = 1139"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n70 + 8 = 78  \n1200 + 78 = 1278  \n1278 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 312", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1663", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 10 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 398", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 90 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 + 2 = 1005"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 329", "Answer": "A: 532", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n3 + 20 = 23\n500 + 23 = 523\n523 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 279", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 120", "Answer": "A: 388", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n300 + 80 = 380  \n380 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 143", "Answer": "A: 755", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n10 + 40 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 446", "Answer": "A: 674", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 40 = 60\n8 + 6 = 14\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n40 + 80 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n7 + 40 = 47\n1300 + 47 = 1347\n1347 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 455", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 220", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 20 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 455", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n9 + 50 = 59\n700 + 59 = 759\n759 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1645", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 30 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 220", "Answer": "A: 511", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n90 + 20 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 541", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n2 + 40 = 42\n700 + 42 = 742\n742 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n7 + 70 = 77\n1000 + 77"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 133", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 30 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 702", "Answer": "A: 914", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n12 + 2 = 14\n900 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 595", "Answer": "A: 810", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n\n10 + 90 = 100\n\n700 + 100 = 800\n\n800 + 15 = 815\n\n815 - 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 115", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n8 + 15 = 23\n800 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 296", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n6 + 90 = 96\n1100 + 96 = 1196\n1196 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n1200 + 150 = 1350  \n1350 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 140", "Answer": "A: 268", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 40 = 60\n200 + 60 = 260\n260 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 391", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n3 + 90 = 93\n900 + 93 = 993\n993 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1406", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 135", "Answer": "A: 570", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 5 = 10\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 510", "Answer": "A: 1399", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 734", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 4 = 8\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1466", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 70 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 142", "Answer": "A: 351", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n9 + 40 = 49\n300 + 49 = 349\n349 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 771", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 70 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 270", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 7 = 47\n1300 + 47"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 6 \n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 331", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 430 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1258", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 548", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 418", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n8 + 8 = 16\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 209", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n6 + 9 = 15\n1100 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 187", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n600 + 120 = 720  \n720 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 247", "Answer": "A: 528", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n1 + 7 = 8  \n400 + 120 = 520  \n520 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 260", "Answer": "A: 448", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n300 + 140 = 440  \n440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1800", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n1700 + 90 = 1790  \n1790 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 20 = 90\n7 + 7 = 14\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 261", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 149", "Answer": "A: 277", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n8 + 9 = 17  \n200 + 60 = 260  \n260 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 569 + 385", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 80 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 9 = 949\n949 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1583", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 20 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1705", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 70 = 100\n1 + 4 = 5\n1600 + 100 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 418", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 123", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 20 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 158", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 50 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 6 = 516\n516 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 143", "Answer": "A: 569", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 40 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n10 + 90 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1736", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n11 + 20 = 31\n1700 + 31 = 1731\n1731 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 20 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 1 + 7 = 1468"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 275", "Answer": "A: 578", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n3 + 70 = 73\n500 + 73 = 573\n573 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 185", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n1000 + 140 = 1140  \n1140 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 192", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 418", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n8 + 8 = 16\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1788", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n50 + 30 = 80\n3 + 5 = 8\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 9\n1549 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 313", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 269", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 60 = 130\n8 + 9 = 17\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200  \n19 + 50 = 69  \n1200 + 69 = 1269  \n1269 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1547", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 196", "Answer": "A: 531", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n400 + 120 = 520  \n520 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 268", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 793", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 273", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1611", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n24 + 80 = 104\n1500 + 104 = 1604\n1604 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 826", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1593", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 8 = 88\n1500 + 88 = 1588\n1588 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1143", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 137", "Answer": "A: 955", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n10 + 30 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 565", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 50 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 539 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1611", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 20 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 171", "Answer": "A: 777", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n6 + 70 = 76\n700 + 76 = 776\n776 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 10 = 1510"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 463", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 60 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 9 = 859\n859 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n10 + 90 = 100\n4 + 5 = 9\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 575", "Answer": "A: 736", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 70 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n70 + 30 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n3 + 9 = 12\n1300 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 50 = 70\n6 + 9 = 15\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 214", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n4 + 4 = 8\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1547", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 349", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 263", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 706", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 6 = 56\n800 + 56 = 856\n856 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 404", "Answer": "A: 712", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n8 + 4 = 12\n700 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 407", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 7 = 27\n1200 + 27 = 1227\n1227 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 327", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3 = 903\n903 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 662", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 60 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 415 + 349", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 40 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 799 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1676", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n9 + 7 = 16\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 663", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3\n880 + 3 = 883\n883 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 183", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n90 + 80 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 10 = 780"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 346", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 373", "Answer": "A: 569", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n90 + 70 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 6\n566 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n5 + 90 = 95\n1100 + 95 = 1195\n1195 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n3 + 8 = 11\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 358", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 7 = 9\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 292", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n8 + 90 = 98\n600 + 98 = 698\n698 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 595", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n700 + 170 = 870  \n870 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 148", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 210", "Answer": "A: 759", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n49 + 10 = 59\n700 + 59"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n11 + 50 = 61\n1500 + 61 = 1561\n1561 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 779", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 70 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1518", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 80 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 572", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 70 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 475", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 70 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 218", "Answer": "A: 914", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6\n906 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1594", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 313", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n1 + 13 = 14\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n8 + 40 = 48\n1000 + 48 = 1048\n1048 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1463", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 20 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 10 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 716", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n10 + 10 = 20  \n900 + 20 = 920  \n920 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 148", "Answer": "A: 392", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 40 = 80\n4 + 8 = 12\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 8 = 38\n1400 + 38 = 1438\n1438 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9 \n1330 + 9 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 148", "Answer": "A: 533", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 40 = 120\n5 + 8 = 13\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 754", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 397", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 4 = 824\n824 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 370", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n51 + 70 = 121  \n600 + 121"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 405", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n70 + 0 = 70  \n9 + 5 = 14  \n600 + 70 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 10 = 30\n1100 + 30 = 1130\n1130 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n6 + 11 = 17\n1500 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n14 + 20 = 34\n1000 + 34 = 1034\n1034 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 374", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n7 + 4 = 11\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 60 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 496", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 151", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "600 + 150 = 750\n2 + 1 = 3\n750 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 297", "Answer": "A: 580", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 90 = 170\n3 + 7 = 10\n\n400 + 170 = 570\n570 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1825", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 70 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1585", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 50 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 174", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 691", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n5 + 90 = 95  \n800 + 95 = 895  \n895 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 540", "Answer": "A: 791", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 229", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 20 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n23 + 25 = 48\n1000 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 385", "Answer": "A: 809", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 80 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 401", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n7 + 1 = 8\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 40 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 222", "Answer": "A: 353", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 20 = 50\n300 + 50 = 350\n350 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 467 + 528", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 8 = 15\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1479", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 9 = 79\n1400 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 158", "Answer": "A: 635", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 50 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 = 627\n627 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 738", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 30 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n8 + 8 = 16\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 400", "Answer": "A: 793", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 0 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 905 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1588", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n5 + 80 = 85\n1500 + 85 = 1585\n1585 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 131", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 6 = 13\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 395", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 9\n1250 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 485", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 80 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 292", "Answer": "A: 648", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n500 + 140 = 640  \n640 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n2 + 9 = 11\n1700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 60 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 297", "Answer": "A: 549", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n400 + 140 = 540  \n540 + 9 = 549  \n549  "}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1728", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 70 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 188", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n4 + 80 = 84\n900 + 84 = 984\n984 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n45 + 10 = 55\n1200 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 257", "Answer": "A: 656", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n99 + 50 = 149\n500 + 149 = 649\n649 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 190 + 753", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 136", "Answer": "A: 661", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n5 + 6 = 11\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 224", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 418", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 432", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 9\n980 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1842", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 80 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 561", "Answer": "A: 1354", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 3 + 1 = 1354"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 242", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 40 = 70\n70 + 4 = 74\n700 + 74 = 774\n774 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1727", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 90 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 330", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n49 + 30 = 79  \n1100 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 117", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n76 + 17 = 93\n800 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 318", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 243", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 614", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 10 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n9 + 4 = 13\n1600 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1196", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 7 = 87\n1100 + 87 = 1187\n1187 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 683", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 141", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n12 + 40 = 52\n800 + 52 = 852\n852 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1568", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n1 + 60 = 61\n1500 + 61 = 1561\n1561 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 183", "Answer": "A: 475", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 80 = 170\n300 + 170 = 470\n470 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 163", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 60 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 8 = 1018"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n8 + 40 = 48\n1300 + 48 = 1348\n1348 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 689", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 585", "Answer": "A: 875", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 9 + 5 = 1554"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 834", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 10 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n4 + 7 = 11\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1891", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n10 + 70 = 80\n1800 + 80 = 1880\n1880 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 226", "Answer": "A: 497", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 20 = 90\n1 + 6 = 7\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 472", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n7 + 70 = 77\n800 + 77 = 877\n877 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 561", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 60 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 336", "Answer": "A: 573", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n7 + 6 = 13\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 214", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1 + 4 = 5\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 303", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n45 + 3 = 48\n1200 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n1000 + 180 = 1180  \n1180 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 568", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 687", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 80 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7 + 9 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1686", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 30 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1789", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 60 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n44 + 2 = 46\n1200 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1636", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n20 + 16 = 36  \n1600 + 36  "}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1263", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n63 + 0 = 63\n1200 + 63"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 40 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n1400 + 160 = 1560  \n1560 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 513", "Answer": "A: 734", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 10 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 169", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 10 = 930\n930 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70\n1200 + 70"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n8 + 3 = 11\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1138", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 4 = 34\n1100 + 34 = 1134\n1134 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1691", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 20 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 7 + 8 "}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 125", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n6 + 6 = 12\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1800", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 30 = 90\n5 + 5 = 10\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 70 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 399", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n1100 + 120 = 1220  \n1220 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 186", "Answer": "A: 418", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 80 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 8 = 418\n418 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 253", "Answer": "A: 416", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n300 + 110 = 410  \n410 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 206", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 6 = 36\n700 + 36 = 736\n736 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n6 + 3 = 9\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 244", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n5 + 40 = 45\n900 + 45 = 945\n945 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 392", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7 = 1067\n1067 - 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 536", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 30 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9\n1379 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 657", "Answer": "A: 862", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n5 + 50 = 55\n800 + 55 = 855\n855 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1642", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 80 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 324", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n18 + 80 = 98\n1400 + 98 = 1498\n1498 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 645", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "495 + 645:\n400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n5 + 5 = 10\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 80 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 221", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 20 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 177", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n5 + 70 = 75\n600 + 75 = 675\n675 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 560", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n5 + 2 = 7\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1669", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n3 + 60 = 63\n1600 + 63 = 1663\n1663 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1700", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1600 + 90 = 1690  \n1690 + 10  "}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 378", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 70 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 543", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 144", "Answer": "A: 722", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 391", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n90 + 90 = 180\n600 + 180 = 780\n780 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 6\n1026 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1752", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n15 + 30 = 45\n1700 + 45 = 1745\n1745 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9 = 1189\n1189 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 843", "Answer": "A: 1741", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n1600 + 130 = 1730  \n1730 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 103", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n1 + 3 = 4\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 90 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 7 + 1 = 1038"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 116", "Answer": "A: 719", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n3 + 16 = 19\n700 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 632", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 10 = 990\n990 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 686", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 9 + 6 = 1055"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n5 + 70 = 75\n1200 + 75 = 1275\n1275 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 437", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 426", "Answer": "A: 630", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n4 + 20 = 24\n600 + 24 = 624\n624 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 171", "Answer": "A: 340", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n\n60 + 70 = 130\n\n200 + 130 = 330\n\n330 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 0 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 505", "Answer": "A: 1374", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 0 = 60\n9 + 5 = 14\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 537", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1641", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 40 = 130\n8 + 3 = 11\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 460", "Answer": "A: 741", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1906", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n98 + 8 = 106  \n1800 + 106"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 233", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n15 + 30 = 45\n700 + 45 = 745\n745 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 242", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 393", "Answer": "A: 533", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n400 + 130 = 530  \n530 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 227", "Answer": "A: 350", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 20 = 40\n3 + 7 = 10\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 173", "Answer": "A: 502", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 70 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 9 = 499\n499 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 627", "Answer": "A: 774", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 7\n7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1837", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 40 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 266", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 60 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 166", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n9 + 6 = 15\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n2 + 7 = 9\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 266", "Answer": "A: 746", "Explanation": "480 + 200 = 680\n60 + 6 = 66\n680 + 66"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 172", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n600 + 160 = 760  \n760 + 4  \n760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 280", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 0 = 90\n7 + 5 = 12\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1930", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n1800 + 120 = 1920  \n1920 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 169", "Answer": "A: 322", "Explanation": "150 + 150 = 300\n3 + 10 = 13\n300 + 13 = 313\n313 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n24 + 20 = 44\n1400 + 44 = 1444\n1444 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 388", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n3 + 8 = 11  \n1000 + 160 = 1160  \n1160 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 501", "Answer": "A: 758", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 0 = 50\n7 + 1 = 8\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 664", "Answer": "A: 818", "Explanation": "150 + 600 = 750\n4 + 60 = 64\n750 + 64 = 814\n814 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 253", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 7 = 997\n997 - 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 148", "Answer": "A: 562", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n10 + 40 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 677", "Answer": "A: 1617", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 212", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 711", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 10 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 656", "Answer": "A: 1533", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n7 + 6 = 13  \n1400 + 120 = 1520  \n1520 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 367", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 672", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n6 + 70 = 76\n800 + 76 = 876\n876 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 40 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 284", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n9 + 4 = 13\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 848", "Answer": "A: 1608", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 40 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 256", "Answer": "A: 664", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n8 + 50 = 58\n600 + 58 = 658\n658 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n2 + 7 = 9\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 101", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 1 = 51\n600 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 329", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n10 + 20 = 30  \n8 + 9 = 17  \n1000 + 30 = 1030  \n1030 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 588 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 496", "Answer": "A: 1012", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n16 + 90 = 106\n900 + 106 = 1006\n1006 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 320", "Answer": "A: 604", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 20 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 874", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n3 + 70 = 73\n900 + 73 = 973\n973 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 389", "Answer": "A: 791", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n2 + 80 = 82\n700 + 82 = 782\n782 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 834", "Answer": "A: 1594", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 30 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 754", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 4 = 11\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 554", "Answer": "A: 1368", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 50 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 5 = 25\n900 + 25 = 925\n925 + 70 = 995\n995 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n76 + 90 = 166  \n1400 + 166 = 1566  \n1566 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 411", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 404", "Answer": "A: 568", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 4 = 64\n500 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1834", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n1700 + 130 = 1830  \n1830 + 4 = 1834"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 90 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 169", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9 \n9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 610 + 368", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 60 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n1000 + 160"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1598", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n5 + 3 = 8\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n6 + 1 = 7\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 457", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1778", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n60 + 10 = 70  \n4 + 4 = 8  \n1700 + 70 = 1770  \n1770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 280", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 80 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 505", "Answer": "A: 858", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 0 = 50\n3 + 5 = 8\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n11 + 70 = 81\n1400 + 81 = 1481\n1481 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n19 + 1 = 20\n1400 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n17 + 80 = 97\n1200 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1082", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n1 + 80 = 81\n1000 + 81 = 1081\n1081 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1576", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 30 = 70\n5 + 1 = 6\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 204", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 4 = 64\n500 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 235", "Answer": "A: 1138", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n3 + 30 = 33\n1100 + 33 = 1133\n1133 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 190", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n1000 + 150 = 1150  \n1150 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 906", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 6 = 36\n1400 + 36 = 1436\n1436 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 667", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n44 + 7 = 51  \n1000 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1794", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 20 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 308", "Answer": "A: 452", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 0 = 40\n4 + 8 = 12\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 783", "Answer": "A: 1774", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n90 + 80 = 170\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1649", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 60 = 140\n3 + 6 = 9\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 324", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 20 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 391", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 90 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1509", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 40 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n6 + 3 = 9\n1500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 393", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 90 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 597", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n1400 + 150 = 1550  \n1550 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 410", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 190", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 90 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 126", "Answer": "A: 752", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 20 = 40\n6 + 6 = 12\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 240", "Answer": "A: 734", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 40 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730 \n730 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n10 + 70 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 194", "Answer": "A: 570", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 90 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 104", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 4 = 1004\n1004 - 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 441", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 329", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 497 + 462", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 60 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 760", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 60 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 287", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n800 + 170 = 970  \n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1896", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 50 = 90\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1514", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 50 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n45 + 0 = 45\n1000 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 343", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n9 + 3 = 12\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 152", "Answer": "A: 352", "Explanation": "200 + 150 = 350\n350 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1493", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 6 = 13\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 347", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 7 = 47\n47 + 7 = 54\n1000 + 54 = 1054\n1054 + 42"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 953 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1763", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 10 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 804", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n50 + 4 = 54  \n900 + 54  \n900 + 54 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 268", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 573", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 3 = 8\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1459", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n10 + 40 = 50  \n1400 + 50 = 1450  \n1450 + 9 = 1459  "}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 439", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 9 = 39\n1200 + 39 = 1239\n1239 + 32"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 485", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 457", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n90 + 50 = 140\n7 + 7 = 14\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1350", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n4 + 40 = 44\n1300 + 44 = 1344\n1344 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 243", "Answer": "A: 483", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 40 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n8 + 8 = 16\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 402", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 2 = 52\n1000 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 448", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n5 + 8 = 13\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 372", "Answer": "A: 541", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 70 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 11 = 541"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 173", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 70 = 160\n4 + 3 = 7\n200 + 160 = 360\n360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1818", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 40 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 7 + 1 = 1818"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n6 + 7 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 200", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40\n1100 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 60 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 198", "Answer": "A: 730", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 90 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 10 = 730\n730 - 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 456", "Answer": "A: 635", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n500 + 120 = 620  \n620 + 9  \n620 + 6  \n620 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n9 + 90 = 99\n1200 + 99 = 1299\n1299 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 20 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 200", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n38 + 0 = 38\n1000 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 229", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n1 + 20 = 21\n500 + 21 = 521\n521 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 192", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n1000 + 120 = 1120  \n1120 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 101", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "786 + 100 = 886\n886 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 329", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n3 + 20 = 23\n700 + 23 = 723\n723 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 760", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n6 + 60 = 66\n800 + 66"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1610", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n90 + 10 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 208 + 407", "Answer": "A: 615", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n8 + 7 = 15\n600 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 609", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 9 = 29\n800 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 447", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 219", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 10 = 20\n600 + 20 = 620\n620 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 40 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 523", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 9 + 3 = 892"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1467", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 0 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 307", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 7 = 97\n1100 + 97 = 1197\n1197 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n1300 + 120 = 1420  \n1420 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 0 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3 + 9 = 1102"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 30 = 90\n9 + 8 = 17\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 369", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n7 + 60 = 67  \n700 + 67 = 767  \n767 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 262", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n90 + 60 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 4\n450 + 2\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1870", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 90 = 170\n1700 + 170 = 1870"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 667", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 5\n845 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1837", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 40 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1427", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7 = 1427\n1427 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1358", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1628", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 1 = 21\n1600 + 21 = 1621\n1621 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1629", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 413", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n100 + 1100 = 1200\n5 + 9 = 14\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 448", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 399", "Answer": "A: 505", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n6 + 99 = 105\n400 + 105 = 505"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 143", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 40 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 4 = 524\n524 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 128", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n52 + 20 = 72\n1000 + 72 = 1072\n1072 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9 = 1199\n1199 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1753", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 60 = 140\n6 + 7 = 13\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 473", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 70 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 10 = 770"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1368", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n2 + 9 = 11\n1320 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 152", "Answer": "A: 661", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n9 + 50 = 59\n600 + 59 = 659\n659 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n5 + 2 = 7\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 30 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1604", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n2 + 2 = 4\n1600 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 445", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 30 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n3 + 9 = 12  \n1000 + 140 = 1140  \n1140 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 316", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 10 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 1\n600 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n70 + 40 = 110\n6 + 4 = 10\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 176", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 509", "Answer": "A: 793", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n84 + 9 = 93\n700 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 10 = 50\n2 + 5 = 7\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 191", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n15 + 90 = 105  \n900 + 105 = 1005  \n1005 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 136", "Answer": "A: 500", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 30 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 234", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n5 + 4 = 9\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1210", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1868", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 10 = 60\n5 + 3 = 8\n1800 + 60 = 1860\n1860 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 294", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n800 + 130 = 930  \n930 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 127", "Answer": "A: 323", "Explanation": "100 + 90 = 190\n6 + 20 = 26\n190 + 26 = 216\n216 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1848", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n99 + 49 = 148  \n1700 + 148 = 1848"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1643", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 50 = 130\n4 + 9 = 13\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1666", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500 \n70 + 80 = 150 \n1500 + 150 = 1650 \n1650 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 333", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 347 + 457", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 50 = 90\n7 + 7 = 14\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1667", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n3 + 4 = 7\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n50 + 10 = 60  \n7 + 5 = 12  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 798", "Answer": "A: 1750", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 90 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 10 = 1750"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 334", "Answer": "A: 629", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 30 = 120\n5 + 4 = 9\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 483", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 80 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 491", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 90 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 441", "Answer": "A: 586", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n5 + 1 = 6  \n500 + 80 = 580  \n580 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 20 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 481", "Answer": "A: 777", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n600 + 170 = 770  \n770 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1757", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 10 = 40\n9 + 8 = 17\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1287", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 1 = 31\n1100 + 31 = 1131\n1131 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 503", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 0 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 705", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n40 + 5 = 45  \n800 + 45 = 845  \n845 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 5 = 12\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 223", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 191", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 90 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1012", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 280", "Answer": "A: 827", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 80 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 156", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 6 = 13\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 330", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1839", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 10 = 30\n5 + 4 = 9\n1800 + 30 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 510", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n98 + 10 = 108\n800 + 108"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n55 + 70 = 125\n1300 + 125 = 1425\n1425 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 587", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n600 + 170 = 770  \n770 + 10 = 780  \n780 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 183", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n19 + 80 = 99  \n700 + 99 = 799  \n799 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n2 + 3 = 5\n1100 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 288 + 415", "Answer": "A: 703", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 10 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 197", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n900 + 130 = 1030  \n1030 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 382", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n2 + 80 = 82\n700 + 82 = 782\n782 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 393", "Answer": "A: 609", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 90 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 6 = 606\n606 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 746", "Answer": "A: 955", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n9 + 40 = 49\n900 + 49 = 949\n949 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1493", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 743", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n6 + 40 = 46\n800 + 46 = 846\n846 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 418 + 265", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 60 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 756", "Answer": "A: 903", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 641", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 1 = 6\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 623", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n5 + 3 = 8\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1393", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 10 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 368", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 60 = 70\n5 + 8 = 13\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n2 + 5 = 7\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 275", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 136", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1354", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 2 + 2 = 1354"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 174", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1869", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 70 = 160\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 730", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1542", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 10 = 40\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 682", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1943", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 50 = 130\n9 + 4 = 13\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 331", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 491", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1354", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 128", "Answer": "A: 807", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 20 = 90\n9 + 8 = 17\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1600", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 30 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 590", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1842", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n1700 + 130 = 1830  \n1830 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1170", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 213", "Answer": "A: 441", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 10 = 30\n400 + 30 = 430\n430 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 225 + 348", "Answer": "A: 573", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 40 = 60\n5 + 8 = 13\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n10 + 40 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 5 = 75\n1500 + 75 = 1575\n1575 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 636", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 30 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 418 + 185", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n18 + 80 = 98\n500 + 98 = 598\n598 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 414", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 10 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 2 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1730", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 70 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 614", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n2 + 14 = 16\n1200 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1391", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 50 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 166", "Answer": "A: 881", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n15 + 60 = 75\n800 + 75 = 875\n875 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 593", "Answer": "A: 715", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 106", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 6 = 66\n900 + 66 = 966\n966 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1501", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 0 = 90\n8 + 3 = 11\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n6 + 60 = 66\n1200 + 66 = 1266\n1266 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1631", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 80 = 120\n2 + 9 = 11\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 128", "Answer": "A: 614", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 20 = 100\n6 + 8 = 14\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1319", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 266", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 289", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 108 + 889", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n8 + 80 = 88\n900 + 88 = 988\n988 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 978", "Answer": "A: 1572", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n4 + 8 = 12\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 7\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 371", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 9 = 1019  \n1019 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 255", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 50 = 100\n2 + 5 = 7\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 0 = 40\n5 + 9 = 14\n1500 + 40 = 1540\n1540 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n4 + 3 = 7\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n38 + 1 = 39\n1000 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9\n1100 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 590", "Answer": "A: 1547", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 90 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 358", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n900 + 130 = 1030  \n1030 + 9 = 1039"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 723", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n4 + 20 = 24\n900 + 24 = 924\n924 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 401", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 0 = 40\n3 + 1 = 4\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 167", "Answer": "A: 316", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 60 = 100\n9 + 7 = 16\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 583", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n4 + 3 = 7\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 237", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n19 + 30 = 49\n400 + 49 = 449\n449 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 156", "Answer": "A: 305", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n9 + 6 = 15  \n200 + 90 = 290  \n290 + 15  "}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 1 = 91\n1100 + 91 = 1191\n1191 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 260", "Answer": "A: 1170", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 494", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 90 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1860", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n1 + 50 = 51\n1800 + 51 = 1851\n1851 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n8 + 2 = 10\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 267 + 612", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 10 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 370", "Answer": "A: 552", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 70 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 126", "Answer": "A: 838", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n12 + 20 = 32\n800 + 32 = 832\n832 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 415", "Answer": "A: 552", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 10 = 40\n7 + 5 = 12\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 655", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n17 + 4 = 21\n1100 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 693", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n700 + 160 = 860  \n860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 296", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 90 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 8 = 68\n1400 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 558", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 10 = 900"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1567", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 291", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n40 + 90 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 6 = 936"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1826", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 30 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1775", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n1 + 4 = 5  \n1600 + 170 = 1770  \n1770 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1671", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 10 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n1200 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n1000 + 120 = 1120  \n1120 + 4  \n1124 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 450", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 479", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n2 + 70 = 72\n1000 + 72 = 1072\n1072 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 504", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 4 = 54\n1400 + 54 = 1454\n1454 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 607", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 7 = 57\n800 + 57"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 508", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 0 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 10 = 960"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1841", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n50 + 80 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 190", "Answer": "A: 486", "Explanation": "200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 264", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 60 = 90\n5 + 4 = 9\n600 + 90 = 690 \n690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 431 + 487", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1693", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 70 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 70 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 298", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n60 + 90 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1082", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 70 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n7 + 40 = 47\n1300 + 47 = 1347\n1347 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1844", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n1700 + 130 = 1830  \n1830 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n5 + 9 = 14\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 3 = 43\n1300 + 43 = 1343\n1343 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 244", "Answer": "A: 414", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n300 + 110 = 410  \n410 + 4 = 414"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1447", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 60 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 534", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n2 + 4 = 6\n920 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 559", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 184", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5 + 4\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n6 + 2 = 8\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 295", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 839", "Answer": "A: 1528", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 30 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 112", "Answer": "A: 661", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 10 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 20 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 848", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 352", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1719", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 60 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 651", "Answer": "A: 882", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 177", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1 + 7 = 8\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n6 + 8 = 14\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 115", "Answer": "A: 864", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9\n850 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230 \n1230 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 397", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 90 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 344", "Answer": "A: 701", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7\n690 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1540", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n2 + 30 = 32\n1500 + 32 = 1532\n1532 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 592", "Answer": "A: 935", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 90 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 5 = 935\n935 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n14 + 50 = 64  \n1400 + 64 = 1464  \n1464 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 163", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1800", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 20 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 156", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 90 = 180\n1100 + 180 = 1280\n1280 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 497", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 171", "Answer": "A: 460", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 70 = 150\n300 + 150 = 450\n450 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n10 + 60 = 70\n70 + 5 = 75\n1500 + 75 = 1575\n1575 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 30 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 386", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 8 = 958\n958"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 464", "Answer": "A: 901", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 60 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 420", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 5 = 495\n400 + 20 = 420\n490 + 420 = 910\n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 102", "Answer": "A: 274", "Explanation": "100 + 70 = 170\n2 + 102 = 104\n170 + 104"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 436", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n19 + 50 = 69\n1200 + 69"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1379", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 233", "Answer": "A: 576", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 30 = 70\n3 + 3 = 6\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n19 + 10 = 29\n1000 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 601", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 1 = 71\n700 + 71"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 309", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 9 = 39\n500 + 39 = 539\n539 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 399", "Answer": "A: 513", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 90 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 9\n500 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1557", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1400 + 150 = 1550  \n1550 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 20 = 50\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 445", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n7 + 5 = 12\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 983 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 20 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 3\n1603 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 108", "Answer": "A: 382", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 8 = 78\n300 + 78 = 378\n378 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 242", "Answer": "A: 901", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 852", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n16 + 50 = 66\n900 + 66 = 966\n966 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 495", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3 + 5 = 948"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 496", "Answer": "A: 720", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 747", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 691", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n20 + 90 = 110  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 393", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 10 = 1240"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 583", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 80 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 40 = 60\n1000 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 591", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6 = 1206\n1206 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 90 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 4 = 1324\n1324 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1280", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n19 + 60 = 79\n1200 + 79 = 1279\n1279 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 521", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1287", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n9 + 8 = 17\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 506", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n40 + 6 = 46\n700 + 46 = 746\n746 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 307", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "180 + 300 = 480\n1 + 7 = 8\n480 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 80 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 375", "Answer": "A: 650", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 5 = 10\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 377", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 70 = 160\n5 + 7 = 12\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1000 + 100 = 1100  \n1 + 8 = 9  \n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n15 + 30 = 45  \n1100 + 45 = 1145  \n1145 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n900 + 150 = 1050  \n1050 + 4 + 9 = 1063"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 217", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n4 + 7 = 11\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 70 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 234", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n2 + 4 = 6\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 246", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n2 + 6 = 8\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 325", "Answer": "A: 611", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 20 = 100\n6 + 5 = 11\n\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 728 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1635", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 7 = 27\n1600 + 27 = 1627\n1627 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 279", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n18 + 70 = 88\n800 + 88 = 888\n888 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 132", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n3 + 2 = 5  \n1000 + 70 = 1070  \n1070 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 183", "Answer": "A: 788", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n5 + 80 = 85\n700 + 85 = 785\n785 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 490", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 6 = 46\n1000 + 46 = 1046\n1046 + 90 "}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 602", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 2 = 52\n1300 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 728", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n20 + 20 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 513", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1 + 3 = 4\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 223", "Answer": "A: 523", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n23 \n500 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 351", "Answer": "A: 479", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 8 = 478\n478 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 913", "Answer": "A: 1507", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 10 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 129", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 20 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1713", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 50 = 100\n7 + 6 = 13\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 583", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 186", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n5 + 6 = 11\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 216", "Answer": "A: 786", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 225", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 20 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3\n1013 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 40 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 476", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 241", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 40 = 60\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 6 = 366\n366 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 190", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n8 + 90 = 98\n700 + 98 "}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1200", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 103", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 3 = 43\n700 + 43 = 743\n743 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 110", "Answer": "A: 238", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n28 + 10 = 38\n200 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 488", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 80 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 445", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n7 + 40 = 47\n900 + 47 = 947\n947 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 289", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 388", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n60 + 80 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 205", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 5 = 25\n900 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 325", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n6 + 20 = 26\n800 + 26 = 826\n826 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 474", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 4 = 9\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 413", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n4 + 3 = 7\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 618", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 18 = 38\n700 + 38 = 738\n738 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 216", "Answer": "A: 837", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 10 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 659", "Answer": "A: 773", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n14 + 50 = 64\n700 + 64 = 764\n764 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n7 + 8 = 15\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 313", "Answer": "A: 526", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n13 + 13 = 26\n500 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 640", "Answer": "A: 810", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1695", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n94 + 1 = 95  \n1600 + 95"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n70 + 30 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1803", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n7 + 90 = 97\n1700 + 97 = 1797\n1797 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n8 + 10 = 18\n1400 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 50 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1 + 4 = 5\n1460 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1371", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 40 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 590", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n1000 + 160 = 1160  \n1160 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 606", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 6 = 66\n1300 + 66 = 1366\n1366 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n2 + 30 = 32  \n1300 + 32 = 1332  \n1332 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 360", "Answer": "A: 888", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 482", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 698", "Answer": "A: 1643", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n1500 + 130 = 1630  \n1630 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1453", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 403", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 3 = 23\n800 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 60 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 160", "Answer": "A: 443", "Explanation": "200 + 80 = 280  \n280 + 3 = 283  \n100 + 60 = 160  \n280 + 160 = 440  \n440 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 314", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n3 + 4 = 7\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1686", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 0 = 80\n5 + 1 = 6\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 10 = 1390"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 539", "Answer": "A: 703", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n600 + 90 = 690  \n690 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1 + 4 = 5\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 15 = 45\n1400 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 390", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n7 + 70 = 77\n1100 + 77 = 1177\n1177 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 452", "Answer": "A: 704", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 50 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 468", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 3 = 83\n1000 + 83"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 516", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 10 = 30\n1 + 6 = 7\n1100 + 30 = 1130\n1130 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 101", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "893 + 100 = 993\n993 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 173", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n2 + 70 = 72\n900 + 72 = 972\n972 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1825", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n6 + 19 = 25\n1800 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 406", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 6 = 96\n700 + 96 = 796\n796 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 90 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1702", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 30 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 194", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 90 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 4 \n710 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n6 + 50 = 56\n1400 + 56 = 1456\n1456 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 364", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n9 + 7 = 16\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n1 + 70 = 71\n1100 + 71 = 1171\n1171 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 340", "Answer": "A: 623", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n500 + 120 = 620  \n620 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n\n11 + 16 = 27\n\n1000 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 377", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n2 + 70 = 72\n800 + 72 = 872\n872 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 392", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n7 + 2 = 9  \n600 + 180 = 780  \n780 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 229", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n6 + 9 = 15\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10 = 1100"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 398", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 352", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 223", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n11 + 20 = 31\n1000 + 31 = 1031\n1031 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 297", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 90 = 180\n600 + 180 = 780\n780 + 5\n785 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 392", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 550", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n1 + 70 = 71\n1200 + 71"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n1300 + 110 = 1410  \n1410 + 10 = 1420"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n4 + 30 = 34  \n1200 + 34 = 1234  \n1234 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 157", "Answer": "A: 459", "Explanation": "300 + 150 = 450\n2 + 7 = 9\n450 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 425", "Answer": "A: 577", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 5 = 7\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 505", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 5 = 25\n700 + 25 = 725\n725 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 232", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 30 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 8 = 618\n618 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 391", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n8 + 90 = 98\n800 + 98 = 898\n898 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1871", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 40 = 60\n7 + 4 = 11\n1800 + 60 = 1860\n1860 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 286", "Answer": "A: 586", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n80 + 6 = 86  \n500 + 86"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 844", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n4 + 4 = 8  \n1600 + 70 = 1670  \n1670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 510", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 632", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 286", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 6 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 167", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n9 + 60 = 69\n800 + 69 = 869\n869 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n2 + 7 = 9\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 617", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "160 + 600 = 760\n3 + 17 = 20\n760 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 787", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 9 = 949  \n949 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n19 + 30 = 49\n1400 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 50 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 932 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1627", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n1500 + 120 = 1620  \n1620 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 579", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n8 + 70 = 78\n1400 + 78 = 1478\n1478 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n5 + 50 = 55\n1400 + 55 = 1455\n1455 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 348", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 255", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 80 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 7\n1140 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 217", "Answer": "A: 821", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n4 + 10 = 14\n800 + 14 = 814\n814 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 162", "Answer": "A: 327", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 60 = 120\n5 + 2 = 7\n200 + 120 = 320\n320 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 = 1193"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 171", "Answer": "A: 670", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 10 = 670"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1439", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n2 + 2 = 4\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 906", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n7 + 6 = 13\n1100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 307", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n19 + 7 = 26  \n1100 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 326", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 20 = 80\n3 + 6 = 9\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 145", "Answer": "A: 503", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 40 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1709", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n3 + 6 = 9\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 407", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 7 = 37\n500 + 37 = 537\n537 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 481", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1459", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n10 + 40 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 289", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 80 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 0 = 60\n8 + 9 = 17\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 848", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 40 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 518", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 566", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 773", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n6 + 70 = 76\n900 + 76 = 976\n976 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n2 + 5 = 7\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n9 + 6 = 15\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 190", "Answer": "A: 300", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 90 = 100\n200 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 318", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 349", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 40 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 145", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 793", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 10 = 930"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 572", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 345", "Answer": "A: 788", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 5 = 8\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 493", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 146", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 536", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n9 + 6 = 15\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 70 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 10 = 1130"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 9 = 89\n900 + 89 = 989\n989 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 50 = 80\n4 + 2 = 6\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 667 + 138", "Answer": "A: 805", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 704", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 4 = 54\n900 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 701 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n1 + 40 = 41\n1100 + 41 = 1141\n1141 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1921", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 90 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n99 + 11 = 110\n1300 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 234", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n30 + 30 = 60  \n500 + 60 = 560  \n560 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1877", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 0 = 70\n4 + 3 = 7\n1800 + 70 = 1870\n1870 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 211", "Answer": "A: 773", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 10 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 2 + 1 = 773"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1523", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 181", "Answer": "A: 287", "Explanation": "100 + 80 = 180\n6 + 1 = 7\n180 + 7 = 187\n187 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 163", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n19 + 60 = 79\n700 + 79 = 779\n779 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 419", "Answer": "A: 554", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 10 = 40\n5 + 9 = 14\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 30 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 285", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 394 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 484", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n2 + 80 = 82\n1000 + 82 = 1082\n1082 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 590 + 314", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n900 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1428", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 30 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 8 = 1428"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 811", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n3 + 99 = 102  \n900 + 102 = 1002  "}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n12 + 70 = 82\n1000 + 82 = 1082\n1082 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n2 + 9 = 11\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 844", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n11 + 90 = 101\n1100 + 101 = 1201\n1201 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 330", "Answer": "A: 836", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n6 + 30 = 36\n800 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 447 + 442", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n7 + 2 = 9\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 749", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 40 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1716", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n10 + 90 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 16 = 1716"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n4 + 70 = 74\n1200 + 74 = 1274\n1274 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 146", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n1300 + 90 = 1390  \n1390 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 749", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n5 + 40 = 45\n900 + 45 = 945\n945 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 20 = 70\n4 + 4 = 8\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 842", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 6 = 76\n1000 + 76 = 1076\n1076 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 1 = 91\n1100 + 91 = 1191\n1191 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1379", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n15 + 60 = 75  \n1300 + 75 = 1375  \n1375 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n6 + 60 = 66\n1100 + 66 = 1166\n1166 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n3 + 4 = 7\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 159", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n600 + 140 = 740  \n740 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 311", "Answer": "A: 529", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 10 = 20\n500 + 20 = 520\n520 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 316", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 6 = 846\n846 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n24\n1400 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 583", "Answer": "A: 1227", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n15 + 6 = 21\n1200 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 305", "Answer": "A: 686", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 0 = 80\n1 + 5 = 6\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1709", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 70 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n6 + 3 = 9\n1700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n10 + 50 = 60  \n7 + 6 = 13  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 617", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 10 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 616 + 260", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n16 + 60 = 76\n800 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 295", "Answer": "A: 421", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 90 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 6 = 416\n416 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1290", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 10 = 1290"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n9 + 10 = 19\n1200 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 109", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 9 = 29\n900 + 29 = 929\n929 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 469", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 60 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 10 = 860"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 339", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 30 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 187", "Answer": "A: 825", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n700 + 110 = 810  \n810 + 5 = 815  \n815 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 259", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1170", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100   \n60 + 0 = 60   \n2 + 8 = 10    \n1100 + 60 = 1160  \n1160 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 20 = 50\n7 + 8 = 15\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1168", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 7 = 67\n1100 + 67 = 1167\n1167 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 361", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1792", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 243", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 521", "Answer": "A: 1225", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n4 + 20 = 24\n1200 + 24 = 1224\n1224 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 200", "Answer": "A: 411", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n400 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1691", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 30 = 80\n6 + 5 = 11\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1379", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 126", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 20 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 10 = 820\n820 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 1 = 41\n1400 + 41 = 1441\n1441 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 218", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 9 = 1179\n1179 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 563", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3 = 813\n813 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 5 \n1480 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 398", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n19 + 90 = 109\n800 + 109 = 909\n909 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1838", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 40 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 7 + 1 = 1838"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n40 + 80 = 120\n9 + 2 = 11\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 20 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 247", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 947 + 504", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 4 = 44\n1400 + 44 = 1444\n1444 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n6 + 30 = 36\n1000 + 36 = 1036\n1036 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 610", "Answer": "A: 875", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 10 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 2 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 623", "Answer": "A: 786", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 180", "Answer": "A: 549", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 80 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1508", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 80 = 100\n3 + 5 = 8\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 728", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 20 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 295", "Answer": "A: 612", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n10 + 90 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n7 + 5 = 12\n600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1722", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 60 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 7 + 5 = 1710 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 10 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 480", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 80 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 158", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 141", "Answer": "A: 309", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n8 + 1 = 9  \n200 + 100 = 300  \n300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 721", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 30 = 110\n5 + 5 = 10\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 720", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n18 + 20 = 38\n900 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n6 + 6 = 12\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 80 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 219", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n9 + 5 = 14\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 4 + 3\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 579", "Answer": "A: 1543", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 70 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 4 \n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n19 + 20 = 39\n1200 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 656", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 100", "Answer": "A: 363", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 0 = 60\n3 + 0 = 3\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 209", "Answer": "A: 482", "Explanation": "200 + 70 = 270  \n270 + 3 = 273  \n270 + 9 = 279  \n279 + 200"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 456", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n6 + 50 = 56\n600 + 56 = 656\n656 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 10 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9\n1080 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 448", "Answer": "A: 619", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 128", "Answer": "A: 500", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 20 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 10 = 500\n500 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 497", "Answer": "A: 817", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 156", "Answer": "A: 496", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n400 + 90 = 490  \n490 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 70 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 561", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 60 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1405", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 10 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1350", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 7 = 10\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1696", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n17 + 70 = 87  \n1600 + 87 = 1687  \n1687 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 317 + 525", "Answer": "A: 842", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 20 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 674", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n8 + 4 = 12\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 346", "Answer": "A: 614", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 40 = 100\n8 + 6 = 14\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1909", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 30 = 100\n1800 + 100 = 1900\n1900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 233", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 107", "Answer": "A: 405", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n98 + 7 = 105\n300 + 105"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 313", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1807", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 60 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 211", "Answer": "A: 880", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n60 + 10 = 70  \n800 + 70 = 870  \n870 + 1 = 871  \n871 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 362", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 156", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n56\n1000 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1324", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 235", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1877", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 90 = 170\n1700 + 170 = 1870\n1870 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 610", "Answer": "A: 729", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 10 = 20\n700 + 20 = 720\n720 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 146", "Answer": "A: 345", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n200 + 130 = 330\n9 + 6 = 15  \n330 + 15  "}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 499", "Answer": "A: 757", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 90 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 473", "Answer": "A: 955", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 70 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 306", "Answer": "A: 733", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 6 = 26\n700 + 26 = 726\n726 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n1300 + 120 = 1420  \n1420 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n70 + 20 = 90  \n1300 + 90 = 1390  \n1390 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n19 + 20 = 39\n1500 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1874", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 70 = 160\n7 + 7 = 14\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 8 = 28\n1000 + 28 = 1028\n1028 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1723", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 90 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 145", "Answer": "A: 288", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 5 = 8\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 20 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n3 + 8 = 11\n1700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1250", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n10 + 50 = 60  \n1 + 7 = 8  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 349 + 358", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 50 = 90\n9 + 8 = 17\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 0 = 50\n7 + 1 = 8\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 403", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n90 + 0 = 90  \n3 + 3 = 6  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1372", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 50 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 248", "Answer": "A: 482", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 40 = 70\n4 + 8 = 12\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 294", "Answer": "A: 405", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n10 + 90 = 100\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 4 = 404\n404 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 20 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 375", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4\n1200 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 434", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1672", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n11 + 60 = 71\n1600 + 71 = 1671\n1671 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 153", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 600", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n51 + 0 = 51\n800 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 849", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n11 + 40 = 51\n900 + 51 = 951\n951 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 138", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 226", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n19 + 20 = 39\n700 + 39 = 739\n739 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n11 + 60 = 71\n1000 + 71"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 90 = 180\n3 + 9 = 12\n1000 + 180 = 1180\n1180 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 446", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 40 = 50\n9 + 6 = 15\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1467", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 20 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 8\n1458 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 222", "Answer": "A: 907", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n5 + 2 = 7\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 616", "Answer": "A: 775", "Explanation": "150 + 600 = 750\n9 + 6 = 15\n750 + 15 = 765\n765 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 415 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1280", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 322", "Answer": "A: 704", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 267", "Answer": "A: 444", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 60 = 130\n7 + 7 = 14\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 410", "Answer": "A: 882", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 410", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 184", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n1000 + 150 = 1150  \n1150 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n1 + 5 = 6\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 90 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 718", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 344", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n9 + 4 = 13\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 303", "Answer": "A: 414", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n11 + 3 = 14\n400 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 8 + 8 = 1006  "}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 733", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 387", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n50 + 80 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1652", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1620", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1498", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 90 = 180\n1300 + 180 = 1480\n1480 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 195", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 7 = 47\n1100 + 47 = 1147\n1147 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n28 + 20 = 48\n1100 + 48 = 1148\n1148 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 595", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 90 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6 = 1146\n1146 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 608", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 8 = 38\n800 + 38 = 838\n838 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1863", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n10 + 40 = 50\n1800 + 50 = 1850\n1850 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 605", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 0 = 30\n3 + 5 = 8\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 792", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1168", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100  \n9 + 50 = 59  \n1100 + 59 = 1159  \n1159 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 215", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n2 + 5 = 7\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1632", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 2 = 72\n1500 + 72 = 1572\n1572 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 355", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 50 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 282", "Answer": "A: 757", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 7 = 757"}
{"Question": "Q: 569 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1633", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 10 = 30\n1600 + 30 = 1630\n1630 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n5 + 80 = 85\n1000 + 85 = 1085\n1085 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 633 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1584", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 50 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 50 = 110\n1600 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 347", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n6 + 7 = 13\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 404", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 4 = 54\n1100 + 54 = 1154\n1154 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 235", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n3 + 5 = 8\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 402", "Answer": "A: 624", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n20 + 0 = 20  \n2 + 2 = 4  \n600 + 20 = 620  \n620 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 176 + 484", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 80 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 6 = 656\n656 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1419", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1344", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 1 = 1344"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 112", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 2 = 9\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n1 + 25 = 26\n1000 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 439", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 30 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n4 + 9 = 13\n1000 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 492", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 90 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 573", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 70 = 100\n6 + 3 = 9\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 113", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 10 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n5 + 6 = 11\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n9 + 90 = 99\n1400 + 99 = 1499\n1499 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 372", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 10 = 870"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 242", "Answer": "A: 507", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 40 = 100\n5 + 2 = 7\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1628", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n7 + 20 = 27\n1600 + 27 = 1627\n1627 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 382", "Answer": "A: 520", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 80 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 10 = 520"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 588", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n18 + 80 = 98\n1400 + 98 = 1498\n1498 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 432", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 259", "Answer": "A: 394", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 50 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 147", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n4 + 7 = 11\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n1 + 70 = 71\n1100 + 71 = 1171\n1171 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 466", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 275", "Answer": "A: 495", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 70 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 293", "Answer": "A: 577", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n80 + 90 = 170\n4 + 3 = 7\n400 + 170 = 570\n570 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 603", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n27 + 3 = 30\n\n900 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 373", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 113", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 279", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 70 = 140\n7 + 9 = 16\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 309", "Answer": "A: 648", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 0 = 30\n9 + 9 = 18\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100  \n15 + 50 = 65  \n1100 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 378", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1 + 8 = 9\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 344", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 4 = 9\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 357", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1887", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n27 + 60 = 87  \n1800 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 50 = 70\n5 + 7 = 12\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 154", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n60 + 50 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 9  \n1110 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 584", "Answer": "A: 758", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 799 + 312", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n99 + 12 = 111\n1000 + 111"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 386", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 80 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 920", "Answer": "A: 1848", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n28 + 20 = 48\n1800 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 693 + 187", "Answer": "A: 880", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 10 = 880\n880 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 247", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 170", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n75 + 70 = 145\n800 + 145"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 7 = 27\n27 + 0 = 27\n1300 + 27 = 1327\n1327 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 415 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n15 + 16 = 31\n1200 + 31"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n1 + 50 = 51\n1000 + 51 = 1051\n1051 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 230", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n19 + 30 = 49\n600 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n8 + 6 = 14\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 174", "Answer": "A: 475", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n1 + 70 = 71\n400 + 71 = 471\n471 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "950 + 400 = 1350\n50 + 60 = 110\n1350 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 217", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 106", "Answer": "A: 624", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n18 + 6 = 24\n600 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1511", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 80 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 3 \n1500 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 649", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 267", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 5\n1045 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 368", "Answer": "A: 765", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n600 + 150 = 750  \n750 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 374", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1344", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n4 + 40 = 44\n1300 + 44"}
{"Question": "Q: 418 + 743", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n3 + 70 = 73\n1100 + 73 = 1173\n1173 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1718", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 50 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 127", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 20 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 180", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 722 + 249", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 40 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1\n1021 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 268", "Answer": "A: 724", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 60 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n5 + 70 = 75\n1100 + 75 = 1175\n1175 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1416", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 20 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 7\n1407 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 40 = 90\n3 + 6 = 9\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n5 + 60 = 65\n1300 + 65 = 1365\n1365 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 177", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 7 = 14\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 227", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1923", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 50 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1254", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n9 + 40 = 49\n1200 + 49 = 1249\n1249 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 477", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n10 + 70 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8 = 1288"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 204", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 69\n1200 + 60 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 499", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 5\n835 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 60 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n7 + 9 = 16\n1340 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 503", "Answer": "A: 798", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n90 + 0 = 90  \n5 + 3 = 8  \n700 + 90 = 790  \n790 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 621", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n9 + 90 = 99\n1300 + 99 = 1399\n1399 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1547", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n1400 + 110 = 1510  \n1510 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n70 + 20 = 90\n3 + 4 = 7\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 303", "Answer": "A: 825", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n20 + 3 = 23\n800 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 602", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 2 = 32\n1200 + 32 = 1232\n1232 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1594", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n9 + 5 = 14  \n1500 + 80 = 1580  \n1580 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 262", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 60 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 533", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 30 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n9 + 6 = 15\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 345", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n2 + 5 = 7\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 140", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n9 + 40 = 49\n900 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 230", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n600 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 0 = 7\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 926", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 330", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n21 + 30 = 51\n1200 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 308", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n60 + 0 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 279", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n1000 + 140 = 1140  \n1140 + 9  \n1140 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 822", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n900 + 22 = 922"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 5 = 55\n1300 + 55 = 1355\n1355 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 178", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 70 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1668", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n10 + 50 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n70 + 20 = 90  \n6 + 7 = 13  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6\n1150 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 326", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1370", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n1200 + 160 = 1360   \n1360 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 588 + 369", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 60 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 9 \n8"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 124", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1567", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n2 + 5 = 7\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1527", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n20 + 7 = 27\n1500 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 412", "Answer": "A: 540", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 162", "Answer": "A: 264", "Explanation": "100 + 160 = 260\n2 + 2 = 4\n260 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 768", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1384", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 60 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 956", "Answer": "A: 1827", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 50 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 7 = 1827\n1827 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1766", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 90 = 160\n4 + 2 = 6\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 639", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n70 + 9 = 79\n900 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 733 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 539 + 394", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 316", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 10 = 20\n2 + 6 = 8\n800 + 20 = 820\n820 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 101", "Answer": "A: 694", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n93 + 1 = 94\n600 + 94"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 161", "Answer": "A: 355", "Explanation": "190 + 160 = 350\n4 + 1 = 5\n350 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 108", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n2 + 8 = 10  \n1000 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 151", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n500 + 140 = 640  \n640 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1655", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 80 = 150\n4 + 1 = 5\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 969 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 60 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 102", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 2 = 32\n500 + 32 = 532\n532 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 276", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 70 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 5\n1015 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 502", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 2 = 22\n1200 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 20 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 378", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 231", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n10 + 30 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 350", "Answer": "A: 600", "Explanation": "250 + 300 = 550\n550 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 128", "Answer": "A: 1096", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 487", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9 = 919"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 442", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n5 + 2 = 7\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 236", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 30 = 100\n2 + 6 = 8\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 109", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n9 + 9 = 18\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1823", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 40 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 3 "}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 303", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n48 + 3 = 51\n800 + 51"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n1 + 80 = 81  \n1200 + 81 = 1281  \n1281 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 12 = 62\n1300 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1724", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 70 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 156", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n44 + 50 = 94\n800 + 94 = 894\n894 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 401", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n3 + 1 = 4\n500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 633", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 5 + 3 = 808"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1299", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 5 \n1290 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1552", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n6 + 6 = 12\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 226", "Answer": "A: 462", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 20 = 50\n6 + 6 = 12\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 324", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 20 = 70\n5 + 4 = 9\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 659", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n6 + 50 = 56\n900 + 56 = 956\n956 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n8\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1633", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n50 + 70 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 4 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 188", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 80 = 160\n4 + 8 = 12\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 476", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n2 + 6 = 8  \n1300 + 140 = 1440  \n1440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 80 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n3 + 30 = 33\n1300 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 121 + 116", "Answer": "A: 237", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 10 = 30\n1 + 6 = 7\n200 + 30 = 230\n230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 533", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n7 + 30 = 37\n1300 + 37 = 1337\n1337 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 652", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 50 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 785", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 80 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 589", "Answer": "A: 713", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 80 = 100\n4 + 9 = 13\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 70 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 428", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 9 = 79\n1200 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 773", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 70 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 11 = 961"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 30 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 183", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1493", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n6 + 7 = 13\n1480 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1416", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 20 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 415", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n9 + 15 = 24\n500 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 341", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n6 + 40 = 46\n600 + 46 = 646\n646 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 706", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n56 + 6 = 62  \n1200 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 286", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 80 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 40 = 120\n4 + 7 = 11\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 505", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 5 = 25\n800 + 25 = 825\n825 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 230", "Answer": "A: 503", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 10 = 100\n7 + 9 = 16\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 563", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 9 + 3 = 952  "}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n8 + 7 = 15\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 280", "Answer": "A: 500", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 80 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 80 = 170 \n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 30 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 569 + 237", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9\n799 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 171", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 309", "Answer": "A: 1196", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 9 = 16\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 190 + 600", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 \n700 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1917", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 30 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 327", "Answer": "A: 888", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 328", "Answer": "A: 705", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n7 + 8 = 15\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 543", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 297", "Answer": "A: 515", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n18 + 90 = 108\n400 + 108 = 508\n508 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 348", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 297", "Answer": "A: 805", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700  \n8 + 90 = 98   \n700 + 98 = 798  \n798 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 143", "Answer": "A: 604", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 40 = 100\n1 + 3 = 4\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n9 + 5 = 14\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 383", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n19 + 80 = 99\n900 + 99 = 999\n999 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n60 + 60 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 351", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 7 + 1 = 718"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 693", "Answer": "A: 1411", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 90 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 834", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 30 = 120\n9 + 4 = 13\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n11 + 70 = 81\n1400 + 81 = 1481\n1481 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1604", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 355", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n75 + 50 = 125\n1000 + 125 = 1125\n1125 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1672", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 30 = 60\n7 + 5 = 12\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 368", "Answer": "A: 612", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 60 = 100\n4 + 8 = 12\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1533", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n10 + 10 = 20\n7 + 6 = 13\n1500 + 20 = 1520\n1520 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 393", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 90 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1901", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 60 = 90 \n1800 + 90 = 1890 \n1890 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 430 + 492", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 276", "Answer": "A: 659", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 70 = 150\n3 + 6 = 9\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1449", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 80 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 508", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n2 + 8 = 10\n700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 557", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 7 = 14\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 149", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 190", "Answer": "A: 774", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n600 + 170 = 770  \n770 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 754", "Answer": "A: 1243", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n9 + 4 = 13\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 135", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n9 + 5 = 14\n910 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 40 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 90 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 3 + 1 = 1554"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 377", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 70 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1783", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 40 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 267", "Answer": "A: 410", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 60 = 100\n3 + 7 = 10\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 290", "Answer": "A: 396", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n6 + 90 = 96\n300 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n17 + 20 = 37\n1300 + 37 = 1337\n1337 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 5 = 45\n900 + 45 = 945\n945 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n8 + 9 = 17\n1200 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1866", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 90 = 160\n4 + 2 = 6\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 397", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 9 = 889\n2 + 7 = 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 144", "Answer": "A: 361", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n17 + 40 = 57\n300 + 57 = 357\n357 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 520", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 526", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 50 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 612", "Answer": "A: 1478", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 10 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 8 = 1478"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 500", "Answer": "A: 685", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n85\n600 + 85"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 716 + 294", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n10 + 20 = 30\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 395", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 6\n826 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 445", "Answer": "A: 705", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n1300 + 120 = 1420  \n1420 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 767", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "160 + 760 = 920\n5 + 7 = 12\n920 + 12 = 932"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 536", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 938 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1690", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 50 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n39\n1000 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1097", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n2 + 5 = 7\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 839", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 6 = 1326\n1326 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 2 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 205", "Answer": "A: 343", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 5 = 35\n300 + 35 = 335\n335 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n4 + 2 = 6\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 919 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1479", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n19 + 60 = 79  \n1400 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n2 + 5 = 7\n1020 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 989", "Answer": "A: 1889", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n89\n1800 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 234", "Answer": "A: 752", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n10 + 30 = 40\n8 + 4 = 12\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 697", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n7 + 7 = 14\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 229", "Answer": "A: 390", "Explanation": "160 + 220 = 380  \n1 + 9 = 10  \n380 + 10  "}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1700", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n1 + 99 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 424", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n90 + 20 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 941", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 40 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 198", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n900 + 150 = 1050  \n1050 + 8 + 8 = 1066  "}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 427", "Answer": "A: 590", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 20 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 10 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 431 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1 + 2 = 3\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1523", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 402 + 275", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n2 + 70 = 72\n600 + 72 = 672\n672 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n4 + 3 = 7\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 643", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 223", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 90 = 180\n1200 + 180 = 1380\n1380 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 277", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n19 + 70 = 89  \n900 + 89 = 989  \n989 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 332", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 30 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 142", "Answer": "A: 287", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 2 = 7\n200 + 80 = 280\n280 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 800 + 177", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n77\n900 + 77"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 20 = 70\n5 + 3 = 8\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 436", "Answer": "A: 765", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n20 + 30 = 50  \n9 + 6 = 15  \n700 + 50 = 750  \n750 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1532", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 1 = 31\n1500 + 31"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 364", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 60 = 70\n4 + 4 = 8\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 702", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 1 = 71\n800 + 71 = 871\n871 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 244", "Answer": "A: 473", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 40 = 60\n9 + 4 = 13\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 851", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 603", "Answer": "A: 1322", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n19 + 3 = 22\n1300 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 368", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 60 = 70\n9 + 8 = 17\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 116", "Answer": "A: 1000", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n4 + 6 = 10\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n1 + 18 = 19\n1000 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 356", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n8 + 6 = 14\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n4 + 2 = 6\n1100 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 681", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 7 = 957"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 60 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 588", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 583", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 80 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n9 + 3 = 12\n1200 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 5 = 35\n1200 + 35 = 1235\n1235 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1658", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n16 + 40 = 56\n1600 + 56 = 1656\n1656 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 10 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 162", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 599", "Answer": "A: 704", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n5 + 99 = 104\n600 + 104 = 704"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 296", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n17 + 90 = 107\n900 + 107 = 1007\n1007 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 193", "Answer": "A: 527", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 518", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 208 + 175", "Answer": "A: 383", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n8 + 70 = 78  \n300 + 78 = 378  \n378 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 864", "Answer": "A: 1831", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 60 = 120\n7 + 4 = 11\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "380 + 700 = 1080\n80 + 3 = 83\n1080 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 141", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 1 = 41\n900 + 41 = 941\n941 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 347", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n3 + 40 = 43\n800 + 43 = 843\n843 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1350", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n80 + 60 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 673", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 70 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 418", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 5\n1295 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 839", "Answer": "A: 1749", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n10 + 30 = 40\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 164", "Answer": "A: 321", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 60 = 110\n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 104", "Answer": "A: 378", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 4 = 74\n300 + 74 = 374\n374 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n9 + 6 = 15\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1372", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n1200 + 170 = 1370  \n1370 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 539 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1436", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n1300 + 120 = 1420  \n1420 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 715", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 387", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 80 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n10 + 80 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 260", "Answer": "A: 1239", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 421", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n17 + 20 = 37\n1200 + 37 = 1237\n1237 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 829", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 635", "Answer": "A: 755", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 30 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1453", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n10 + 30 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 9\n1440 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1447", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n2 + 40 = 42\n1400 + 42 = 1442\n1442 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 442", "Answer": "A: 714", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 40 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 50 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 674", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 898", "Answer": "A: 1893", "Explanation": "990 + 800 = 1790\n5 + 90 = 95\n1790 + 95 = 1885\n1885 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 342", "Answer": "A: 459", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 40 = 50\n7 + 2 = 9\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 896", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n2 + 96 = 98\n900 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 414", "Answer": "A: 993", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n9 + 4 = 13\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1561", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n50 + 7 = 57  \n1500 + 57 = 1557  \n1557 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n2 + 20 = 22\n1000 + 22 = 1022\n1022 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1196", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 672", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 4  \n800 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 477", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1771", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 20 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1644", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 40 = 130\n5 + 9 = 14\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 420", "Answer": "A: 639", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n19 + 20 = 39\n600 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1486", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 10 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 423", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 3 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 750", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1281", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 70 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 446", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n8 + 6 = 14\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n5 + 7 = 12\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1512", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n7 + 5 = 12\n1500 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1552", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 3 = 43\n1500 + 43 = 1543\n1543 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 393", "Answer": "A: 550", "Explanation": "150 + 300 = 450  \n7 + 90 = 97  \n450 + 97 = 547  \n547 + 3   "}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 292", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 90 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 235", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 5 = 9\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 758", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 251", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9\n920 + 10 = 930\n930 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 631", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 437", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 149", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n50 + 80 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 461", "Answer": "A: 838", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 60 = 130\n7 + 1 = 8\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 120", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n4 + 20 = 24\n500 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 614", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 595", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 90 = 100\n3 + 5 = 8\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 380", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700,\n9 + 80 = 89,\n700 + 89."}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 134", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n4\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 117", "Answer": "A: 862", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n45 + 17 = 62\n800 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n11 + 7 = 18\n1400 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 367", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 60 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 373", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n4 + 70 = 74\n900 + 74 = 974\n974 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 284", "Answer": "A: 421", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 80 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n3 + 90 = 93\n1200 + 93 = 1293\n1293 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 90 = 180\n3 + 6 = 9\n1100 + 180 = 1280\n1280 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n1 + 3 = 4  \n1000 + 160 = 1160  \n1160 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 256", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 1 = 61\n1400 + 61"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1281", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1758", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 80 = 150\n1 + 7 = 8\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 495", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 90 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 100", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n56  \n500 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 145", "Answer": "A: 1046", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n1 + 40 = 41\n1000 + 41 = 1041\n1041 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 208", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n8 + 8 = 16\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 40 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n8 + 8 = 16\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 865", "Answer": "A: 970", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900 \n5 + 60 = 65 \n900 + 65 = 965 \n965 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n16 + 16 = 32\n1300 + 32"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 158", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9 = 979\n979 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 343", "Answer": "A: 807", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 40 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n4 + 3 = 7\n800 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 223", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 177 + 354", "Answer": "A: 531", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 50 = 120\n7 + 4 = 11\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n90 + 7 = 97\n1100 + 97 = 1197\n1197 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 149", "Answer": "A: 430", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 257", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 40 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1350", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 7 = 10\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 128", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n28 + 20 = 48\n1000 + 48 = 1048\n1048 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1457", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n50 + 6 = 56  \n1400 + 56 = 1456  \n1456 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 269", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 424", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 1\n1300 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 324 + 271", "Answer": "A: 595", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 70 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 122", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 480", "Answer": "A: 717", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 80 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 121", "Answer": "A: 312", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 20 = 110\n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 357", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 1 = 821  \n821 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 526", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 6 = 13\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 613", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 10 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n10 + 70 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n2 + 80 = 82\n1300 + 82 = 1382\n1382 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 163", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 60 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 104", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n1 + 4 = 5  \n1000 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1434", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 4 = 34\n1400 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n8 + 70 = 78\n1500 + 78 = 1578\n1578 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1666", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 80 = 160\n1 + 5 = 6\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 249", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 190 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1792", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 40 = 80\n7 + 5 = 12\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1503", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n1400 + 100 = 1500  \n1500 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n900 + 170 = 1070  \n1070 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 136", "Answer": "A: 458", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 30 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 737", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "900 + 30 = 930\n\n100 + 700 = 800\n\n90 + 30 = 120\n\n800 + 120 = 920\n\n920 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 500", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 0 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 446", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 40 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 422", "Answer": "A: 644", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 20 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1542", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 10 = 30\n1500 + 30 = 1530\n1530 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 329", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n1100 + 80 = 1180  \n1180 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1623", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n4 + 10 = 14\n1600 + 14 = 1614\n1614 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 292", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 90 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 227", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n5 + 40 = 45  \n1100 + 45 = 1145  \n1145 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1782", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 10 = 70\n5 + 7 = 12\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 603", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 3 = 23\n700 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1892", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 50 = 90\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6 + 9 = 1015"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 698", "Answer": "A: 1490", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 90 = 180\n1300 + 180 = 1480\n1480 + 10 = 1490"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1683", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 7 = 77\n1600 + 77 = 1677\n1677 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 50 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 403", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 3 = 23\n1000 + 23 = 1023\n1023 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 710 + 373", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n10 + 70 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1663", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 80 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 2 = 82\n1100 + 82 = 1182\n1182 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1558", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 4 = 54\n1500 + 54 = 1554\n1554 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1666", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 20 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1905", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n54 + 50 = 104\n1800 + 104 = 1904\n1904 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 185", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 732", "Answer": "A: 851", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n10 + 30 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 11 = 851\n851 - 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 181", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 243", "Answer": "A: 446", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n3 + 40 = 43\n400 + 43 = 443\n443 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 369", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n6 + 60 = 66\n1000 + 66 = 1066\n1066 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 336", "Answer": "A: 541", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n5 + 30 = 35  \n500 + 35 = 535  \n535 + 6   "}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 142", "Answer": "A: 393", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n50 + 40 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 1 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1767", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 10 = 60\n1 + 6 = 7\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 307", "Answer": "A: 487", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 7 = 87\n400 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 243", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1200", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 273", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9\n1200 + 9 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 744 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1712", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 60 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n4 + 8 = 12\n1700 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 167 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 102", "Answer": "A: 299", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 2 = 92\n200 + 92 = 292\n292 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 292", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 527", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 173", "Answer": "A: 516", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 70 = 110\n3 + 3 = 6\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 120", "Answer": "A: 306", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 20 = 100\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 239", "Answer": "A: 502", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 30 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 321", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 20 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1805", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 10 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 357", "Answer": "A: 555", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n90 + 50 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 15 = 555"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 26 = 46\n1100 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1289", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 30 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 341", "Answer": "A: 527", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 40 = 120\n6 + 1 = 7\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 511", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 10 = 60\n8 + 1 = 9\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 298 + 141", "Answer": "A: 439", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 40 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 9 = 439\n439 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 271", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 327", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 435", "Answer": "A: 633", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 30 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 596", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n6 + 6 = 12\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 494", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n1 + 90 = 91  \n900 + 91 = 991  \n991 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 127", "Answer": "A: 361", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 20 = 50\n4 + 7 = 11\n300 + 50 = 350\n350 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 5 = 55\n1400 + 55 = 1455\n1455 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1689", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 6 = 86\n1600 + 86 = 1686\n1686 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 308", "Answer": "A: 831", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n20 + 8 = 28\n800 + 28 = 828\n828 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 2\n1202 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 294", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 90 = 160\n1 + 4 = 5\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1576", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 80 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 107", "Answer": "A: 776", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 0 = 60\n9 + 7 = 16\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 627", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 20 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 368", "Answer": "A: 787", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n70 + 700 = 770\n770 + 9\n770 + 9 = 779\n779 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 142", "Answer": "A: 595", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 40 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1279", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n60 + 10 = 70  \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 511", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 5 = 905\n905 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n19 + 50 = 69\n1100 + 69 = 1169\n1169 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 144", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n17 + 40 = 57\n800 + 57 = 857\n857 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 268", "Answer": "A: 644", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n70 + 60 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 14 = 644"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 428", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 8 = 15\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1270", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 402", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n7 + 2 = 9\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1775", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 80 = 170\n4 + 1 = 5\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n10 + 80 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 7 = 1697"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n2 + 9 = 11\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 292 + 367", "Answer": "A: 659", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 60 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n2 + 7 = 9\n650 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1194", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 0 = 80\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 236 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n1000 + 50 = 1050  \n1050 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 664", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n15 + 60 = 75\n800 + 75 = 875\n875 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500 \n80 + 30 = 110 \n1500 + 110 = 1610 \n1610 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1604", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 50 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 356", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 50 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 579", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n7 + 9 = 16  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 661", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 60 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 10 = 790\n790 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n2 + 30 = 32\n1000 + 32 = 1032\n1032 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n91 + 9 = 100\n1300 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 205", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 5 = 55\n1000 + 55 = 1055\n1055 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 6 = 1116\n1116 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 405 + 350", "Answer": "A: 755", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n5 + 50 = 55\n700 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1537", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n10 + 50 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 275 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1944", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 80 = 130\n7 + 7 = 14\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n5 + 2 = 7\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 111 + 569", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n10 + 60 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 10 = 680"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 458", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 50 = 100\n6 + 8 = 14\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n2 + 1 = 3\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 452", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n4 + 50 = 54\n1100 + 54 = 1154\n1154 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1955", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 90 = 140\n7 + 8 = 15\n1800 + 140 = 1940\n1940 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 70 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 463", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 343", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 40 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 314", "Answer": "A: 460", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 10 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 6 = 456\n456 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 219", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1148", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n8 + 2 = 10\n1700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 200 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n45\n1000 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1558", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 30 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 160", "Answer": "A: 505", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 60 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 685", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1742", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 80 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 6 = 1736\n1736 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 490", "Answer": "A: 701", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n10 + 90 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 168", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n7 + 8 = 15\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 327", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 7 = 14\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 645", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 304", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 4 = 44\n900 + 44 = 944\n944 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 145", "Answer": "A: 302", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 40 = 90\n7 + 5 = 12\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 155", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n19 + 50 = 69\n900 + 69 = 969\n969 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 233", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 60 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 189", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n94 + 80 = 174  \n1000 + 174 = 1174  \n1174 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 220", "Answer": "A: 366", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1681", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 90 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1731", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 80 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 151", "Answer": "A: 731", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n600 + 130 = 730  \n730 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 259", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 50 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 882", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 80 = 150\n4 + 2 = 6\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 240", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n13 + 40 = 53\n1000 + 53"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n5 + 7 = 12\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 231", "Answer": "A: 551", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 557", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 649 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 40 = 80\n9 + 7 = 16\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n7 + 9 = 16\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1613", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n3 + 10 = 13\n1600 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 620", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 20 = 90\n700 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 631", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 250", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n48 + 50 = 98\n900 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9 + 4 = 1333"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 10 = 60\n7 + 8 = 15\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 402", "Answer": "A: 1374", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 2 = 72\n1300 + 72 = 1372\n1372 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 895 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 80 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 326", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 20 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 290", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 90 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 291", "Answer": "A: 633", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 3 = 633"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 183", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 546 + 205", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 0 = 40\n6 + 5 = 11\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 735", "Answer": "A: 942", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n7 + 30 = 37\n900 + 37 = 937\n937 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 687", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 80 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 220", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n600 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 340", "Answer": "A: 1028", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 40 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 575", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 70 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 511", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 118", "Answer": "A: 277", "Explanation": "150 + 100 = 250\n9 + 10 = 19\n250 + 19 = 269\n269 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 769 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1622", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 521", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 20 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 0 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1753", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 30 = 40\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 744", "Answer": "A: 1046", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n2 + 40 = 42\n1000 + 42 = 1042\n1042 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 119", "Answer": "A: 430", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n11 + 10 = 21\n400 + 21 = 421\n421 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 351", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n9 + 50 = 59\n1200 + 59 = 1259\n1259 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 596", "Answer": "A: 825", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n20 + 90 = 110  \n700 + 110 = 810  \n810 + 9 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 601", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 0 = 20\n6 + 1 = 7\n700 + 20 = 720\n720 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 295", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 90 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 628", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 460", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 60 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 287", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n60 + 80 = 140\n9 + 7 = 16\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 16 = 456"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 502", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n15 + 2 = 17\n1100 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 258", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 8 = 15\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1 + 6 = 7\n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 467 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n7 + 5 = 12\n1220 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 40 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 453", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n1 + 3 = 4\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n2 + 12 = 14\n1600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1562", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 107 + 264", "Answer": "A: 371", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n7 + 60 = 67\n300 + 67 = 367\n367 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 101", "Answer": "A: 236", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 1 = 31\n200 + 31 = 231\n231 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 10 = 1230"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 246", "Answer": "A: 822", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 806 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1657", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n6 + 50 = 56\n1600 + 56 = 1656\n1656 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 100", "Answer": "A: 703", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n3 + 0 = 3\n700 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 335", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n8 + 5 = 13\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 267", "Answer": "A: 493", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 60 = 80\n6 + 7 = 13\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 323 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n3 + 5 = 8\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n18 + 50 = 68\n1100 + 68 = 1168\n1168 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 80 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9\n1390 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 527", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n4 + 7 = 11\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1522", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n18 + 4 = 22\n1500 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 131", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 199", "Answer": "A: 772", "Explanation": "573 + 100 = 673\n673 + 90 = 763\n763 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 372", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 70 = 110\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 412", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n12 + 12 = 24  \n500 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 580", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1386", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 8 = 78\n1300 + 78 = 1378\n1378 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 10 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 366", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 5 \n1325 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 769 + 361", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9 + 1 = 1130"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 114", "Answer": "A: 599", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 4 = 9\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 572", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 573", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 60 = 130\n1100 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n5 + 9 = 14\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n19 + 20 = 39\n1000 + 39 = 1039\n1039 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 463", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 60 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 \n6 + 7 = 13\n900 + 100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 780", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "150 + 780 = 930\n930 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n7 + 6 = 13\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 256", "Answer": "A: 444", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 50 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1858", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 10 = 50\n2 + 6 = 8\n1800 + 50 = 1850\n1850 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1413", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n60 + 40 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 6 + 7 = 1413"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n9 + 40 = 49\n1400 + 49 = 1449\n1449 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 164", "Answer": "A: 600", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500 \n30 + 60 = 90 \n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 10 = 600 \n600 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1803", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n11 + 90 = 101\n1700 + 101 = 1801\n1801 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 768 + 518", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 257", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "200 + 50 = 250\n90 + 200 = 290\n250 + 290 = 540\n540 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 158", "Answer": "A: 455", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n90 + 50 = 140  \n300 + 140 = 440  \n440 + 7 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n9 + 50 = 59\n1000 + 59 = 1059\n1059 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 763", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 60 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 668", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n10 + 60 = 70  \n1400 + 70 = 1470  \n1470 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 387", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n8 + 80 = 88\n800 + 88 = 888\n888 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n5 + 4 = 9\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 416", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 10 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 635", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n3 + 30 = 33\n1400 + 33 = 1433\n1433 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 115", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n9 + 5 = 14\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 465", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 60 = 100\n5 + 5 = 10\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 586 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1200 + 110 = 1310  \n1310 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1525", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 100", "Answer": "A: 265", "Explanation": "165 + 100 = 265"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n10 + 80 = 90  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 319", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n7 + 9 = 16\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n4 + 1 = 5\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100  \n50 + 10 = 60  \n8 + 5 = 13  \n1100 + 60 = 1160  \n1160 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 8 = 48\n1200 + 48 = 1248\n1248 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 552", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 8 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 515", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n8 + 5 = 13\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1836", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n21 + 15 = 36  \n1800 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 975 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1636", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 60 = 130\n5 + 1 = 6\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 294 + 315", "Answer": "A: 609", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 10 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n4 + 5 = 9\n600 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1846", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n1700 + 140 = 1840  \n1840 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 305", "Answer": "A: 600", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n95 + 5 = 100\n500 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 610", "Answer": "A: 881", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 366", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1200 + 150 = 1350  \n1350 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 90 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 337 + 542", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 2 = 9\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 581", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n900 + 9 + 1  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 90 = 150\n3 + 3 = 6\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 654 + 200", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n54 \n800 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 155", "Answer": "A: 729", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 50 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1266", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 281", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 297", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n10 + 90 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 10 = 910"}
{"Question": "Q: 539 + 258", "Answer": "A: 797", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9 + 8 "}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 30 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 20 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 255", "Answer": "A: 397", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n300 + 90 = 390  \n390 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 136", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n30 + 30 = 60  \n7 + 6 = 13  \n600 + 60 = 660  \n660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 330", "Answer": "A: 598", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n60 + 30 = 90  \n500 + 90 = 590  \n590 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1649", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 90 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 142", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1716", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100 \n9 + 7 = 16\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 310", "Answer": "A: 674", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 434", "Answer": "A: 655", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n1 + 4 = 5\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1734", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 70 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 259", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 50 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 297 + 311", "Answer": "A: 608", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 10 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 7 + 1 = 608"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 238", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 441", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n1 + 40 = 41\n700 + 41 = 741\n741 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 260", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 60 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 758", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "160 + 700 = 860\n4 + 50 = 54\n860 + 54 = 914\n914 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9 = 1029\n1029 + 400"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 358", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n400 + 130 = 530  \n530 + 8  \n530 + 8 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n1400 + 160 = 1560  \n1560 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 335", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 30 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 550", "Answer": "A: 1249", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n99 + 50 = 149\n1100 + 149"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 355", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6 + 5 = 1131"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 50 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 162", "Answer": "A: 513", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 60 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 3 = 513"}
{"Question": "Q: 938 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1759", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 20 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 9 = 1759"}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 218", "Answer": "A: 1099", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 134", "Answer": "A: 904", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1275", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 8 = 15\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 573", "Answer": "A: 738", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 70 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 40 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 10 = 70\n4 + 4 = 8\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 40 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 743", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 249", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 129", "Answer": "A: 810", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 10 = 810\n810 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 499", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n33 + 99 = 132  \n800 + 132 = 932"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 612", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 715", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n3 + 5 = 8\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 223", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 345", "Answer": "A: 596", "Explanation": "250 + 300 = 550\n1 + 40 = 41\n550 + 41 = 591\n591 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9 \n1200 + 10 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1886", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 50 = 80\n4 + 2 = 6\n1800 + 80 = 1880\n1880 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n5 + 6 = 11  \n1300 + 150 = 1450  \n1450 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 107", "Answer": "A: 640", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 7 = 37\n600 + 37 = 637\n637 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 331", "Answer": "A: 435", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n4 + 30 = 34\n400 + 34 = 434\n434 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 562", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 10 = 740"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 119", "Answer": "A: 454", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n35 + 10 = 45\n400 + 45 = 445\n445 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 353", "Answer": "A: 503", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n50 + 50 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n6 + 30 = 36\n1100 + 36 = 1136\n1136 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1867", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 80 = 160\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 864", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n12 + 60 = 72  \n900 + 72 = 972  \n972 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 334", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n11 + 30 = 41\n1100 + 41 = 1141\n1141 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1654", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 80 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1295", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 0 = 80\n6 + 9 = 15\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 242", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 10 = 870"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 706", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 6 = 76\n1000 + 76 = 1076\n1076 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1484", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 50 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 219", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1431", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 226", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1511", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 238", "Answer": "A: 810", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 2\n800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 387", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 289", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3 = 1023\n1023 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1102", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 0 = 90\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 289 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 20 = 80\n1300 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 340", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n600 + 100 = 700  \n700 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 125", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n15 + 20 = 35\n700 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 435", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 453", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n4 + 50 = 54\n800 + 54 = 854\n854 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 485", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 80 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n14 + 20 = 34\n1000 + 34 = 1034\n1034 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 509", "Answer": "A: 674", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 0 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 10 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 201", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 0 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 7 = 957\n957 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 281", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1500", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1400 + 90 = 1490  \n1490 + 10 = 1500  "}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1 + 7 = 8\n1300 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 70 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6 = 1536"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1699", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 40 = 90\n2 + 7 = 9\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 535", "Answer": "A: 637", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n2 + 30 = 32\n600 + 32 = 632\n632 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n14 + 90 = 104\n1300 + 104 = 1404\n1404 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 125", "Answer": "A: 485", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 20 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 657", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 50 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 529", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 9\n760 + 1 = 761\n761 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n6 + 9 = 15\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 601", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n19 + 1 = 20\n900 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 733", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n2 + 30 = 32\n1400 + 32 = 1432\n1432 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 1 + 1 = 1252"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 330", "Answer": "A: 652", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 227", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n6 + 20 = 26\n1100 + 26 = 1126\n1126 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 103", "Answer": "A: 928", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 3 = 23\n900 + 23 = 923\n923 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n5 + 2 = 7\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 471", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 70 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 561", "Answer": "A: 832", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n700 + 130 = 830  \n830 + 1 + 1 = 832  "}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 534", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n2 + 4 = 6\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n7 + 9 = 16\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 6 + 1 = 1257"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 823", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n900 + 40 = 940  \n940 + 3  \n8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 425", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 5 = 705\n705 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 231", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 30 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 294", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 7 = 27\n20 + 0 = 20\n7 + 0 = 7\n1000 + 27 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 176 + 150", "Answer": "A: 326", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n70 + 50 = 120\n200 + 120 = 320\n320 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 482", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n20 + 80 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 748", "Answer": "A: 1560", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 40 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 637", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1141", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n6 + 5 = 11\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 251", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 80 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 338", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 2 = 9\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 108", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n77 + 8 = 85  \n1000 + 85  "}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 170", "Answer": "A: 390", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n20 + 70 = 90\n300 + 90 "}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 460", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 60 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1617", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 558", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 642", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 416", "Answer": "A: 978", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1855", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 60 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n10 + 50 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 9 \n1160 + 7 \n116"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 437", "Answer": "A: 809", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n70 + 30 = 100\n2 + 7 = 9\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 135", "Answer": "A: 561", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n6 + 5 = 11\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 282", "Answer": "A: 644", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 262", "Answer": "A: 553", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n400 + 150 = 550  \n550 + 3 = 553"}
{"Question": "Q: 467 + 462", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n60 + 60 = 120  \n7 + 2 = 9  \n800 + 120 = 920  \n920 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1346", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n3 + 40 = 43\n1300 + 43 = 1343\n1343 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 50 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 209", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 0 = 50\n6 + 9 = 15\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n99 + 50 = 149\n1200 + 149"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 728", "Answer": "A: 996", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n8 + 8 = 16\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1000", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1695", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 20 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 639 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1515", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n9 + 6 = 15\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 114", "Answer": "A: 942", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 10 = 30\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 4 = 934\n934 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 683", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 80 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 533", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 3 = 7\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n1400 + 90 = 1490  \n1490 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 215", "Answer": "A: 385", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 10 = 80\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 270", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 123", "Answer": "A: 551", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 20 = 40\n8 + 3 = 11\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1511", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 902 + 367", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n2 + 60 = 62\n1200 + 62 = 1262\n1262 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 559", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 4 + 9 = 933"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n4 + 30 = 34\n1200 + 34 = 1234\n1234 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 121", "Answer": "A: 408", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 1 = 8\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 787", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 70 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 685", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800   \n11 + 80 = 91  \n800 + 91 = 891  \n891 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 150 + 604", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 4 = 54\n700 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 90 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1560", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 80 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 259", "Answer": "A: 510", "Explanation": "250 + 250 = 500\n1 + 9 = 10\n500 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 7 = 1037\n1037 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 128 + 223", "Answer": "A: 351", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 20 = 40\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 262", "Answer": "A: 402", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 60 = 100\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 207", "Answer": "A: 437", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 7 = 37\n400 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 628", "Answer": "A: 1578", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n50 + 20 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 322", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 129", "Answer": "A: 670", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 20 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 352 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 326", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n7 + 6 = 13  \n1200 + 100 = 1300  \n1300 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 562", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n700 + 130 = 830  \n830 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 367", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1802", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 10 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n15 + 19 = 34\n1300 + 34 = 1334"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 346", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 277", "Answer": "A: 519", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 70 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 206", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 6 = 15\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1350", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 50 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 7 = 1350"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 113", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 10 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 3\n830 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 243", "Answer": "A: 397", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n50 + 40 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1110", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1590", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 20 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1819", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 20 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 296", "Answer": "A: 1235", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 90 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6 = 1226\n1226 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 667", "Answer": "A: 805", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 60 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 896 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 40 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 8 = 1438\n1438"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 116", "Answer": "A: 381", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 10 = 70\n5 + 6 = 11\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 207", "Answer": "A: 617", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 7 = 17\n600 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 543", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 460", "Answer": "A: 654", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n500 + 150 = 650  \n650 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 430 + 315", "Answer": "A: 745", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 10 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 682", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n10 + 80 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 20 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 238 + 352", "Answer": "A: 590", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 10 = 590"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 10 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 709", "Answer": "A: 964", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 0 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 70 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 130", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n53 + 30 = 83\n700 + 83"}
{"Question": "Q: 565 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 167 + 584", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 80 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 7 \n7 + 4 = 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 674", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 70 = 140\n8 + 4 = 12\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 383", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n10 + 80 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9 \n1120 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 215", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 10 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 7\n1190 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 586", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 80 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 8 = 958"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 473", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n6 + 70 = 76\n1100 + 76 = 1176\n1176 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 240", "Answer": "A: 540", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 \n500 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 435", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 30 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 786", "Answer": "A: 1598", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 80 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 6 = 1596\n1596 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 747", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n8 + 7 = 15\n900 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 529", "Answer": "A: 907", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 20 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1589", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n1 + 80 = 81\n1500 + 81 = 1581\n1581 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 129", "Answer": "A: 259", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 20 = 50\n200 + 50 = 250\n250 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 490", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 90 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 348", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 519", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 391", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 90 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1 + 1 = 702"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 9 = 89\n1200 + 89 = 1289\n1289 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 729", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n6 + 20 = 26\n800 + 26 = 826\n826 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 251", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 834", "Answer": "A: 1791", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n7 + 4 = 11  \n1700 + 80 = 1780  \n1780 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 297", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 90 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 10 = 780"}
{"Question": "Q: 560 + 327", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 90 = 160\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1762", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 80 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 123", "Answer": "A: 310", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 3 = 10\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 250", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 850 + 328", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 338", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n9 + 8 = 17  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1538", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 70 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1374", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n1200 + 160 = 1360  \n1360 + 8 + 6  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 447", "Answer": "A: 968", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n900 + 60 = 960  \n960 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 246", "Answer": "A: 379", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 40 = 70\n3 + 6 = 9\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 337", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 30 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 357", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n9 + 50 = 59\n800 + 59 = 859\n859 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 803 + 561", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n3 + 60 = 63\n1300 + 63 = 1363\n1363 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 363", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n40 + 60 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 8\n900 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 346 + 130", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 30 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 520", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n7 + 20 = 27\n1100 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 982", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n6 + 80 = 86\n1200 + 86 = 1286\n1286 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 140", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 7 = 47\n800 + 47"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 144", "Answer": "A: 377", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n3 + 4 = 7  \n300 + 70 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1455", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 5 = 55\n1400 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n1100 + 170 = 1270  \n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 264", "Answer": "A: 809", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 60 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 5 = 805\n805 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 912 + 449", "Answer": "A: 1361", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 40 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 11 = 1361"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 464", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 60 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 4 = 614\n614 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1607", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n6 + 1 = 7  \n1500 + 100 = 1600  \n1600 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 389", "Answer": "A: 603", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 80 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 2 = 4\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 232", "Answer": "A: 437", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n5 + 30 = 35\n400 + 35 = 435\n435 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1716", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 20 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 358", "Answer": "A: 495", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 50 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 396", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n90 + 90 = 180\n6 + 6 = 12\n400 + 180 = 580\n580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1248", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1612", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 30 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 717 + 138", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n17 + 30 = 47\n800 + 47 = 847\n847 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 376", "Answer": "A: 1302", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 312", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n8 + 12 = 20\n800 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 609", "Answer": "A: 1499", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 9 = 99\n1400 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n1400 + 100 = 1500  \n1500 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 598", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 90 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 7 + 8 = 785"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 410", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 427", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 20 = 30\n8 + 7 = 15\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n1 + 40 = 41\n1100 + 41 = 1141\n1141 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 690", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 116", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n18 + 16 = 34\n1000 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 480", "Answer": "A: 879", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 208", "Answer": "A: 993", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 0 = 80\n5 + 8 = 13\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 208", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 8 = 98\n700 + 98 = 798\n798 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n4 + 50 = 54\n1000 + 54 = 1054\n1054 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 499", "Answer": "A: 1238", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 90 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9 \n1220 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 171", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 316", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n8 + 10 = 18\n1200 + 18 = 1218\n1218 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1414", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 876", "Answer": "A: 1858", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 70 = 150\n1700 + 150 = 1850\n1850 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 469", "Answer": "A: 979", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 60 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 426", "Answer": "A: 840", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n14 + 20 = 34\n800 + 34 = 834\n834 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1124", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 1 = 21\n1100 + 21 = 1121\n1121 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 573", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n9 + 50 = 59\n1000 + 59 = 1059\n1059 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1537", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1295", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 161", "Answer": "A: 660", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 60 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 9 + 1 = 660"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 345", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n1 + 40 = 41\n500 + 41 = 541\n541 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 305", "Answer": "A: 535", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 5 = 35\n500 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 708", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n6 + 8 = 14\n800 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 413 + 324", "Answer": "A: 737", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 20 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 133", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 30 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 273", "Answer": "A: 378", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n5 + 70 = 75\n300 + 75 = 375\n375 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 429", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n7 + 9 = 16\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 698", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n900 + 160 = 1060  \n1060 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1015", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000  \n12 + 3 = 15  \n1000 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 674", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1133", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7 = 1127\n1127 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 105", "Answer": "A: 709", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n4 + 5 = 9\n700 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 40 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 798 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1919", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 80 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 264", "Answer": "A: 604", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n40 + 60 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 306", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 6 = 26\n1200 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 176", "Answer": "A: 336", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 70 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 673", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 620", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n99 + 20 = 119  \n800 + 119"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 728", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 20 = 90\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 256", "Answer": "A: 654", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 50 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 373", "Answer": "A: 668", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n1 + 90 = 91\n1000 + 91 = 1091\n1091 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 70 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n4 + 20 = 24\n1000 + 24 = 1024\n1024 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n2 + 3 = 5\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 202", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n6 + 2 = 8\n700 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 463", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 60 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 124", "Answer": "A: 561", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 20 = 50\n7 + 4 = 11\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 770", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 138", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 30 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 10 = 830\n830 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 267", "Answer": "A: 535", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n60 + 60 = 120  \n8 + 7 = 15  \n400 + 120 = 520  \n520 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 612", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n6 + 8 = 14\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 353", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 50 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 654 + 447", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 40 = 90\n4 + 7 = 11\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 450", "Answer": "A: 593", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 50 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 343 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 376", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n800 + 130 = 930  \n930 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 933", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1789", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 10 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 50 = 120\n2 + 7 = 9\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 364", "Answer": "A: 621", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 7 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 374", "Answer": "A: 689", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n5 + 4 = 9\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 388", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1376", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 40 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 1 + 5\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 678", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 70 = 110\n3 + 8 = 11\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 182", "Answer": "A: 316", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 80 = 110\n200 + 110 = 310\n310 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n15 + 30 = 45  \n1500 + 45 = 1545  \n1545 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 10 = 60\n9 + 9 = 18\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 30 = 70\n1 + 6 = 7\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 175", "Answer": "A: 568", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 70 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 324", "Answer": "A: 426", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n2 + 20 = 22\n400 + 22 = 422\n422 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1280", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 90 = 160\n6 + 7 = 13\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 596", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n800 + 170 = 970  \n970 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 597", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 90 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 8 = 1448"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 973", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 338", "Answer": "A: 509", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n1 + 8 = 9\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1809", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n80 + 20 = 100\n4 + 5 = 9\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1746", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 80 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 100", "Answer": "A: 241", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 41 = 241\n241 - 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1557", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 230", "Answer": "A: 382", "Explanation": "150 + 200 = 350\n2 + 30 = 32\n350 + 32"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 50 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 311", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 977 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 30 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n7 + 4 = 11\n1700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 386", "Answer": "A: 916", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n4 + 7 = 11\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1687", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 30 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 1 + 6 = 1687"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 361", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 60 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1698", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 40 = 90\n2 + 6 = 8\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1669", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 70 = 160\n5 + 4 = 9\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 400", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n96\n700 + 96"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 502", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 2 = 62\n900 + 62"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1896", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 20 = 80\n8 + 8 = 16\n1800 + 80 = 1880\n1880 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 50 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 70 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 413", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 483", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 7 = 847"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n51 + 60 = 111\n1300 + 111 = 1411\n1411 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 383", "Answer": "A: 605", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 80 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 2\n600 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 728", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n18 + 20 = 38\n900 + 38 = 938\n938 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1433", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n1 + 30 = 31\n1400 + 31 = 1431\n1431 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 349", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 569 + 369", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9 = 929\n929 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 684", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n9 + 4 = 13\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 252", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n800 + 130 = 930  \n930 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 140", "Answer": "A: 250", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 40 = 50\n200 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1486", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n20 + 60 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 10 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 70 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1651", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 60 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n7 + 3 = 10\n1500 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 343", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n17 + 40 = 57\n1100 + 57 = 1157\n1157 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 616 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n16 + 5 = 21\n1300 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 658", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n50 + 50 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n6 + 8 = 14  \n800 + 14  "}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 441", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 40 = 60\n7 + 1 = 8\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n3 + 6 = 9\n1300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1494", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 80 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 303", "Answer": "A: 527", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 3 = 23\n500 + 23 = 523\n523 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 484 + 134", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n500 + 110 = 610  \n610 + 4 = 614  \n614 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1766", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 20 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 308", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n90 + 8 = 98\n900 + 98 = 998\n998 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 604", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 4 = 24\n900 + 24 = 924\n924 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 606", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 6 = 46\n800 + 46 = 846\n846 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 799 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1759", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 9 = 99\n1600 + 99 = 1699\n1699 + 60 = 1759"}
{"Question": "Q: 990 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1686", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 90 = 180\n1500 + 180 = 1680\n1680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 480", "Answer": "A: 1337", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1694", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n50 + 40 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 816", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n24 + 16 = 40\n1000 + 40"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 777", "Answer": "A: 1660", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 70 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1758", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n10 + 40 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1720", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 60 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 676", "Answer": "A: 1507", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 6 = 1506\n1506 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n70 + 60 = 130\n2 + 1 = 3\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 700 + 191", "Answer": "A: 891", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n91  \n800 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 269", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 60 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 2 \n490 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 614", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n5 + 4 = 9\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 70 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 354", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 185", "Answer": "A: 383", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 80 = 170\n200 + 170 = 370\n370 + 8 = 378\n378 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 246", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 40 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 6 + 1 = 607"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 474", "Answer": "A: 663", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 70 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 9 \n9 + 4 = 13\n650 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 90 = 170\n6 + 2 = 8\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n9 + 70 = 79\n1100 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 832 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 70 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1615", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 190", "Answer": "A: 397", "Explanation": "200 + 190 = 390\n7 + 0 = 7\n390 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 416", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n6 + 6 = 12\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 552", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 50 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 379", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 373", "Answer": "A: 679", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n6 + 70 = 76  \n600 + 76 = 676  \n676 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1680", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 90 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 900 + 282", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n82\n1100 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 306", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n78 + 6 = 84\n1000 + 84"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1879", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 80 = 170\n1700 + 170 = 1870\n1870 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 557", "Answer": "A: 755", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 50 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 15 = 755"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 489", "Answer": "A: 605", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 80 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 216", "Answer": "A: 463", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 10 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 7\n457 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 229", "Answer": "A: 370", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n60 + 1 = 61\n300 + 61 = 361\n361 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1306", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n70 + 30 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 837", "Answer": "A: 1796", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 30 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n9 + 7 = 16\n1780 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 228", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 20 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 6\n756 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n1100 + 76 = 1176"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1271", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n6 + 60 = 66\n1200 + 66 = 1266\n1266 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1472", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 0 = 60\n3 + 9 = 12\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 388", "Answer": "A: 888", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 8 = 88\n800 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 339", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n8 + 9 = 17\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n1500 + 40 = 1540  \n1540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 90 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 7 = 1647"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 621", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n50 + 20 = 70   \n800 + 70 = 870  \n870 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 0 = 90\n7 + 8 = 15\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 558", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 50 = 100\n3 + 8 = 11\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 775", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "150 + 700 = 850\n1 + 70 = 71\n850 + 71 = 921\n921 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n7 + 60 = 67\n1200 + 67 = 1267\n1267 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 819", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n7 + 9 = 16\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 3 = 53\n1100 + 53 = 1153\n1153 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 897 + 291", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n1000 + 180 = 1180   \n1180 + 7 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 691", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 768", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n2 + 68 = 70\n1500 + 70"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 601", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 1 = 81\n700 + 81"}
{"Question": "Q: 145 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n45 + 60 = 105  \n1000 + 105"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1436", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 4 = 34\n1400 + 34 = 1434\n1434 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 173", "Answer": "A: 665", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 70 = 160\n500 + 160 = 660\n660 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 7 = 17\n1400 + 17 = 1417\n1417 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1711", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n1600 + 100 = 1700  \n1700 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 433", "Answer": "A: 557", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 292", "Answer": "A: 476", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 90 = 170\n300 + 170 = 470\n470 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 241", "Answer": "A: 678", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 40 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 134", "Answer": "A: 246", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 30 = 40\n2 + 4 = 6\n200 + 40 = 240\n240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 184", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 4 = 6\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 479", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 70 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1329", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n10 + 10 = 20\n1300 + 20 = 1320\n1320 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 509", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 0 = 80\n3 + 9 = 12\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 2 = 32\n1000 + 32 = 1032\n1032 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1812", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 70 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1731", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 60 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n9 + 2 = 11\n1720 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 162", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 60 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 157", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n9 + 50 = 59\n700 + 59 = 759\n759 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 748", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 501", "Answer": "A: 735", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 1 = 31\n700 + 31 = 731\n731 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 797", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n15 + 90 = 105\n800 + 105 = 905\n905 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 425", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1099", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 906", "Answer": "A: 1848", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n42 + 6 = 48\n1800 + 48"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 315", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n4 + 10 = 14\n1100 + 14 = 1114\n1114 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 163 + 562", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 2 = 62\n600 + 62 = 662\n662 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 512", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 10 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 330", "Answer": "A: 588", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n50 + 30 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n40 + 20 = 60  \n2 + 7 = 9  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 20 = 90\n4 + 9 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1261", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 6 = 1256\n1256 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 441", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n700 + 80 = 780  \n780 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 404", "Answer": "A: 1369", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 40 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 5\n1400 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 286", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 90 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 148", "Answer": "A: 341", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 40 = 130\n3 + 8 = 11\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 316", "Answer": "A: 448", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 10 = 40\n2 + 6 = 8\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1771", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n4 + 7 = 11\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 197", "Answer": "A: 551", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 90 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 224", "Answer": "A: 1112", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n8 + 4 = 12\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 117", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n17 + 100 = 117\n1000 + 17 = 1017\n1017 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 989", "Answer": "A: 1850", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n60 + 80 = 140  \n1700 + 140 = 1840  \n1840 + 10 = 1850"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1640", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 10 = 30\n1600 + 30 = 1630\n1630 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 642", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1679", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 2 = 9\n1600 + 70 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 660 + 172", "Answer": "A: 832", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 584 + 631", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 256", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1263", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 80 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 5 = 45\n1300 + 45 = 1345\n1345 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n4 + 4 = 8\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 565", "Answer": "A: 817", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 444", "Answer": "A: 650", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n6 + 40 = 46\n600 + 46 = 646\n646 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 538 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n8 + 7 = 15\n1400 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 280", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n13 + 80 = 93\n1000 + 93"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n77 + 10 = 87\n1000 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 909 + 885", "Answer": "A: 1794", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n9 + 80 = 89\n1700 + 89 = 1789\n1789 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1044", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 70 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5 = 1205\n1205 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 553", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n4 + 3 = 7\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 679", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 351", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n40 + 50 = 90  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 191", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n900 + 140 = 1040  \n1040 + 5 = 1045"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 394", "Answer": "A: 575", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 90 = 170\n400 + 170 = 570\n570 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1734", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n34 + 0 = 34\n1700 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 248", "Answer": "A: 814", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 6  \n806 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 423", "Answer": "A: 764", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 40 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 980 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1689", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 9 = 89\n1600 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n1200 + 150 = 1350  \n1350 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1836", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 9 = 16\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 199", "Answer": "A: 576", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 90 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 587", "Answer": "A: 1544", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 80 = 130\n7 + 7 = 14\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 231", "Answer": "A: 395", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n60 + 30 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 375", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 70 = 80\n4 + 5 = 9\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 170", "Answer": "A: 430", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 70 = 130\n300 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1446", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 40 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 301", "Answer": "A: 907", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n6 + 1 = 7\n900 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 357", "Answer": "A: 952", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1431", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n7 + 4 = 11\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 347", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 40 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n2 + 30 = 32\n1100 + 32 = 1132\n1132 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 838", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n2 + 30 = 32\n1100 + 32 = 1132\n1132 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 109", "Answer": "A: 287", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n78 + 9 = 87\n200 + 87"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 396", "Answer": "A: 741", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 6 = 11\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 377", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 70 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 466", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 60 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 550", "Answer": "A: 738", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n88 + 50 = 138  \n600 + 138  "}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 141", "Answer": "A: 700", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 10 = 700"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 213", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n600 + 90 = 690  \n690 + 9 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1312", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n14 + 80 = 94\n1200 + 94 = 1294\n1294 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 556 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1535", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 665 + 296", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 90 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n10 + 8 = 18\n1400 + 18 = 1418\n1418 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 634", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 4 = 894\n894 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 108 + 182", "Answer": "A: 290", "Explanation": "100 + 80 = 180  \n8 + 2 = 10  \n180 + 10  "}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1661", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 20 = 50\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 978 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1541", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 60 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 478", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 10 = 20\n1300 + 20 = 1320\n1320 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 415", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 10 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1858", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n4 + 50 = 54\n1800 + 54 = 1854\n1854 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 752", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 50 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7 \n7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1933", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 70 = 130\n1 + 2 = 3\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 412 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n5 + 30 = 35\n1000 + 35 = 1035\n1035 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 899", "Answer": "A: 1514", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 90 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 592", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 90 = 160\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 781", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n20 + 50 = 70  \n3 + 8 = 11  \n1000 + 70 = 1070  \n1070 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 30 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 105", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 5 = 45\n900 + 45 = 945\n945 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 318", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 10 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 614", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n90 + 900 = 990\n990 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 349", "Answer": "A: 1299", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1782", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 50 = 80\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 463", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n5 + 3 = 8\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 673", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 7 = 957  \n957 - 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 175", "Answer": "A: 871", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 6\n866 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1453", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 10 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 438", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 90 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 136", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n2 + 30 = 32\n900 + 32 = 932\n932 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 130", "Answer": "A: 765", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 35 = 65\n700 + 65 = 765"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 272", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 70 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 849 + 291", "Answer": "A: 1140", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 9 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 674", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 70 = 90\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 158", "Answer": "A: 543", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 50 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 5 = 535\n535 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 252", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 10 = 740"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1593", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 10 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 604", "Answer": "A: 885", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n80 + 4 = 84  \n800 + 84 = 884  \n884 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 449", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 126", "Answer": "A: 1010", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n4 + 6 = 10  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 10  "}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 855", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 50 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1053", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n4 + 9 = 13\n1040 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 157", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n2 + 50 = 52  \n800 + 52 = 852  \n852 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 3\n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 119", "Answer": "A: 593", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n4 + 9 = 13\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n19 + 4 = 23\n1300 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 202", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n50 + 2 = 52  \n900 + 52 = 952  \n952 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 481", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 764", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 862", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n8 + 60 = 68\n1500 + 68 = 1568\n1568 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 518", "Answer": "A: 671", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n50 + 10 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 526", "Answer": "A: 733", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n7 + 20 = 27\n700 + 27 = 727\n727 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 650", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 50 = 60\n1100 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1704", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 60 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 548", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 40 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 5 \n800 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 665 + 542", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1610", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 60 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 522", "Answer": "A: 925", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n3 + 20 = 23  \n900 + 23 = 923  \n923 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 8 = 10\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 691 + 266", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 60 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 7 = 957\n957 - 1 = 956\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 234", "Answer": "A: 365", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1 + 4 = 5\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 422", "Answer": "A: 633", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n11 + 20 = 31\n600 + 31 = 631\n631 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 510", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1281", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 401 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n1 + 80 = 81\n1000 + 81 = 1081\n1081 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1726", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 5 = 25\n1700 + 25 = 1725\n1725 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n10 + 70 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 151", "Answer": "A: 428", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 50 = 120\n7 + 1 = 8\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n51 + 80 = 131  \n1000 + 131"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1687", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n30 + 50 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n3 + 5 = 8\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 962 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1501", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 30 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 418 + 642", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 40 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 380", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n4 + 80 = 84\n1200 + 84"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 125", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n75 + 25 = 100\n800 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n9 + 7 = 16\n1300 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 225", "Answer": "A: 469", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 20 = 60\n4 + 5 = 9\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 318", "Answer": "A: 559", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 10 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 125", "Answer": "A: 704", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n9 + 5 = 14\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 116", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n4 + 16 = 20  \n900 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 395", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n3 + 5 = 8\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n1 + 16 = 17\n1200 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 165 + 316", "Answer": "A: 481", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 10 = 70\n5 + 6 = 11\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n48 + 8 = 56  \n1000 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 5 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 995 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1779", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n90 + 80 = 170\n5 + 4 = 9\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 20 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 1 = 21\n1100 + 21 = 1121\n1121 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 372", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 302", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n6 + 2 = 8\n1000 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 507", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 7 = 47\n600 + 47"}
{"Question": "Q: 588 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 10 = 1510"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 667", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 60 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 7 \n3"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 346 + 619", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 10 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 6\n950 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 727", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n19 + 20 = 39\n800 + 39 = 839\n839 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1307", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 284", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 858", "Answer": "A: 1328", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 50 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 80 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 10\n1220 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 214", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 10 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1959", "Explanation": "980 + 970 = 1950\n4 + 5 = 9\n1950 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 817 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n10 + 10 = 20\n1400 + 20 = 1420\n1420 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 683", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n2 + 80 = 82\n1200 + 82 = 1282\n1282 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 284 + 713", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 612", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n30 + 10 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 3 = 943"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1714", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n7 + 7 = 14\n1700 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 386", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 90 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 424", "Answer": "A: 714", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n600 + 110 = 710  \n710 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 548", "Answer": "A: 1471", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 396 + 187", "Answer": "A: 583", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 80 = 170\n400 + 170 = 570\n570 + 6 = 576\n576 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1458", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 6\n1456 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 153", "Answer": "A: 511", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 50 = 100\n8 + 3 = 11\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 375", "Answer": "A: 1006", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n1 + 5 = 6\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 117", "Answer": "A: 382", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 10 = 70\n5 + 7 = 12\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 400", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60\n1200 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1571", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 30 = 60\n2 + 9 = 11\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6\n1140 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1760", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n90 + 60 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 10 = 1760"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 660", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 60 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 628", "Answer": "A: 786", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n50 + 20 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 503", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n6 + 3 = 9\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 924 + 274", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4\n1190 + 4 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 215", "Answer": "A: 746", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 10 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 6 "}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 584", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 50 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 671", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700  \n90 + 70 = 160  \n700 + 160 = 860  \n860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 277", "Answer": "A: 687", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 70 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 165", "Answer": "A: 426", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1 + 5 = 6\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 471 + 316", "Answer": "A: 787", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 280 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 397", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 90 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 10 = 980"}
{"Question": "Q: 632 + 258", "Answer": "A: 890", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 10 = 890"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1607", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 20 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 90 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 704 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n4 + 50 = 54\n1200 + 54 = 1254\n1254 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1630", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 50 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 705", "Answer": "A: 1612", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n7 + 5 = 12\n1600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 482", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 555", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 420", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 866", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 8  \n6 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 608", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n3 + 8 = 11\n1200 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n2 + 60 = 62\n1500 + 62 = 1562\n1562 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1011", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1940", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n55 + 80 = 135\n1800 + 135 = 1935\n1935 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 737", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n2 + 30 = 32  \n800 + 32 = 832  \n832 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1664", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 179", "Answer": "A: 840", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 10 = 840"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 405", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 5 = 25\n1000 + 25 = 1025\n1025 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 0 = 50\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 920 + 744", "Answer": "A: 1664", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 40 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 642", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 420", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 764", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n10 + 60 = 70\n1 + 4 = 5\n1400 + 70 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 623", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 20 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 307", "Answer": "A: 606", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n99 + 7 = 106  \n500 + 106"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 242", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1540", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n4 + 6 = 10  \n1400 + 130 = 1530  \n1530 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 183", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 80 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 10 = 860\n860 - 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 246", "Answer": "A: 435", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n300 + 120 = 420  \n420 + 9  \n420 + 9 + 6   "}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 787", "Answer": "A: 1688", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n1 + 80 = 81  \n1600 + 81 = 1681  \n1681 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 543", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 546", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n2 + 6 = 8  \n700 + 100 = 800  \n800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1742", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n6 + 6 = 12\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1803", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n90 + 0 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n64\n1300 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 581", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 80 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 718", "Answer": "A: 1714", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n90 + 10 = 100  \n6 + 8 = 14  \n1600 + 100 = 1700  \n1700 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1491", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 487", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 7 = 14\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 666", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n14 + 60 = 74\n700 + 74 = 774\n774 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 210", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 545 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n5 + 8 = 13\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 236", "Answer": "A: 539", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n3 + 30 = 33\n500 + 33 = 533\n533 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 514", "Answer": "A: 678", "Explanation": "600 + 70 = 670\n4 + 4 = 8\n670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 437", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7 + 8 = 1125"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 121", "Answer": "A: 365", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n60 + 4 = 64\n300 + 64 = 364\n364 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 424 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 60 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 4 \n1284 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 150", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n44 + 50 = 94\n700 + 94"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1585", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 10 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 372", "Answer": "A: 646", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 70 = 140\n4 + 2 = 6\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 719", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n40 + 10 = 50  \n800 + 50 = 850  \n850 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 0 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1658", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n1500 + 150 = 1650  \n1650 + 8 = 1658  \n1658 -"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n7 + 6 = 13\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 352", "Answer": "A: 687", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n5 + 2 = 7\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 382", "Answer": "A: 548", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 80 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 8 = 548\n548 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1875", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 90 = 170\n2 + 3 = 5\n1700 + 170 = 1870\n1870 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 985", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 195", "Answer": "A: 375", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 90 = 170\n200 + 170 = 370\n370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 142", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1467", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n6 + 60 = 66\n1400 + 66 = 1466\n1466 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 721", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 171", "Answer": "A: 277", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n6 + 70 = 76\n200 + 76 = 276\n276 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 40 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n4 + 60 = 64\n1400 + 64"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 394", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 90 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 101", "Answer": "A: 242", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 1 = 41\n200 + 41 = 241\n241 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 591", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n2 + 90 = 92\n800 + 92 = 892\n892 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 449", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 286", "Answer": "A: 1213", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n1100 + 100 = 1200  \n1200 + 7 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n8 + 50 = 58\n1400 + 58 = 1458\n1458 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 203", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n40 + 0 = 40  \n2 + 3 = 5  \n900 + 40 = 940  \n940 + 5  "}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 443", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n700 + 90 = 790  \n790 + 1 + 3 = 794  "}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 921", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 357", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 50 = 100\n6 + 7 = 13\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 303", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n49 + 3 = 52\n800 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1568", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 30 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 514", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 167", "Answer": "A: 281", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n10 + 60 = 70\n4 + 7 = 11\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 274", "Answer": "A: 656", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 70 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 506", "Answer": "A: 625", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n19 + 6 = 25\n600 + 25"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 292", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n30 + 90 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 5 \n720 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 412", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 10 = 20\n900 + 20 = 920\n920 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 163", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n18 + 60 = 78  \n1000 + 78 = 1078  \n1078 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 50 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 6 = 1276\n1276 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 414", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n4 + 10 = 14\n1000 + 14 = 1014\n1014 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1759", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 20 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 106", "Answer": "A: 793", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n80 + 6 = 86  \n700 + 86 = 786  \n786 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 342", "Answer": "A: 708", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n6 + 2 = 8\n700 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 155", "Answer": "A: 369", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n14 + 50 = 64\n300 + 64 = 364\n364 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 574", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 70 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 371 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n71 + 19 = 90\n1000 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 774", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n4 + 4 = 8  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1638", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n50 + 80 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 972", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 70 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 557 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1246", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 555", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 50 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 7 + 5 = 927"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 350", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 50 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 217", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n4 + 10 = 14\n1000 + 14 = 1014\n1014 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1406", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n90 + 10 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 424", "Answer": "A: 693", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 20 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 792 + 671", "Answer": "A: 1463", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 70 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 889", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 80 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n5 + 9 = 14\n1200 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 664 + 436", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 30 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 523", "Answer": "A: 1378", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n15 + 30 = 45\n1200 + 45 = 1245\n1245 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 815 + 293", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n15 + 90 = 105\n1000 + 105 = 1105\n1105 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n4 + 40 = 44\n1000 + 44 = 1044\n1044 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 161 + 145", "Answer": "A: 306", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1 + 5 = 6\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 961", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 60 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 746", "Answer": "A: 910", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n900 + 10  \n6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 904", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n15 + 4 = 19\n1100 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 692", "Answer": "A: 1627", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 90 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1725", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 50 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n9 + 6 = 15\n1710 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 283", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 201 + 159", "Answer": "A: 360", "Explanation": "200 + 150 = 350\n1 + 9 = 10\n350 + 10 = 360"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1808", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 80 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 284", "Answer": "A: 733", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n40 + 80 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 9 = 729\n729 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 645", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5 = 1025\n1025 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 191", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 90 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 599 + 610", "Answer": "A: 1209", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 797 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 90 = 180\n7 + 5 = 12\n1300 + 180 = 1480\n1480 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1924", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n1800 + 120 = 1920  \n1920 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1824", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n40 + 80 = 120   \n1700 + 120 = 1820  \n1820 + 1 + 3   "}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 558", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n20 + 50 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 5 + 8 = 683"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 432", "Answer": "A: 578", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 30 = 70\n6 + 2 = 8\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1612", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 30 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n3 + 9 = 12\n1600 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 497 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1303", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 0 = 90\n7 + 6 = 13\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 30 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 949 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1509", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 60 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1690", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 50 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 7 + 3\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 305", "Answer": "A: 679", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 0 = 70\n4 + 5 = 9\n600 + 70 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1931", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 90 = 120\n1800 + 120 = 1920\n1920 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 659", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n9 + 9 = 18\n1400 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 375", "Answer": "A: 997", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 2 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 436", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 304", "Answer": "A: 482", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 4 = 74\n400 + 74 = 474\n474 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 552", "Answer": "A: 960", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n8 + 50 = 58\n900 + 58 = 958\n958 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 535 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 5 = 35\n1000 + 35"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 494", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 90 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 10 = 680"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 418", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n9 + 8 = 17\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 313", "Answer": "A: 535", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 330", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n26 + 30 = 56\n1000 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 325 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 521", "Answer": "A: 1022", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n1 + 20 = 21\n1000 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 361", "Answer": "A: 1119", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 580", "Answer": "A: 791", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 80 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 7 = 67\n1000 + 67 = 1067\n1067 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 841 + 416", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 10 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n9 + 2 = 11\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 567", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n9 + 60 = 69\n1200 + 69 = 1269\n1269 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n9 + 5 = 14\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 115 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1112", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n15 + 97 = 112  \n1000 + 112"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 159 + 148", "Answer": "A: 307", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 40 = 90\n9 + 8 = 17\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 441", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 649", "Answer": "A: 880", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1064", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n9 + 50 = 59\n1000 + 59 = 1059\n1059 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 842", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n20 + 40 = 60\n5 + 2 = 7\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1562", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 3 = 53\n1500 + 53 = 1553\n1553 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 474", "Answer": "A: 695", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 737", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 30 = 90\n5 + 7 = 12\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 396", "Answer": "A: 651", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n500 + 140 = 640  \n640 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n5 + 7 = 12\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 170 + 775", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "170 + 700 = 870\n70 + 5 = 75\n870 + 75"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 367", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 60 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n3 + 1 = 4\n1500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 40 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 788 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 20 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n8 + 9 = 17\n1300 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 615", "Answer": "A: 751", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 10 = 40\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 6 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 257", "Answer": "A: 409", "Explanation": "150 + 250 = 400\n2 + 7 = 9\n400 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1918", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n90 + 90 = 180\n4 + 4 = 8\n1800 + 180 = 1980\n1980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 608 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n8 + 80 = 88\n1300 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 70 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6 = 1396"}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 497", "Answer": "A: 746", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9 = 739\n739 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 756", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n5 + 50 = 55  \n900 + 55 = 955  \n955 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n30 + 10 = 40  \n1400 + 40 "}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 684", "Answer": "A: 1143", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n9 + 4 = 13\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 410", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 844", "Answer": "A: 1088", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1707", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 20 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 220 + 479", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 297", "Answer": "A: 548", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n50 + 90 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 366", "Answer": "A: 537", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n400 + 130 = 530  \n530 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 728", "Answer": "A: 1538", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n10 + 20 = 30\n1500 + 30 = 1530\n1530 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1732", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 40 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 291", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 90 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 216 + 115", "Answer": "A: 331", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n16 + 10 = 26\n300 + 26 = 326\n326 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1183", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 2 = 82\n1100 + 82 = 1182\n1182 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 905 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1842", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n5 + 30 = 35\n1800 + 35 = 1835\n1835 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 616 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n10 + 30 = 40\n6 + 9 = 15\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 975 + 256", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 50 = 120\n5 + 6 = 11\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 447 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1424", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 70 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 224", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n8 + 4 = 12\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 9 = 1409"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 581", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n1200 + 160 = 1360  \n1360 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 383", "Answer": "A: 648", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 5\n645 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n4 + 9 = 13\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 583", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n10 + 80 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 107", "Answer": "A: 573", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 7 = 67\n500 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 266", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 60 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 726", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n20 + 20 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 9\n840 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 90 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 318", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n7 + 8 = 15\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 399 + 497", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n90 + 90 = 180  \n9 + 7 = 16  \n700 + 180 = 880  \n880 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n6 + 10 = 16\n1000 + 16 = 1016\n1016 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n8 + 6 = 14\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n40 + 10 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 315", "Answer": "A: 490", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n75 + 15 = 90\n400 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 486 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1233", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 163", "Answer": "A: 882", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n19 + 60 = 79\n800 + 79 = 879\n879 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 293 + 738", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300  \n11 + 5 = 16  \n1300 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1646", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n10 + 30 = 40  \n1600 + 40 = 1640  \n1640 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 521", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 1 = 2\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 659 + 318", "Answer": "A: 977", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n9 + 8 = 17\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 437", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n2 + 7 = 9\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 269", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n9 + 60 = 69\n700 + 69 = 769\n769 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 547 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 10 = 50\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1954", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n60 + 90 = 150\n1 + 3 = 4\n1800 + 150 = 1950\n1950 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1453", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 90 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 478", "Answer": "A: 808", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 70 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 994 + 248", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 851", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 50 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 317", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 10 = 20\n800 + 20 = 820\n820 + 6 \n820 + 6 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 249 + 273", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n400 + 110 = 510  \n510 + 9 = 519  \n519 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 127", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 7 = 14\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 505", "Answer": "A: 986", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 0 = 80\n1 + 5 = 6\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 759", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 159", "Answer": "A: 1147", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n80 + 50 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 8 + 9  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 556", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 360", "Answer": "A: 549", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n400 + 140 = 540  \n540 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 291", "Answer": "A: 415", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 90 = 110\n300 + 110 = 410\n410 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 272", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n5 + 70 = 75\n800 + 75 = 875\n875 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 334", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 40 = 100\n2 + 1 = 3\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 351", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 50 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 6\n846 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 375", "Answer": "A: 560", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 70 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 223", "Answer": "A: 408", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n300 + 100 = 400  \n400 + 5 = 405  \n405 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 480", "Answer": "A: 649", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1530", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 4 = 24\n1500 + 24 = 1524\n1524 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 247", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9 = 1139\n1139 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 7 \n1407 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 278", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 70 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 367", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n8 + 7 = 15\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n1000 + 100 = 1100  \n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 263 + 497", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n600 + 150 = 750  \n750 + 10 = 760  \n760  "}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 511", "Answer": "A: 964", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1946", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n90 + 50 = 140\n1 + 5 = 6\n1800 + 140 = 1940\n1940 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 50 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n3 + 4 = 7\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 326", "Answer": "A: 772", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 20 = 60\n6 + 6 = 12\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 423 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1190", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 606", "Answer": "A: 1377", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 6 = 76\n1300 + 76 = 1376\n1376 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 10 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 616", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 270", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 70 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 524", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n3 + 4 = 7\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n10 + 10 = 20\n6 + 8 = 14\n20 + 14 = 34\n1500 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 713", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 523", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 721", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 172", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1641", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 4 = 11\n30 + 11 = 41\n1600 + 41"}
{"Question": "Q: 992 + 383", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n90 + 80 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 805 + 537", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n5 + 30 = 35\n1300 + 35 = 1335\n1335 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n72 + 30 = 102\n1400 + 102"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 776", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n1300 + 110 = 1410  \n1410 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 273", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n10 + 70 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 164 + 734", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 130 = 190\n700 + 190 = 890\n890 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 455", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n10 + 50 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 279 + 237", "Answer": "A: 516", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n9 + 7 = 16  \n400 + 100 = 500  \n500 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 147", "Answer": "A: 688", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n1 + 7 = 8\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 123", "Answer": "A: 243", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 20 = 40\n3 + 3 = 6\n200 + 40 = 240\n240 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 527", "Answer": "A: 664", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600 \n30 + 20 = 50 \n600 + 50 = 650 \n650 + 7 = 657 \n657 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1296", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 4 = 94\n1200 + 94 = 1294\n1294 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 460", "Answer": "A: 1179", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n19 + 60 = 79\n1100 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 263", "Answer": "A: 654", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 60 = 150\n500 + 150 = 650\n650 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1439", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 440 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n40 + 16 = 56\n1300 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n9 + 25 = 34\n1100 + 34"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 90 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 549 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n40 + 7 = 47  \n1200 + 47 = 1247  \n1247 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 644", "Answer": "A: 782", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 40 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 120", "Answer": "A: 422", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n2 + 20 = 22\n400 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n3 + 9 = 12\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 368", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 571", "Answer": "A: 1444", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n1300 + 140 = 1440  \n1440 + 1 + 3  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 324", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 4 = 5\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 658", "Answer": "A: 762", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n4 + 50 = 54\n700 + 54 = 754\n754 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 109", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 9 = 49\n800 + 49 = 849\n849 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 502", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 0 = 60\n4 + 2 = 6\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 411 + 857", "Answer": "A: 1268", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 50 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 164", "Answer": "A: 342", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n70 + 60 = 130\n8 + 4 = 12\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1358", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 272", "Answer": "A: 836", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 6 = 836\n836 - 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 588", "Answer": "A: 846", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 2 = 82\n1200 + 82 = 1282\n1282 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 404", "Answer": "A: 582", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 4 = 74\n500 + 74 = 574\n574 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 500", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n97 \n800 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 147", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 10 = 980\n980 - 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n1 + 16 = 17\n1500 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 781", "Answer": "A: 975", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 673 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1442", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 60 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 975 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1899", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 20 = 90\n5 + 4 = 9\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 672", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 564 + 365", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 60 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1600", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n\n30 + 60 = 90\n\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n\n1590 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 9\n1240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 484", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 348 + 151", "Answer": "A: 499", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 50 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 8 + 1 = 499"}
{"Question": "Q: 352 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 581 + 409", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n80 + 9 = 89\n900 + 89 = 989\n989 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n90 + 60 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4 \n1354 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 329", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9\n1280 + 9 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 318 + 302", "Answer": "A: 620", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n18 + 2 = 20\n600 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 159", "Answer": "A: 805", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 50 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 151", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 363", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n9 + 60 = 69\n800 + 69 = 869\n869 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1627", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 60 = 120\n2 + 5 = 7\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 706 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n6 + 40 = 46  \n1600 + 46 = 1646  \n1646 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 298", "Answer": "A: 517", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n19 + 80 = 99\n400 + 99 = 499\n499 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1108", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n3 + 5 = 8\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 141", "Answer": "A: 747", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n6 + 40 = 46\n700 + 46 = 746\n746 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 421", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 20 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 9 \n1040 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 569", "Answer": "A: 744", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 4 + 9 = 743\n743 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 114", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n3 + 14 = 17\n1000 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1847", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 40 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 417", "Answer": "A: 1388", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 10 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 466", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n19 + 60 = 79\n1200 + 79 = 1279\n1279 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1562", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n1 + 60 = 61\n1500 + 61 = 1561\n1561 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 845", "Answer": "A: 1301", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n6 + 5 = 11\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 744", "Answer": "A: 1367", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n1300 + 60 = 1360  \n1360 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 220", "Answer": "A: 738", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n18 + 20 = 38\n700 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 151", "Answer": "A: 579", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 50 = 70\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 588", "Answer": "A: 883", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 265", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n7 + 60 = 67\n1100 + 67 = 1167\n1167 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 281", "Answer": "A: 421", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 80 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 225", "Answer": "A: 526", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n1 + 20 = 21\n500 + 21 = 521\n521 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n8 + 9 = 17\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 819 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1728", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n19 + 9 = 28\n1700 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 563", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 60 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 8 + 3 = 841"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 265", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5\n1140 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 988", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 80 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 766", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7 + 6 = 1123"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1535", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 5 = 45\n90 + 0 = 90\n1400 + 45 = 1445\n1445 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 0 = 60\n4 + 9 = 13\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 295 + 109", "Answer": "A: 404", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 0 = 90\n5 + 9 = 14\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 151", "Answer": "A: 559", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n8 + 50 = 58  \n500 + 58 = 558  \n558 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 699 + 658", "Answer": "A: 1357", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n90 + 50 = 140   \n9 + 8 = 17  \n1200 + 140 = 1340  \n1340 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1437", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 90 = 130\n3 + 4 = 7\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 341", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n9 + 1 = 10\n700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1016", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 475", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n7 + 5 = 12\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 498 + 400", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n800 + 98"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 136", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 30 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 6 = 786\n786 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 590", "Answer": "A: 1406", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n16 + 90 = 106\n1300 + 106 = 1406"}
{"Question": "Q: 378 + 325", "Answer": "A: 703", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n8 + 5 = 13\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 448", "Answer": "A: 605", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 40 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 7 + 8 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 322", "Answer": "A: 743", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 2 = 3\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 80 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 236", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9\n1029"}
{"Question": "Q: 914 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1578", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n14 + 60 = 74\n1500 + 74 = 1574\n1574 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 237", "Answer": "A: 950", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 30 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 418", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 10 = 40\n1 + 8 = 9\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 349", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n78 + 40 = 118\n1000 + 118 = 1118\n1118 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1097", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 20 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 550", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 117", "Answer": "A: 429", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n10 + 10 = 20\n2 + 7 = 9\n400 + 20 = 420\n420 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 355", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n16 + 50 = 66\n700 + 66 = 766\n766 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1662", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 10 = 50\n1600 + 50 = 1650\n1650 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 912", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 124 + 172", "Answer": "A: 296", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 70 = 90\n4 + 2 = 6\n200 + 90 = 290\n290 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1645", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n4 + 1 = 5\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1724", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 60 = 110\n7 + 7 = 14\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n13 + 5 = 18\n1100 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 146 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1115", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 301", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 1 = 81\n1000 + 81 = 1081\n1081 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 574 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1499", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 20 = 90\n4 + 5 = 9\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 50 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 294 + 145", "Answer": "A: 439", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n90 + 40 = 130\n4 + 5 = 9\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 550 + 352", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 50 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 361", "Answer": "A: 734", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n70 + 60 = 130\n3 + 1 = 4\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 930 + 307", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 7 = 37\n1200 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 267 + 537", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 30 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 7 \n790 + 7 = 797\n797 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1879", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 8 = 78\n1800 + 78 = 1878\n1878 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 497 + 150", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500  \n97 + 50 = 147  \n500 + 147 = 647"}
{"Question": "Q: 596 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1468", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 20 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1572", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 10 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 7 = 1027\n1027 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 10 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 1\n1000 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 308", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 8 = 68\n1200 + 68\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1508", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 50 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 233", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1940", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 50 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 6 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 120", "Answer": "A: 277", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n50 + 20 = 70\n200 + 70 = 270\n270 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 315", "Answer": "A: 441", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 10 = 30\n6 + 5 = 11\n400 + 30 = 430\n430 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 765", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 742 + 262", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n2 + 2 = 4\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 431", "Answer": "A: 864", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n3 + 1 = 4\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n8 + 30 = 38\n1000 + 38 = 1038\n1038 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1822", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n60 + 50 = 110\n1700 + 110 = 1810\n1810 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 869 + 538", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9 \n1399 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 784 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1366", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 80 = 160\n4 + 2 = 6\n1200 + 160 = 1360\n1360 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 442", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n1 + 40 = 41\n1000 + 41 = 1041\n1041 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 155", "Answer": "A: 396", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1 + 5 = 6\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 923", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n3 + 20 = 23\n1500 + 23 = 1523\n1523 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 300", "Answer": "A: 631", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n600 + 31"}
{"Question": "Q: 548 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n40 + 60 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 8 + 1 = 1309"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 306", "Answer": "A: 567", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 6 = 66\n500 + 66 = 566\n566 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 174", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 482", "Answer": "A: 617", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 80 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 385", "Answer": "A: 919", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 0 = 70\n3 + 8 = 11\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 630", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n70 + 30 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 710 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n10 + 70 = 80  \n1100 + 80 = 1180  \n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 539", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n9 + 9 = 18\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 584", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n7 + 80 = 87\n900 + 87 = 987\n987 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 623 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 50 = 70\n3 + 7 = 10\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 232 + 343", "Answer": "A: 575", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n30 + 40 = 70\n2 + 3 = 5\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 531 + 390", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 783", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 147", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n700 + 130 = 830  \n830 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 221", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1\n701 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 168 + 823", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n60 + 20 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 3  \n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n10 + 70 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 603", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n9 + 3 = 12\n1200 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 146", "Answer": "A: 361", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n15 + 40 = 55\n300 + 55 = 355\n355 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1557", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 10 = 50\n5 + 2 = 7\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1703", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 60 = 90\n6 + 7 = 13\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 423", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 20 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 3\n560 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 298", "Answer": "A: 820", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 662", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n4 + 60 = 64\n700 + 64 = 764\n764 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 267", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n30 + 60 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 462 + 200", "Answer": "A: 662", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 0 = 60\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1806", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n40 + 60 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n50 + 20 = 70  \n1 + 7 = 8  \n1000 + 70 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 938 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 668", "Answer": "A: 780", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 434", "Answer": "A: 564", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1634", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 10 = 30\n1600 + 30 = 1630\n1630 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1381", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 4 \n1370 + 4 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 908 + 250", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n8 + 50 = 58\n1100 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 253", "Answer": "A: 956", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n3 + 50 = 53 \n900 + 53 = 953 \n953 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 581", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n3 + 1 = 4\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1658", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 90 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1883", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n1800 + 70 = 1870  \n1870 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1528", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n9 + 19 = 28\n1500 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1594", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 60 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000 \n80 + 50 = 130 \n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 132", "Answer": "A: 702", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n70 + 30 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n70 + 4 = 74\n1100 + 74 = 1174\n1174 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1143", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 30 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 3\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 439", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1541", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 1 = 41\n1500 + 41"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n9 + 6 = 15\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 334", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n6 + 30 = 36\n900 + 36 = 936\n936 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 548", "Answer": "A: 862", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 40 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 245", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500 \n10 + 40 = 50 \n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 536 + 728", "Answer": "A: 1264", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1161", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n2 + 9 = 11\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 447 + 393", "Answer": "A: 840", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n700 + 130 = 830  \n830 + 7 = 837  \n837 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 301", "Answer": "A: 681", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 1 = 81\n600 + 81"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 632", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 487", "Answer": "A: 840", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 10 = 840"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1748", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n20 + 10 = 30  \n1700 + 30 = 1730  \n1730 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 578 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1577", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 90 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 823 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1715", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 90 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 481", "Answer": "A: 720", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n30 + 80 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1009", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 70 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1288", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n88\n1200 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 400", "Answer": "A: 913", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n900 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n9 + 6 = 15\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 361 + 149", "Answer": "A: 510", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 40 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n1 + 9 = 10\n500 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n1200 + 140 = 1340  \n1340 + 8 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 848", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n1 + 48 = 49\n900 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 139 + 376", "Answer": "A: 515", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 70 = 100\n9 + 6 = 15\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 675", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 70 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 209", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 0 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 9 = 759\n759 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 120", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1114", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 50 = 100\n8 + 6 = 14\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 557", "Answer": "A: 1385", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 50 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 269", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 60 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 7 \n1240 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 450", "Answer": "A: 586", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 936", "Answer": "A: 1827", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n90 + 30 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 729", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 226", "Answer": "A: 1013", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 20 = 100\n7 + 6 = 13\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 460", "Answer": "A: 720", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 60 = 120\n600 + 120"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 549", "Answer": "A: 923", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n70 + 40 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 9 = 919\n919 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 208", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n70 + 8 = 78  \n1000 + 78  "}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 938", "Answer": "A: 1791", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n50 + 30 = 80\n3 + 8 = 11\n1700 + 80 = 1780\n1780 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 540", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 40 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 526", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 20 = 40\n9 + 6 = 15\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1712", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 50 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 385", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n900 + 160 = 1060  \n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 341", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 9 + 1 = 830"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 146", "Answer": "A: 928", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 40 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 8\n920 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 715", "Answer": "A: 1059", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 10 = 50\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 431", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n10 + 30 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n4 + 8 = 12\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 133", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n15 + 30 = 45\n700 + 45 = 745\n745 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 494 + 432", "Answer": "A: 926", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1586", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 4 = 84\n1500 + 84 = 1584\n1584 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 80 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1596", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 50 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n7 + 5 = 12\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1677", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n60 + 10 = 70  \n1600 + 70 = 1670  \n1670 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 991 + 186", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1504", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 30 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 733 + 122", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 841", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 40 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 3 = 1153"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n20 + 80 = 100  \n1400 + 100 = 1500  \n1500 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n2 + 3 = 5\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 236", "Answer": "A: 338", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n2 + 30 = 32\n300 + 32 = 332\n332 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 345", "Answer": "A: 560", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n15 + 40 = 55\n500 + 55 = 555\n555 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 481 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 1\n1121 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 402", "Answer": "A: 1050", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n48 + 2 = 50  \n1000 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 533 + 126", "Answer": "A: 659", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n30 + 20 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 3 = 653\n653 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1740", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n40 + 90 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 10 = 1740"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 147", "Answer": "A: 489", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 40 = 80\n2 + 7 = 9\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 808", "Answer": "A: 927", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n19 + 8 = 27\n900 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 524", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 215", "Answer": "A: 681", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 10 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 6\n676 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 433", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 30 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 166", "Answer": "A: 350", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n80 + 60 = 140\n200 + 140 = 340\n340 + 10 = 350\n350 - 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 216", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n5 + 99 = 104  \n1000 + 104"}
{"Question": "Q: 649 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1242", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 90 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1777", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n70 + 4 = 74  \n1700 + 74 = 1774  \n1774 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 318 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1076", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n18 + 50 = 68  \n1000 + 68 = 1068  \n1068 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 229", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 356", "Answer": "A: 1322", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 50 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 714", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 4 = 6\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1489", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 70 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 292", "Answer": "A: 1137", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1560", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n1400 + 150 = 1550  \n1550 + 1 + 9  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1774", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 4 = 74\n1700 + 74"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 60 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 935 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1902", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n30 + 60 = 90\n5 + 7 = 12\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 899 + 627", "Answer": "A: 1526", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n90 + 20 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 7 = 47\n1400 + 47 = 1447\n1447 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 243", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1577", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n10 + 60 = 70\n3 + 4 = 7\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 161", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n5 + 1 = 6\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 234 + 290", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1931", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n1800 + 120 = 1920  \n1920 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 483 + 488", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n80 + 80 = 160\n3 + 8 = 11\n800 + 160 = 960\n960 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 537", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 118", "Answer": "A: 240", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 18 = 38\n200 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 353 + 114", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 10 = 60\n3 + 4 = 7\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n9 + 90 = 99\n1500 + 99 = 1599 \n1599 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 793", "Answer": "A: 1007", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n4 + 3 = 7\n1000 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 838", "Answer": "A: 1684", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n6 + 8 = 14  \n1600 + 70 = 1670  \n1670 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 313 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 297", "Answer": "A: 431", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 90 = 120\n4 + 7 = 11\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 864", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n30 + 60 = 90 \n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 204", "Answer": "A: 652", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n48 + 4 = 52\n600 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 505", "Answer": "A: 680", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n75 + 5 = 80\n600 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 867", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 810", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 122", "Answer": "A: 774", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 20 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 132", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1439", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 426", "Answer": "A: 620", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n90 + 20 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 355 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 597 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 7 + 1 = 1308"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 755", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 384", "Answer": "A: 767", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n80 + 80 = 160\n3 + 4 = 7\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 621", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n1400 + 40 = 1440  \n1440 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 328", "Answer": "A: 497", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 20 = 80\n9 + 8 = 17\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1797", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 8 = 88\n1700 + 88 = 1788\n1788 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 621", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 297", "Answer": "A: 870", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 913 + 134", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n10 + 30 = 40  \n1000 + 40 = 1040  \n1040 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 644", "Answer": "A: 1509", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 40 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n5 + 4 = 9\n1500 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n7 + 17 = 24\n1200 + 24  "}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n5 + 11 = 16\n1200 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 358 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n58 + 9 = 67  \n1000 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 703 + 649", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n3 + 40 = 43\n1300 + 43 = 1343\n1343 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 341", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n600 + 130 = 730  \n730 + 8 = 738  \n738 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 478 + 285", "Answer": "A: 763", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 8\n758 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 622", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 10 = 1260"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 370", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n5 + 70 = 75\n1000 + 75"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 9\n1240 + 7 "}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1619", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n20 + 90 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 317", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n9 + 10 = 19  \n1100 + 19 = 1119  \n1119 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 323 + 449", "Answer": "A: 772", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n3 + 9 = 12\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 427", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n8 + 20 = 28\n1100 + 28 = 1128\n1128 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 165", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5 = 985\n985 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 497", "Answer": "A: 803", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n6 + 90 = 96\n700 + 96 = 796\n796 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 175", "Answer": "A: 677", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n2 + 70 = 72\n600 + 72 = 672\n672 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 547", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n10 + 40 = 50  \n800 + 50 = 850  \n850 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1903", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 70 = 90\n7 + 6 = 13\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n22 + 0 = 22\n1100 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 627", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n90 + 20 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 656", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 162", "Answer": "A: 842", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 452", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 50 = 100\n6 + 2 = 8\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 984", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n10 + 80 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 539", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n40 + 30 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 657", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 50 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 1 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 128", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n1 + 20 = 21  \n1000 + 21 = 1021  \n1021 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 543", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n70 + 40 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 10 = 1020"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 785", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 80 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 178", "Answer": "A: 439", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 70 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 498", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 90 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 259", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 50 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 9 = 479\n479 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 347", "Answer": "A: 449", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n2 + 40 = 42\n400 + 42 = 442\n442 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 806", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n20 + 6 = 26\n900 + 26 = 926\n926 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 414", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n80 + 4 = 84\n500 + 84 = 584\n584 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 163", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 325", "Answer": "A: 536", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 20 = 30\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 60 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 659", "Answer": "A: 1643", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 50 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1065", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 412", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 10 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 164", "Answer": "A: 572", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n8 + 60 = 68\n500 + 68 = 568\n568 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1332", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 668 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1540", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 70 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 192", "Answer": "A: 340", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n40 + 90 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 10 = 340"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 243", "Answer": "A: 514", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1 + 3 = 4\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 273", "Answer": "A: 542", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 70 = 130\n9 + 3 = 12\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 453 + 803", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n3 + 3 = 6\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 419", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 546", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n7 + 6 = 13\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n40 + 10 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 898", "Answer": "A: 1726", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 8 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 746 + 434", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1622", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 30 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 491", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 5 = 1345\n1345 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1761", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 0 = 50\n6 + 5 = 11\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 10 = 70\n3 + 7 = 10\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 894", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 855 + 752", "Answer": "A: 1607", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 50 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 183 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 3 = 83\n1000 + 83 = 1083\n1083 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 968 + 117", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n8 + 7 = 15\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 391 + 504", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 4 = 94\n800 + 94 = 894\n894 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 887 + 167", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 7 \n1040 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1234", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4   "}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 128", "Answer": "A: 613", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 20 = 100\n5 + 8 = 13\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 10 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 438 + 411", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n8 + 1 = 9\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n9 + 8 = 17\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 176 + 718", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n6 + 8 = 14\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1290", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90\n1200 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1673", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n4 + 60 = 64\n1600 + 64 = 1664\n1664 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n5 + 8 = 13\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 990", "Answer": "A: 1162", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 634 + 263", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 60 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n18 + 40 = 58\n1300 + 58 = 1358\n1358 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1528", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n2 + 90 = 92\n1400 + 92 = 1492\n1492 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 123", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n76 + 20 = 96\n800 + 96 = 896\n896 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1795", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 90 = 180\n8 + 7 = 15\n1600 + 180 = 1780\n1780 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 574", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n1 + 4 = 5  \n1300 + 140 = 1440  \n1440 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 957 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1803", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 40 = 90\n7 + 6 = 13\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 402", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 2 = 52\n1300 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 121 + 229", "Answer": "A: 350", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 9 = 10\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 330", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 30 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 282", "Answer": "A: 759", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 907 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1559", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n7 + 50 = 57\n1500 + 57 = 1557\n1557 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 351", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n18 + 50 = 68  \n1200 + 68 = 1268  \n1268 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 759", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 625", "Answer": "A: 1360", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n30 + 20 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 565", "Answer": "A: 1392", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n20 + 60 = 80\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n9 + 8 = 17\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 354", "Answer": "A: 1094", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 341", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 1 = 8\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1682", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n11 + 70 = 81\n1600 + 81 = 1681\n1681 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 212", "Answer": "A: 581", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 10 = 70\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1934", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 60 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 1 + 3 = 1934"}
{"Question": "Q: 309 + 323", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n9 + 20 = 29\n600 + 29 = 629\n629 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 9 = 89\n1300 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 528 + 114", "Answer": "A: 642", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 10 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 959 + 453", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n9 + 3 = 12\n1400 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 329 + 230", "Answer": "A: 559", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1165", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 5 = 65\n1100 + 65"}
{"Question": "Q: 387 + 594", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n80 + 90 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 229", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 190 + 186", "Answer": "A: 376", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 80 = 170\n200 + 170 = 370\n370 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1649", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n49 + 0 = 49\n1600 + 49"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 298", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n80 + 90 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 769", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n7 + 60 = 67\n1200 + 67 = 1267\n1267 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 706", "Answer": "A: 1485", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n70 + 6 = 76\n1400 + 76 = 1476\n1476 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 537", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n90 + 30 = 120  \n1000 + 120 = 1120  \n1120 + 4  \n1124 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 681", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9 + 1 = 850"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 60 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n4 + 9 = 13\n1100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 707", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n50 + 7 = 57\n1100 + 57 = 1157\n1157 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 326 + 137", "Answer": "A: 463", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 30 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 160", "Answer": "A: 462", "Explanation": "300 + 160 = 460  \n460 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 552", "Answer": "A: 896", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n4 + 2 = 6\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 374 + 478", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n4 + 8 = 12  \n700 + 140 = 840  \n840 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 601", "Answer": "A: 1066", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 0 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 463", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 141", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 386", "Answer": "A: 565", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 80 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 9\n550 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 800", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n12\n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 822", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 20 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 129", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n71 + 20 = 91\n800 + 91 = 891\n891 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 297", "Answer": "A: 816", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n19 + 90 = 109\n700 + 109 = 809\n809 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 218", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 8 = 15\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n140 + 1000 = 1140\n1140 + 9  \n9 + 7 = 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 915 + 690", "Answer": "A: 1605", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n15 + 90 = 105\n1500 + 105"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 919", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 10 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 537", "Answer": "A: 1489", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n1400 + 80 = 1480  \n1480 + 9 = 1489  \n1489 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 324 + 639", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n20 + 30 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 798", "Answer": "A: 1405", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n7 + 90 = 97\n1300 + 97 = 1397\n1397 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 250", "Answer": "A: 1085", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 404 + 527", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n4 + 20 = 24\n900 + 24 = 924\n924 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 526", "Answer": "A: 1173", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n7 + 6 = 13\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 493", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n80 + 90 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 30 = 50\n1500 + 50 = 1550\n1550 + 5 + 1 = 1556"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 557", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n40 + 50 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 615", "Answer": "A: 965", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 315", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 5 = 10\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 580 + 600", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n80 + 100 = 180  \n1000 + 180"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 282", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 80 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1648", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n6 + 2 = 8\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1520", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n9 + 11 = 20\n1500 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 181", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n90 + 80 = 170\n500 + 170 = 670\n670 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 390", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n9 + 90 = 99\n700 + 99"}
{"Question": "Q: 911 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n11 + 80 = 91\n1400 + 91 = 1491\n1491 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 446", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 40 = 80\n6 + 6 = 12\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 156", "Answer": "A: 765", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n9 + 50 = 59\n700 + 59 = 759\n759 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 451", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 50 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1838", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 60 = 130\n1700 + 130 = 1830\n1830 + 8 = 1838"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 560", "Answer": "A: 1502", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n900 + 120 = 1020  \n1020 + 3  \n1020 + 8  "}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 233", "Answer": "A: 742", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n9 + 30 = 39\n700 + 39 = 739\n739 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 153", "Answer": "A: 259", "Explanation": "100 + 150 = 250\n6 + 3 = 9\n250 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1811", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1700 + 110 = 1810  \n1810 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 756", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 6 = 13\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 228 + 771", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 312 + 294", "Answer": "A: 606", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n10 + 90 = 100\n2 + 4 = 6\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 396", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9\n839 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 654", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 50 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 237", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 7 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 863 + 895", "Answer": "A: 1758", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n60 + 90 = 150\n3 + 5 = 8\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 80 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 108 + 216", "Answer": "A: 324", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n8 + 16 = 24\n300 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1327", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 601", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 1 = 21\n1100 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 395", "Answer": "A: 599", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n4 + 90 = 94\n500 + 94 = 594\n594 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 360 + 266", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n60 + 60 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 725 + 167", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 721 + 726", "Answer": "A: 1447", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n1 + 6 = 7\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 441 + 554", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1374", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n60 + 10 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1780", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90 + 80 = 170\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1473", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 505", "Answer": "A: 845", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 5 = 45\n800 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 180", "Answer": "A: 354", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n70 + 80 = 150\n200 + 150 = 350\n350 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 153 + 808", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n50 + 8 = 58\n900 + 58 = 958\n958 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 9\n1110 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 263", "Answer": "A: 516", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n50 + 60 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 410", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n45 + 10 = 55\n800 + 55"}
{"Question": "Q: 456 + 276", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n50 + 70 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 110 + 200", "Answer": "A: 310", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n200 + 10 = 210\n210 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 134", "Answer": "A: 263", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n20 + 30 = 50\n9 + 4 = 13\n200 + 50 = 250\n250 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 407", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n11 + 7 = 18\n1200 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 299", "Answer": "A: 890", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 90 = 180\n700 + 180 = 880\n880 + 10 = 890"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 377", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 235 + 504", "Answer": "A: 739", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 4 = 34\n700 + 34 = 734\n734 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 905 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1904", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n5 + 90 = 95\n1800 + 95 = 1895\n1895 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 403 + 410", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n3 + 10 = 13\n800 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1462", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 90 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 70 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 555", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 8 + 5 = 953"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 70 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 626", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 6 = 11\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 210", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 10 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 405", "Answer": "A: 1097", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n90 + 0 = 90\n2 + 5 = 7\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n48 - 1 = 47\n1600 + 47 = 1647"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 258", "Answer": "A: 933", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n70 + 50 = 120  \n800 + 120 = 920  \n920 + 5 = 925  \n925 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 782 + 154", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n80 + 50 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1673", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n30 + 30 = 60  \n4 + 9 = 13  \n1600 + 60 = 1660  \n1660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 677", "Answer": "A: 1524", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 70 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1940", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n40 + 90 = 130\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 10 = 1940"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 559", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "130 + 550 = 680  \n1 + 9 = 10  \n680 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 147", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 389", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n2 + 9 = 11\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 770", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n1300 + 150 = 1450  \n1450 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 434", "Answer": "A: 1427", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n90 + 30 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 503 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n3 + 15 = 18\n1400 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1736", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1350", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 10 = 1350"}
{"Question": "Q: 641 + 849", "Answer": "A: 1490", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 10 = 1490"}
{"Question": "Q: 173 + 373", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 3 = 6\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1579", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n8 + 70 = 78\n1500 + 78 = 1578\n1578 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 622", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n25 + 90 = 115  \n1400 + 115 = 1515  \n1515 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 213 + 423", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n10 + 20 = 30\n600 + 30 = 630\n630 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 566", "Answer": "A: 1212", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 60 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n1600 + 100 = 1700  \n1700 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 702", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 2 = 22\n1200 + 22 = 1222\n1222 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 517", "Answer": "A: 655", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 10 = 40\n600 + 40 \n8 + 7 = 15\n640 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1287", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n90 + 90 = 180\n1100 + 180 = 1280\n1280 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 187", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n10 + 80 = 90  \n900 + 90 = 990  \n990 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 392", "Answer": "A: 570", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n400 + 160 = 560  \n560 + 10 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 666 + 805", "Answer": "A: 1471", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 0 = 60\n6 + 5 = 11\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1352", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n30 + 10 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 853 + 152", "Answer": "A: 1005", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n50 + 3 = 53  \n900 + 53 = 953  \n953 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 389", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n3 + 80 = 83\n1200 + 83 = 1283\n1283 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 522 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1372", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 50 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 622 + 456", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 668", "Answer": "A: 826", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n\n50 + 60 = 110\n\n700 + 110 = 810\n\n810 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 155", "Answer": "A: 365", "Explanation": "200 + 150 = 350\n10 + 5 = 15\n350 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 70 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 177", "Answer": "A: 511", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n30 + 70 = 100\n4 + 7 = 11\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1625", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 40 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 937 + 316", "Answer": "A: 1253", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n30 + 10 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 7\n1240 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 236", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n7 + 6 = 13\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 437 + 430", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 117", "Answer": "A: 857", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 10 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 493 + 618", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 10 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 888 + 335", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1735", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 519", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400  \n20 + 10 = 30  \n1400 + 30 = 1430  \n1430 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 314", "Answer": "A: 832", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 10 = 20\n800 + 20 = 820\n820 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 402", "Answer": "A: 542", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 2 = 42\n500 + 42"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 715", "Answer": "A: 817", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n2 + 15 = 17\n800 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 555 + 172", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 70 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 5 = 725\n725 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 725", "Answer": "A: 917", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 5   \n910 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 655", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 50 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n40 + 70 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 258", "Answer": "A: 563", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n5 + 50 = 55\n500 + 55 = 555\n555 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 151 + 521", "Answer": "A: 672", "Explanation": "150 + 500 = 650\n1 + 20 = 21\n650 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1799", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n4 + 90 = 94\n1700 + 94 = 1794\n1794 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 343", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 40 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1202", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 559", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 50 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 551 + 299", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n50 + 90 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9 = 849\n849 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1398", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n70 + 20 = 90\n5 + 3 = 8\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 460", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 60 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 307", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 0 = 90\n6 + 7 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 177", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 982 + 178", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n1000 + 150 = 1150  \n1150 + 10 = 1160  \n1160 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 198", "Answer": "A: 336", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 90 = 120\n8 + 8 = 16\n200 + 120 = 320\n320 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 475", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 70 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 438", "Answer": "A: 594", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 30 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1457", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n90 + 50 = 140\n9 + 8 = 17\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 130", "Answer": "A: 646", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n16 + 30 = 46\n600 + 46"}
{"Question": "Q: 961 + 148", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 40 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1 + 8 = 9\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 788 + 456", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 454", "Answer": "A: 659", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n5 + 50 = 55\n600 + 55 = 655\n655 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 310 + 308", "Answer": "A: 618", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n10 + 8 = 18\n600 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1273", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n9 + 4 = 13\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 628", "Answer": "A: 1405", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 20 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 120 + 462", "Answer": "A: 582", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 60 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 569", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 436 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n30 + 30 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 707 + 464", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n7 + 60 = 67\n1100 + 67 = 1167\n1167 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 243 + 832", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1707", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n7 + 0 = 7  \n1700 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 164", "Answer": "A: 914", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 150", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 50 = 130\n400 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 502 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1033", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n2 + 30 = 32\n1000 + 32 = 1032\n1032 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 814 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1514", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n14 + 0 = 14\n1500 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 649 + 501", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n40 + 0 = 40\n9 + 1 = 10\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1180", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 8 = 10\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 817", "Answer": "A: 1445", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 10 = 30\n1400 + 30 = 1430\n1430 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 111", "Answer": "A: 373", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 10 = 70\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1316", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 40 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 9 + 5 = 1014"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 799", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n60 + 90 = 150\n800 + 150 = 950\n950 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 534 + 427", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 20 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 4 = 954\n954 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 430", "Answer": "A: 619", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n80 + 30 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 118", "Answer": "A: 607", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 10 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 9 = 599\n599 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 216", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 10 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 262", "Answer": "A: 477", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n10 + 60 = 70\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 356", "Answer": "A: 865", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n9 + 50 = 59\n800 + 59 = 859\n859 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 339 + 205", "Answer": "A: 544", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 5 = 35\n500 + 35 = 535\n535 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 246", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 482", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 265", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n20 + 70 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 = 995\n995 - 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 591", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 624 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 197 + 526", "Answer": "A: 723", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1601", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n20 + 70 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1376", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 50 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 315", "Answer": "A: 597", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n80 + 10 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 2 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 714 + 611", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 10 = 20\n1300 + 20 = 1320\n1320 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 844", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 605", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n47 + 5 = 52\n1200 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 264 + 231", "Answer": "A: 495", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 30 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 444 + 651", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 5 = 1095\n1095 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 642", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n30 + 40 = 70\n2 + 2 = 4\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 671 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1651", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n70 + 80 = 150  \n1500 + 150  \n1500 + 150 + 1   "}
{"Question": "Q: 688 + 115", "Answer": "A: 803", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n88 + 15 = 103\n700 + 103 = 803"}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1477", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n10 + 60 = 70\n1400 + 70\n1470 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 822", "Answer": "A: 928", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n6 + 20 = 26\n900 + 26 = 926\n926 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 435", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n2 + 30 = 32\n1200 + 32 = 1232\n1232 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 696", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n3 + 6 = 9\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 552", "Answer": "A: 817", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 50 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 311 + 211", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n11 + 10 = 21\n500 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 898 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1862", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1700 + 150 = 1850  \n1850 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 518 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 10 = 20\n1100 + 20 = 1120\n1120 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 987 + 523", "Answer": "A: 1510", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 963 + 477", "Answer": "A: 1440", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n60 + 70 = 1300\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 10 = 1440"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1254", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n54 \n1200 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n9 + 6 = 15\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 655 + 780", "Answer": "A: 1435", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n55 + 80 = 135\n1300 + 135 = 1435"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 547", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n3 + 7 = 10\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 507 + 599", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n7 + 90 = 97  \n1000 + 97 = 1097  \n1097 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 795 + 209", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 0 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 + 4 = 999\n999 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 500 + 339", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n30 + 9 = 39  \n800 + 39"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1293", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 50 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 251", "Answer": "A: 460", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n9 + 50 = 59\n400 + 59 = 459\n459 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 998 + 681", "Answer": "A: 1679", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 80 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 9 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 152", "Answer": "A: 615", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 50 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 3\n610 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 372", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n9 + 70 = 79  \n700 + 79 = 779  \n779 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 689", "Answer": "A: 1464", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n5 + 9 = 14\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1812", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n30 + 70 = 100\n4 + 8 = 12\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 822 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1685", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 60 = 80\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 184 + 854", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 50 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 4 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n7 + 2 = 9\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 305 + 667", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n5 + 60 = 65\n900 + 65 = 965\n965 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1907", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 40 = 90\n8 + 9 = 17\n1800 + 90 = 1890\n1890 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1052", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n5 + 40 = 45\n1000 + 45 = 1045\n1045 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 341", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 40 = 80\n1 + 1 = 2\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 337", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 30 = 80\n2 + 7 = 9\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1452", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 70 = 140\n4 + 8 = 12\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1690", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n90\n1600 + 90 = 1690"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1412", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n9 + 3 = 12\n1400 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 474", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 141", "Answer": "A: 752", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n11 + 40 = 51\n700 + 51 = 751\n751 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 505", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 0 = 90\n7 + 5 = 12\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 800 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1054", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 4 = 54\n1000 + 54"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1738", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n90 + 40 = 130\n2 + 6 = 8\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 574", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 70 = 160 \n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 9 \n1269"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n40 + 6 = 46  \n1000 + 46  "}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1298", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 40 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 543 + 821", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 20 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 344", "Answer": "A: 1223", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 304", "Answer": "A: 1095", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 4 = 94\n1000 + 94 = 1094\n1094 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 647 + 688", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n40 + 80 = 120\n7 + 8 = 15\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 378", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n80 + 70 = 150  \n5 + 8 = 13  \n800 + 150 = 950  \n950 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1106", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n14 + 90 = 104  \n1000 + 104 = 1104  \n1104 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1000 + 110 = 1110  \n1110 + 10 = 1120"}
{"Question": "Q: 366 + 445", "Answer": "A: 811", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 40 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6\n806 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 808", "Answer": "A: 1528", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n20 + 8 = 28\n1500 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 694", "Answer": "A: 1619", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n20 + 90 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 102", "Answer": "A: 486", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 2 = 82\n400 + 82"}
{"Question": "Q: 735 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n5 + 4 = 9\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1603", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 30 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 287", "Answer": "A: 1023", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n30 + 80 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 6  \n1016 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 106", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 0 = 60\n7 + 6 = 13 \n\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 698", "Answer": "A: 1211", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n10 + 90 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3 \n1200 + 3 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 648 + 510", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n48 + 10 = 58\n1100 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 797", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 632", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n40 + 30 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 666", "Answer": "A: 1663", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 60 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n7 + 6 = 13\n1650 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 595", "Answer": "A: 712", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n600 + 100 = 700  \n7 + 5 = 12  \n700 + 12  "}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 880", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 80 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1456", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 70 = 150\n5 + 1 = 6\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 624", "Answer": "A: 784", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 20 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 774 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1666", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n4 + 2 = 6  \n1500 + 160 = 1660  \n1660 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 524", "Answer": "A: 1254", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 742", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 2 = 7\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 650", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n16 + 50 = 66\n900 + 66"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1945", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n50 + 80 = 130\n8 + 7 = 15\n1800 + 130 = 1930\n1930 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 928 + 355", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 50 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 110", "Answer": "A: 949", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 10 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 791", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n20 + 90 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 326", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n9 + 6 = 15\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 547", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 377", "Answer": "A: 490", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n13 + 70 = 83  \n400 + 83 = 483  \n483 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 715", "Answer": "A: 1580", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 10 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 586 + 313", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 713", "Answer": "A: 838", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n20 + 10 = 30\n800 + 30 = 830\n830 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 127 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 762", "Answer": "A: 1632", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n1500 + 130 = 1630  \n1630 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 162 + 541", "Answer": "A: 703", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n2 + 1 = 3\n700 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 170", "Answer": "A: 685", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n15 + 70 = 85\n600 + 85"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 389", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n9 + 80 = 89\n900 + 89 = 989\n989 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 390", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 949", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 40 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9 + 4 = 1410 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 20 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 9\n1350 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n10 + 30 = 40\n4 + 3 = 7\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 351 + 146", "Answer": "A: 497", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 40 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 896", "Answer": "A: 1487", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 90 = 180\n1300 + 180 = 1480\n1480 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 702 + 361", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n2 + 60 = 62\n1000 + 62 = 1062\n1062 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 569", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n700 + 150 = 850  \n850 + 10 = 860  "}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1515", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 594 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n90 + 40 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 9 = 1339\n1339 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 5 = 1515\n1515 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 868 + 223", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n60 + 20 = 80\n8 + 3 = 11\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 851 + 229", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070 \n1070 + 9 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1513", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n80 + 20 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n5 + 8 = 13\n1500 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 297", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n30 + 90 = 120\n3 + 7 = 10\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 735", "Answer": "A: 920", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n80 + 30 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 149 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 299", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500  \n76 + 90 = 166  \n500 + 166 = 666  \n666 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n10 + 80 = 90\n7 + 6 = 13\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 170", "Answer": "A: 1130", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1000 + 130"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 407", "Answer": "A: 1160", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 0 = 50\n3 + 7 = 10\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 120", "Answer": "A: 332", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n12 + 20 = 32\n300 + 32"}
{"Question": "Q: 656 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n50 + 8 = 58  \n1500 + 58 = 1558  \n1558 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 487", "Answer": "A: 732", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 80 = 120\n5 + 7 = 12\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 648", "Answer": "A: 1438", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 40 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 775", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n9 + 70 = 79\n1100 + 79 = 1179\n1179 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 357", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 160 + 694", "Answer": "A: 854", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 90 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 115", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n20 + 10 = 30\n8 + 5 = 13\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 482", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n40 + 80 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 9\n920 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 393 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 20 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 358", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 824", "Answer": "A: 1156", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 20 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 430", "Answer": "A: 562", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 30 = 60\n500 + 60 = 560\n560 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1277", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 476 + 497", "Answer": "A: 973", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n800 + 160 = 960  \n960 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 335", "Answer": "A: 948", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n10 + 30 = 40\n3 + 5 = 8\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 210 + 564", "Answer": "A: 774", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n10 + 60 = 70\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1658", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n30 + 20 = 50  \n1600 + 50 = 1650  \n1650 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 152 + 676", "Answer": "A: 828", "Explanation": "150 + 670 = 820\n2 + 6 = 8\n820 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 871", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n10 + 70 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 469", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n2 + 60 = 62\n700 + 62 = 762\n762 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 907", "Answer": "A: 1397", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n90 + 7 = 97\n1300 + 97"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 107", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 0 = 60\n6 + 7 = 13\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 435 + 446", "Answer": "A: 881", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n5 + 6 = 11\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 355", "Answer": "A: 456", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n1 + 50 = 51\n400 + 51 = 451\n451 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 188", "Answer": "A: 343", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n50 + 80 = 130  \n200 + 130 = 330  \n330 + 13 = 343"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 521", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 3 = 863 \n863 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 357", "Answer": "A: 469", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 50 = 60\n400 + 60 = 460\n2 + 7 = 9\n460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 781 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1767", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1 + 6 = 7\n1760 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 129 + 456", "Answer": "A: 585", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 50 = 70\n9 + 6 = 15\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1821", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n16 + 5 = 21\n1800 + 21"}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 366", "Answer": "A: 1314", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n40 + 60 = 100  \n1200 + 100 = 1300  \n1300 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 2 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 110", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 20 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 186", "Answer": "A: 545", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 80 = 130\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 9 = 539\n539 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 351", "Answer": "A: 517", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n60 + 50 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 662", "Answer": "A: 1595", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n30 + 60 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 222 + 712", "Answer": "A: 934", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900  \n22 + 10 = 32  \n900 + 32 = 932  \n932 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 327 + 364", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n20 + 60 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 592 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1274", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 80 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 790 + 530", "Answer": "A: 1320", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 389", "Answer": "A: 1142", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 327", "Answer": "A: 692", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 20 = 80\n5 + 7 = 12\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 412", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 104 + 692", "Answer": "A: 796", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n4 + 90 = 94\n700 + 94 = 794\n794 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 332", "Answer": "A: 847", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n15 + 30 = 45\n800 + 45 = 845\n845 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 294", "Answer": "A: 819", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 90 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 9\n9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n7 + 2 = 9\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 385 + 478", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "800 + 60 = 860\n3 + 5 = 8\n860 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 190", "Answer": "A: 1081", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1471", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 0 = 60\n3 + 8 = 11\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 999 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n90 + 80 = 170\n1200 + 170 = 1370\n1370 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 386", "Answer": "A: 577", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n90 + 80 = 170  \n400 + 170 = 570  \n570 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 416 + 520", "Answer": "A: 936", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n16 + 20 = 36\n900 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n18 + 70 = 88\n1100 + 88 = 1188\n1188 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 362 + 614", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 432", "Answer": "A: 1186", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n4 + 2 = 6\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1713", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600  \n50 + 60 = 110  \n1600 + 110 = 1710  \n1710 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 518", "Answer": "A: 727", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n9 + 10 = 19\n700 + 19 = 719\n719 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 943", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 40 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 384 + 823", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 20 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 3 + 4 = 1207"}
{"Question": "Q: 283 + 129", "Answer": "A: 412", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n80 + 20 = 100\n3 + 9 = 12\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 603 + 614", "Answer": "A: 1217", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n3 + 10 = 13\n1200 + 13 = 1213\n1213 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 400", "Answer": "A: 659", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 9 = 59\n600 + 59"}
{"Question": "Q: 612 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n10 + 30 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 825", "Answer": "A: 1188", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n60 + 20 = 80\n3 + 5 = 8\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 154", "Answer": "A: 1083", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n9 + 4 = 13\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 206 + 571", "Answer": "A: 777", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n6 + 70 = 76\n700 + 76 = 776\n776 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 171", "Answer": "A: 758", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n87 + 70 = 157  \n600 + 157 = 757  \n757 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 485 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 50 = 130\n1300 + 130 = 1430\n1430 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 60 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 592", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n30 + 90 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 298", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n600 + 160 = 760  \n760 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 679 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1621", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 40 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 622", "Answer": "A: 853", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 646", "Answer": "A: 1237", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 477", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 70 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 9 \n1190 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 331", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n55 + 30 = 85\n1200 + 85 = 1285\n1285 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 900", "Answer": "A: 1506", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n6 + 0 = 6\n1500 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 399", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n\n70 + 90 = 160\n\n900 + 160 = 1060\n\n1060 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 104", "Answer": "A: 950", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 4 = 44\n900 + 44 = 944\n944 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 129", "Answer": "A: 504", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n70 + 20 = 90  \n5 + 9 = 14  \n400 + 90 = 490  \n490 + 14  "}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1158", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n48 + 10 = 58\n1100 + 58 = 1158"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 312", "Answer": "A: 962", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 257 + 195", "Answer": "A: 452", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n50 + 90 = 140\n300 + 140 = 440\n440 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 536", "Answer": "A: 670", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 6 = 10\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 281 + 793", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 412 + 928", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1002", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n1 + 1 = 2\n1000 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 295", "Answer": "A: 536", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1 + 5 = 6\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 157", "Answer": "A: 616", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 7 = 16\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 230", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 30 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 250 + 125", "Answer": "A: 375", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n50 + 20 = 70\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 678", "Answer": "A: 899", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n20 + 70 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 685 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1640", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 50 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 772 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1163", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 40 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 689", "Answer": "A: 794", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n5 + 80 = 85\n700 + 85 = 785\n785 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 268 + 382", "Answer": "A: 650", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 10 = 650"}
{"Question": "Q: 155 + 477", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1495", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n50 + 30 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1060", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n1 + 59 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 119", "Answer": "A: 1104", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 945 + 254", "Answer": "A: 1199", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1542", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n1400 + 130 = 1530  \n1530 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 307", "Answer": "A: 675", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600  \n60 + 7 = 67  \n600 + 67 = 667  \n667 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 391", "Answer": "A: 1020", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900  \n20 + 90 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 405", "Answer": "A: 519", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n14 + 5 = 19\n500 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 231", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 30 = 100\n6 + 1 = 7\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 357", "Answer": "A: 1120", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 319", "Answer": "A: 436", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n10 + 10 = 20\n7 + 9 = 16\n400 + 20 = 420\n420 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 40 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 426", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n20 + 20 = 40  \n1200 + 40 = 1240  \n1240 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 850", "Answer": "A: 959", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n9 + 50 = 59\n900 + 59"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 774", "Answer": "A: 893", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n10 + 70 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 9 + 4 = 893"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 882", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n9 + 80 = 89\n900 + 89 = 989\n989 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 271", "Answer": "A: 628", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 70 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 256", "Answer": "A: 358", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n2 + 50 = 52\n300 + 52 = 352\n352 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 170", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140"}
{"Question": "Q: 477 + 283", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 80 = 150\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 10 = 760\n760"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n40 + 20 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 712 + 506", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n10 + 6 = 16\n1200 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 583 + 615", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n1100 + 90 = 1190  \n1190 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 328", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 20 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 732", "Answer": "A: 863", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 30 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 1\n860 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 187 + 812", "Answer": "A: 999", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n80 + 10 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 7 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 818 + 308", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n18 + 8 = 26\n1100 + 26"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 387", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n50 + 80 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 532", "Answer": "A: 1389", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 30 = 80\n7 + 2 = 9\n1300 + 80 = 1380\n1380 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1639", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 90 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 90 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 712", "Answer": "A: 1697", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 2 = 7\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 202", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 2 = 22\n1000 + 22 = 1022\n1022 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 719", "Answer": "A: 1481", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n60 + 10 = 70\n2 + 9 = 11\n1400 + 70 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1339", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 461 + 253", "Answer": "A: 714", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 138", "Answer": "A: 664", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 30 = 50\n6 + 8 = 14\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 186", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n20 + 80 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 174 + 314", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 10 = 80\n4 + 4 = 8\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n20 + 20 = 40\n3 + 8 = 11\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1419", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n20 + 50 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 587", "Answer": "A: 849", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 147 + 331", "Answer": "A: 478", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n40 + 30 = 70\n7 + 1 = 8\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 226", "Answer": "A: 717", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n90 + 20 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 400 + 629", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n29\n1000 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 926 + 746", "Answer": "A: 1672", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 40 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 682 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1299", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 10 = 90\n2 + 7 = 9\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 799", "Answer": "A: 1205", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n6 + 90 = 96\n1100 + 96 = 1196\n1196 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1707", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 80 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 812 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1432", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n12 + 20 = 32\n1400 + 32"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1335", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 80 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 218", "Answer": "A: 1089", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 519", "Answer": "A: 1308", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n9 + 9 = 18  \n1200 + 90 = 1290  \n1290 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 512 + 517", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 10 = 20\n2 + 7 = 9\n1000 + 20 = 1020\n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 323", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 698 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1652", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 50 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 136 + 359", "Answer": "A: 495", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n400 + 80 = 480  \n480 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 760", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 2 = 72\n900 + 72 = 972\n972 + 60"}
{"Question": "Q: 745 + 842", "Answer": "A: 1587", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 2 = 7\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 285", "Answer": "A: 496", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n11 + 80 = 91\n400 + 91 = 491\n491 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 286", "Answer": "A: 1251", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 80 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 513", "Answer": "A: 1111", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 10 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n8 + 3 = 11\n1100 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 145", "Answer": "A: 445", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n45 + 0 = 45\n400 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1551", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 4 = 44\n1500 + 44 = 1544\n1544 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 265", "Answer": "A: 788", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 60 = 80\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 9 + 1 = 1240"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 653", "Answer": "A: 1244", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 50 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 585", "Answer": "A: 1358", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 3 + 5 "}
{"Question": "Q: 824 + 806", "Answer": "A: 1630", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 6 = 26\n1600 + 26 = 1626\n1626 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 981", "Answer": "A: 1588", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n7 + 80 = 87\n1500 + 87 = 1587\n1587 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 106 + 493", "Answer": "A: 599", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n6 + 90 = 96\n500 + 96 = 596\n596 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1677", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 10 = 60\n9 + 8 = 17\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 392", "Answer": "A: 737", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 2 = 7\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 519", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n9 + 10 = 19\n700 + 19 = 719\n719 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 936 + 187", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 6 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 369 + 639", "Answer": "A: 1008", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 925", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n6 + 20 = 26\n1300 + 26 = 1326\n1326 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 180", "Answer": "A: 512", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n32 + 80 = 112\n400 + 112"}
{"Question": "Q: 504 + 937", "Answer": "A: 1441", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n4 + 30 = 34\n1400 + 34 = 1434\n1434 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 208", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 8 = 38\n800 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n30 + 7 = 37\n1000 + 37 = 1037\n1037 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 859 + 359", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 341", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 305", "Answer": "A: 1068", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n60 + 0 = 60  \n3 + 5 = 8  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1164", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 0 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 875 + 500", "Answer": "A: 1375", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n75 \n1300 + 75"}
{"Question": "Q: 262 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1143", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 507", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 7 = 67\n900 + 67"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 169", "Answer": "A: 658", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n80 + 60 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 9\n640 + 9 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 250", "Answer": "A: 629", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n70 + 50 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 461", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 214", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 4 = 1034\n1034 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 333 + 883", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 248", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 40 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 141 + 479", "Answer": "A: 620", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 70 = 110\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 861 + 353", "Answer": "A: 1214", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n50 + 2 = 52\n1300 + 52 = 1352\n1352 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1734", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n70 + 50 = 120\n9 + 5 = 14\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n2 + 30 = 32\n1300 + 32 = 1332\n1332 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1408", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n2 + 6 = 8\n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 971 + 247", "Answer": "A: 1218", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 640 + 199", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1483", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 950 + 423", "Answer": "A: 1373", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 20 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 139", "Answer": "A: 766", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 30 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 479 + 316", "Answer": "A: 795", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n9 + 6 = 15  \n700 + 80 = 780  \n780 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 664", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n19 + 60 = 79\n1300 + 79 = 1379\n1379 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 570 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1099", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n70 + 20 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 975", "Answer": "A: 1363", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n80 + 70 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 332 + 228", "Answer": "A: 560", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n30 + 20 = 50\n2 + 8 = 10\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 428 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 50 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 483", "Answer": "A: 669", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n80 + 80 = 160  \n6 + 3 = 9  \n500 + 160 = 660  \n660 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 804 + 522", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n4 + 20 = 24\n1300 + 24 = 1324\n1324 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 398 + 120", "Answer": "A: 518", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n98 + 20 = 118\n400 + 118"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 843", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n10 + 40 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 261", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5\n1140 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 450", "Answer": "A: 711", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 50 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 829 + 763", "Answer": "A: 1592", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 60 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 295", "Answer": "A: 953", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n50 + 90 = 140  \n800 + 140 = 940  \n940 + 8 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n40 + 90 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 3  "}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 179", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n9 + 9 = 18\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 249", "Answer": "A: 1189", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 601 + 708", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n1 + 8 = 9\n1300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 759 + 385", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n50 + 80 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9 + 5 = 1130 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1544", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n70 + 70 = 140  \n1400 + 140 = 1540  \n1540 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 496 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 811", "Answer": "A: 1641", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1570", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n10 + 50 = 60  \n1500 + 60 = 1560  \n1560 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 833 + 259", "Answer": "A: 1092", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 50 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 561", "Answer": "A: 1425", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n60 + 50 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1416", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 40 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 585 + 387", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n80 + 5 = 85\n85 + 7 = 92\n800 + 92"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 163", "Answer": "A: 1035", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 60 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 3 = 1033\n1033 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 550", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n50 + 50 = 100\n800 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 204", "Answer": "A: 347", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 4 = 44\n300 + 44 = 344\n344 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 273 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 10 = 1260\n1260 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 186", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n6 + 80 = 86\n500 + 86 = 586\n586 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 120", "Answer": "A: 686", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n60 + 20 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 122", "Answer": "A: 326", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n4 + 20 = 24\n300 + 24 = 324\n324 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 324 + 578", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 519 + 179", "Answer": "A: 698", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n19 + 70 = 89\n600 + 89 = 689\n689 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 703", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n3 + 3 = 6\n900 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 846 + 916", "Answer": "A: 1762", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700  \n40 + 10 = 50  \n1700 + 50 = 1750  \n1750 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 115", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 10 = 90\n400 + 90 = 490\n490 + 6\n496 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 224 + 316", "Answer": "A: 540", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n4 + 6 = 10\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 287 + 434", "Answer": "A: 721", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 30 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 123 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n20 + 70 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 249", "Answer": "A: 454", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n5 + 40 = 45\n400 + 45 = 445\n445 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 951", "Answer": "A: 1705", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 50 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 4\n1704 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 153", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 50 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 5 = 995\n995 - 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 528", "Answer": "A: 1482", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 20 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 322 + 117", "Answer": "A: 439", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n20 + 10 = 30\n2 + 7 = 9\n400 + 30 = 430\n430 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 974 + 768", "Answer": "A: 1742", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 490 + 432", "Answer": "A: 922", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 687 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1231", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 746", "Answer": "A: 902", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 40 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 259 + 107", "Answer": "A: 366", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n50 + 7 = 57\n300 + 57 = 357\n357 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 515 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n15 + 70 = 85\n1300 + 85 = 1385\n1385 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1638", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n16 + 20 = 36\n1600 + 36"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 820", "Answer": "A: 1662", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 20 = 60\n1600 + 60 = 1660\n1660 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 812", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n80 + 10 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 9 = 1049"}
{"Question": "Q: 381 + 670", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n80 + 70 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 373 + 804", "Answer": "A: 1177", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 4 = 74\n1100 + 74 = 1174\n1174 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 266", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1568", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n9 + 50 = 59\n1500 + 59 = 1559\n1559 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 469", "Answer": "A: 1285", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 678 + 577", "Answer": "A: 1255", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n8 + 7 = 15\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 672", "Answer": "A: 1517", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400  \n40 + 70 = 110  \n1400 + 110 = 1510  \n1510 + 7  "}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 800", "Answer": "A: 912", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n12\n900 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 223 + 244", "Answer": "A: 467", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n20 + 40 = 60\n3 + 4 = 7\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 157 + 901", "Answer": "A: 1058", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 1 = 51\n1000 + 51 = 1051\n1051 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 868", "Answer": "A: 1466", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n90 + 60 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 181", "Answer": "A: 918", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 80 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 989 + 578", "Answer": "A: 1567", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 70 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 9 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 276", "Answer": "A: 837", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 873 + 570", "Answer": "A: 1443", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 70 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 328", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 464", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n6 + 60 = 66\n700 + 66 = 766\n766 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 310", "Answer": "A: 584", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n70 + 10 = 80\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 251 + 729", "Answer": "A: 980", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9 = 979\n979 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 143 + 442", "Answer": "A: 585", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 2 = 5\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 642 + 761", "Answer": "A: 1403", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 226 + 463", "Answer": "A: 689", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n20 + 60 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 412 + 358", "Answer": "A: 770", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n10 + 50 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 2 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 307 + 125", "Answer": "A: 432", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n7 + 20 = 27\n400 + 27 = 427\n427 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 787 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1684", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 90 = 170\n7 + 7 = 14\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 980", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000  \n18 + 80 = 98  \n1000 + 98 "}
{"Question": "Q: 419 + 236", "Answer": "A: 655", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 30 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 334 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 70 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 4 = 1104\n1104 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 368 + 524", "Answer": "A: 892", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 582", "Answer": "A: 1549", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 9 = 1549\n1549 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 223", "Answer": "A: 1129", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n6 + 20 = 26\n1100 + 26 = 1126\n1126 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n40 + 50 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 371", "Answer": "A: 803", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n30 + 70 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 825 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1779", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n20 + 50 = 70\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 529 + 153", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 50 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 267", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n10 + 60 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 854 + 171", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 4 + 1 = 1025"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 440", "Answer": "A: 556", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n16 + 40 = 56\n500 + 56"}
{"Question": "Q: 761 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1286", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 1 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1155", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 914", "Answer": "A: 1534", "Explanation": "620 + 900 = 1520\n20 + 14 = 34\n1520 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 927 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1382", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n20 + 50 = 70\n1300 + 70 = 1370\n1370 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n70 + 30 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 218 + 967", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n18 + 60 = 78\n1100 + 78 = 1178\n1178 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 944 + 365", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 60 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 638 + 736", "Answer": "A: 1374", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 277 + 422", "Answer": "A: 699", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 20 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 7 + 2 = 699"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 942", "Answer": "A: 1777", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 40 = 70\n5 + 2 = 7\n1700 + 70 = 1770\n1770 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 396", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 90 = 150\n5 + 6 = 11\n600 + 150 = 750\n750 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 445 + 399", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 90 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 5 = 835\n835 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 780 + 239", "Answer": "A: 1019", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n80 + 30 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 9 "}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 699", "Answer": "A: 1113", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 90 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n4 + 9 = 13\n1100 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 221 + 751", "Answer": "A: 972", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n20 + 50 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 721", "Answer": "A: 987", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 976 + 230", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 30 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 175 + 365", "Answer": "A: 540", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 60 = 130\n5 + 5 = 10\n400 + 130 = 530\n530 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 921 + 720", "Answer": "A: 1641", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 20 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 669 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1157", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 9 \n1140 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 726 + 633", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 6 + 3\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 783", "Answer": "A: 1662", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 80 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n50 + 70 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 362", "Answer": "A: 1222", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 626", "Answer": "A: 1203", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n7 + 6 = 13\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 444", "Answer": "A: 726", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 40 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 483", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 80 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1 + 3 = 4\n1000 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 423", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n3 + 3 = 6\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 864 + 476", "Answer": "A: 1340", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n1200 + 130 = 1330  \n1330 + 10 = 1340  "}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1529", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 80 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 796", "Answer": "A: 1302", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n6 + 90 = 96\n1200 + 96 = 1296\n1296 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 547", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 798", "Answer": "A: 928", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 98 = 128\n800 + 128 = 928"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 603", "Answer": "A: 720", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n17 + 3 = 20\n700 + 20"}
{"Question": "Q: 665 + 179", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 5 \n830 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 154 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1125", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 70 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 4 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 442 + 525", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 544", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 40 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 756 + 316", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n50 + 10 = 60  \n6 + 6 = 12  \n1000 + 60 = 1060  \n1060 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 102 + 577", "Answer": "A: 679", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n2 + 70 = 72\n600 + 72 = 672\n672 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 242", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 40 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 468", "Answer": "A: 1226", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n50 + 60 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 852 + 124", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 343", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1492", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 5 = 12\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 596", "Answer": "A: 931", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 253 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1032", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n50 + 70 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 452", "Answer": "A: 1294", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n40 + 50 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 487", "Answer": "A: 1063", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n70 + 80 = 150\n900 + 150 = 1050\n1050 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 241", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 40 = 60\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 320", "Answer": "A: 729", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n9 + 20 = 29  \n700 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 261 + 111", "Answer": "A: 372", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 10 = 70\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 291", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n1100 + 150 = 1250  \n1250 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 139", "Answer": "A: 515", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n6 + 9 = 15\n500 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 655", "Answer": "A: 1330", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n75 + 50 = 125\n1200 + 125 = 1325\n1325 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 459 + 555", "Answer": "A: 1014", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n50 + 50 = 100  \n9 + 5 = 14  \n900 + 100 = 1000  \n1000 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 598", "Answer": "A: 1078", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 90 = 170\n900 + 170 = 1070\n1070 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 244", "Answer": "A: 768", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 4 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 670 + 647", "Answer": "A: 1317", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n70 + 40 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 100", "Answer": "A: 617", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n17 \n600 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 521 + 746", "Answer": "A: 1267", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n20 + 40 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 452", "Answer": "A: 608", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n50 + 50 = 100  \n6 + 2 = 8  \n500 + 100 = 600  \n600 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 169 + 681", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n60 + 80 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 9 + 1 = 850"}
{"Question": "Q: 429 + 342", "Answer": "A: 771", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n9 + 2 = 11\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 219", "Answer": "A: 824", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n5 + 19 = 24\n800 + 24"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 227", "Answer": "A: 367", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 413", "Answer": "A: 852", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n30 + 10 = 40\n9 + 3 = 12\n800 + 40 = 840\n840 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1535", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n70 + 60 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 552 + 869", "Answer": "A: 1421", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 248 + 239", "Answer": "A: 487", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 30 = 70\n8 + 9 = 17\n400 + 70 = 470\n470 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 809 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1753", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n9 + 40 = 49\n1700 + 49 = 1749\n1749 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 20 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n2 + 7 = 9\n1400 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 531", "Answer": "A: 1402", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 1 \n1400 + 1 = "}
{"Question": "Q: 470 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1356", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 211", "Answer": "A: 601", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 10 = 100\n500 + 100 = 600\n600 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 724 + 773", "Answer": "A: 1497", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 966 + 747", "Answer": "A: 1713", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n60 + 40 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 6 \n1700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 243", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 40 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 7 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 40 = 70\n7 + 5 = 12\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 741", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n80 + 40 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 598 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1166", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n90 + 60 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 708 + 136", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n8 + 30 = 38  \n800 + 38 = 838  \n838 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 293", "Answer": "A: 1084", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 90 = 180\n900 + 180 = 1080\n1080 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 620", "Answer": "A: 1563", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 286", "Answer": "A: 488", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n2 + 80 = 82\n400 + 82 = 482\n482 + 6\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 111", "Answer": "A: 869", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n50 + 10 = 60  \n8 + 1 = 9  \n800 + 60 = 860  \n860 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 758 + 507", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n8 + 7 = 15\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 757 + 225", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 20 = 70\n7 + 5 = 12\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1132", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n10 + 10 = 20\n1100 + 20 = 1120\n1120 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 186 + 336", "Answer": "A: 522", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n400 + 110 = 510  \n510 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 267 + 953", "Answer": "A: 1220", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n60 + 50 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 7 + 3 = 1220"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 586", "Answer": "A: 1423", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 80 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 729 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1365", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 926", "Answer": "A: 1763", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 20 = 50\n7 + 6 = 13\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 495", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n60 + 90 = 150\n700 + 150 = 850\n850 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 390", "Answer": "A: 1126", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n30 + 90 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 747 + 405", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100  \n47 + 5 = 52  \n1100 + 52"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 342", "Answer": "A: 841", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700  \n90 + 40 = 130  \n9 + 2 = 11  \n700 + 130 = 830  \n830 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 323 + 905", "Answer": "A: 1228", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n20 + 5 = 25\n1200 + 25 = 1225\n1225 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 571 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1564", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n1400 + 160 = 1560  \n1560 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 893 + 508", "Answer": "A: 1401", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 0 = 90\n3 + 8 = 11\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 299 + 148", "Answer": "A: 447", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n99 + 48 = 147\n300 + 147 = 447\n447 - 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 777 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1300 + 100 = 1400  \n1400 + 7 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 171 + 203", "Answer": "A: 374", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n70 + 3 = 73\n300 + 73 = 373\n373 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 814", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 4 = 11\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 133", "Answer": "A: 1100", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 30 = 90\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 7\n1090 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 473", "Answer": "A: 592", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n10 + 70 = 80\n9 + 3 = 12\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 152", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n94 + 50 = 144\n800 + 144 = 944\n944 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 364 + 624", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1368", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 10 = 60\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 718 + 222", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n18 + 20 = 38\n900 + 38 = 938\n938 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 487 + 758", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n7 + 8 = 15\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 336 + 704", "Answer": "A: 1040", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n30 + 4 = 34\n1000 + 34 = 1034\n1034 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 408", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n19 + 8 = 27\n1000 + 27"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 210", "Answer": "A: 530", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n500 + 30"}
{"Question": "Q: 620 + 218", "Answer": "A: 838", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 18 = 38\n800 + 38"}
{"Question": "Q: 904 + 486", "Answer": "A: 1390", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n4 + 80 = 84\n1300 + 84 = 1384\n1384 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 105 + 687", "Answer": "A: 792", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n5 + 80 = 85\n700 + 85 = 785\n785 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 304 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1135", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n4 + 30 = 34\n1100 + 34 = 1134\n1134 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 629 + 874", "Answer": "A: 1503", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n20 + 70 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 709 + 551", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200  \n9 + 50 = 59  \n1200 + 59 = 1259  \n1259 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1418", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300  \n70 + 30 = 100  \n1300 + 100 = 1400  \n1400 + 9  \n1400 + 19"}
{"Question": "Q: 482 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 80 = 160\n1300 + 160 = 1460\n1460 + 2 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 103", "Answer": "A: 236", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 3 = 33\n200 + 33"}
{"Question": "Q: 246 + 779", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 70 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 245", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n1 + 5 = 6\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 133 + 191", "Answer": "A: 324", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n30 + 90 = 120  \n200 + 120 = 320  \n320 + 3 + 1 "}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 381", "Answer": "A: 1354", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 179", "Answer": "A: 943", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 70 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 4 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 616 + 552", "Answer": "A: 1168", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n10 + 50 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 314 + 108", "Answer": "A: 422", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n14 + 8 = 22\n400 + 22"}
{"Question": "Q: 675 + 319", "Answer": "A: 994", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n5 + 9 = 14\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 233", "Answer": "A: 432", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n90 + 30 = 120\n9 + 3 = 12\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 448 + 878", "Answer": "A: 1326", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 954", "Answer": "A: 1409", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 316 + 175", "Answer": "A: 491", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n16 + 70 = 86\n400 + 86 = 486\n486 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 285", "Answer": "A: 1257", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 7 = 1257\n1257 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 567 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 236", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 30 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 317", "Answer": "A: 1290", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 10 = 1290"}
{"Question": "Q: 510 + 572", "Answer": "A: 1082", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n10 + 70 = 80\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 103 + 582", "Answer": "A: 685", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n3 + 80 = 83\n600 + 83 = 683\n683 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 552", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 50 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 10 = 690"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 164", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 60 = 80\n5 + 4 = 9\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 672 + 732", "Answer": "A: 1404", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n70 + 30 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 253", "Answer": "A: 1046", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 3 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 821 + 853", "Answer": "A: 1674", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 50 = 70\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 1 + 3 = 1674"}
{"Question": "Q: 272 + 543", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n70 + 40 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n90 + 9 = 99  \n1000 + 99 = 1099  \n1099 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 576", "Answer": "A: 1407", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n30 + 70 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1139", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 40 = 130\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 715 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1148", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n15 + 30 = 45\n1100 + 45 = 1145\n1145 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 205 + 246", "Answer": "A: 451", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n5 + 40 = 45\n400 + 45 = 445\n445 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 156", "Answer": "A: 589", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n30 + 50 = 80\n3 + 6 = 9\n500 + 80 = 580\n580 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 233", "Answer": "A: 1219", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 878 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1857", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 70 = 140\n1700 + 140 = 1840\n8 + 9 = 17\n1840 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 266 + 861", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 568", "Answer": "A: 1057", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n80 + 60 = 140\n9 + 8 = 17\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1448", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n50 + 90 = 140\n1300 + 140 = 1440\n1440 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 713 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n10 + 90 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 3 \n1400 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 406 + 551", "Answer": "A: 957", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900  \n6 + 50 = 56  \n900 + 56 = 956  \n956 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n70 + 40 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6\n1010 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 464 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1429", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n60 + 60 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 712", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 302", "Answer": "A: 1098", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n90 + 0 = 90\n6 + 2 = 8\n1000 + 90 = 1090\n1090 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 188 + 110", "Answer": "A: 298", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n88 + 10 = 98\n200 + 98 = 298\n298 - 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 999", "Answer": "A: 1876", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 90 = 160\n7 + 9 = 16\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 876 + 866", "Answer": "A: 1742", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n6 + 6 = 12\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 298", "Answer": "A: 1029", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 426", "Answer": "A: 678", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 266", "Answer": "A: 806", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 60 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 126", "Answer": "A: 874", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 633 + 265", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n30 + 60 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 606 + 172", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n6 + 70 = 76  \n700 + 76 = 776  \n776 + 2  "}
{"Question": "Q: 948 + 234", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 30 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 931", "Answer": "A: 1620", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n1500 + 110 = 1610  \n1610 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 376 + 995", "Answer": "A: 1371", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200  \n76 + 95 = 171  \n1200 + 171  "}
{"Question": "Q: 955 + 328", "Answer": "A: 1283", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n50 + 20 = 70\n5 + 8 = 13\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 258 + 863", "Answer": "A: 1121", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 282 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 680", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n70 + 80 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 856", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200  \n20 + 50 = 70    \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 6 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 180", "Answer": "A: 1159", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 505 + 663", "Answer": "A: 1168", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n5 + 60 = 65\n1100 + 65 = 1165\n1165 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 320 + 751", "Answer": "A: 1071", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 202 + 627", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n2 + 20 = 22\n800 + 22 = 822\n822 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 242 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n40 + 7 = 47\n1000 + 47 = 1047\n1047 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 520", "Answer": "A: 701", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 20 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 884 + 283", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 80 = 160\n3 + 3 = 6\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 249", "Answer": "A: 1191", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n2 + 9 = 11\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 724", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 20 = 60\n8 + 4 = 12\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 119 + 550", "Answer": "A: 669", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n19 + 50 = 69\n600 + 69"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1776", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 90 = 170\n3 + 3 = 6\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 909", "Answer": "A: 1890", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n80 + 0 = 80\n1800 + 80 = 1880\n1880 + 1 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 886 + 545", "Answer": "A: 1431", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n80 + 40 = 120\n6 + 5 = 11\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 200", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n76\n800 + 76"}
{"Question": "Q: 645 + 205", "Answer": "A: 850", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n45 + 5 = 50  \n800 + 50"}
{"Question": "Q: 372 + 111", "Answer": "A: 483", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 10 = 80\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 3 = 483\n483 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 382 + 138", "Answer": "A: 520", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 30 = 110\n400 + 110 = 510\n510 + 10 = 520"}
{"Question": "Q: 865 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1795", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n60 + 30 = 90\n1700 + 90 = 1790\n1790 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 737 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1616", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n30 + 70 = 100  \n7 + 9 = 16  \n1500 + 100 = 1600  \n1600 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 172", "Answer": "A: 696", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n20 + 70 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 767 + 144", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n60 + 40 = 100  \n800 + 100 = 900  \n7 + 4 = 11  \n900 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 602 + 287", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n2 + 80 = 82\n800 + 82 = 882\n882 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 106", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n90 + 6 = 96\n700 + 96 = 796\n796 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 240 + 947", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 837 + 423", "Answer": "A: 1260", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 20 = 50\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 652 + 203", "Answer": "A: 855", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 0 = 50\n2 + 3 = 5\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 340", "Answer": "A: 761", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 890 + 584", "Answer": "A: 1474", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n90 + 80 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 100 + 679", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n79\n700 + 79"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 364", "Answer": "A: 546", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n80 + 60 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 6 = 546\n546 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 399", "Answer": "A: 718", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n19 + 90 = 109\n600 + 109 = 709\n709 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 582 + 694", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 703", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 0 = 60\n6 + 3 = 9\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 943 + 790", "Answer": "A: 1733", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 90 = 130\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 113 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1004", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 342 + 700", "Answer": "A: 1042", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n42 + 0 = 42\n1000 + 42"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 930", "Answer": "A: 1067", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 217", "Answer": "A: 900", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 10 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3\n890 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 828", "Answer": "A: 1684", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n50 + 20 = 70\n6 + 8 = 14\n1600 + 70 = 1670\n1670 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 344 + 977", "Answer": "A: 1321", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n40 + 70 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 820 + 314", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 10 = 30\n1100 + 30 = 1130\n1130 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 195", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n50 + 90 = 140\n1 + 5 = 6\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 211 + 836", "Answer": "A: 1047", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n11 + 30 = 41\n1000 + 41 = 1041\n1041 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 646 + 445", "Answer": "A: 1091", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 40 = 80\n6 + 5 = 11\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 711", "Answer": "A: 1699", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 10 = 90\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 397", "Answer": "A: 929", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n30 + 90 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 7 = 927\n927 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 577 + 595", "Answer": "A: 1172", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n70 + 90 = 160  \n7 + 5 = 12  \n1000 + 160 = 1160  \n1160 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 209", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 0 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 886", "Answer": "A: 1675", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n80 + 80 = 160\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n9 + 6 = 15\n1660 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 532", "Answer": "A: 1511", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n70 + 30 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 9\n1500 + 9 + "}
{"Question": "Q: 604 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n4 + 13 = 17\n1400 + 17 = 1417"}
{"Question": "Q: 626 + 328", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n6 + 8 = 14\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 665 + 463", "Answer": "A: 1128", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n60 + 60 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 5\n1125 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 367 + 624", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n7 + 4 = 11\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 816 + 948", "Answer": "A: 1764", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n16 + 40 = 56\n1700 + 56 = 1756\n1756 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 827", "Answer": "A: 1300", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n70 + 20 = 90\n1200 + 90 = 1290\n1290 + 3 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 979 + 971", "Answer": "A: 1950", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n70 + 70 = 140\n9 + 1 = 10\n1800 + 140 = 1940\n1940 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 329", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n60 + 20 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 10 = 990"}
{"Question": "Q: 199 + 582", "Answer": "A: 781", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n90 + 80 = 170\n600 + 170 = 770\n770 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 252 + 386", "Answer": "A: 638", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n50 + 80 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 8 = 638"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 725", "Answer": "A: 1569", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n4 + 5 = 9\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1347", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n1200 + 140 = 1340  \n1340 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1620", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n50 + 60 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 883 + 465", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 60 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 3 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 630 + 124", "Answer": "A: 754", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 20 = 50\n700 + 50 = 750\n750 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 963", "Answer": "A: 1265", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n2 + 60 = 62\n1200 + 62 = 1262\n1262 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1805", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n3 + 2 = 5\n1800 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 816", "Answer": "A: 995", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n70 + 10 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 850", "Answer": "A: 1077", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 50 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 923 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1914", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800\n20 + 90 = 110\n1800 + 110 = 1910\n1910 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 801 + 144", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n1 + 44 = 45\n900 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 261", "Answer": "A: 889", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 60 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 386 + 190", "Answer": "A: 576", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n80 + 90 = 170\n400 + 170 = 570\n570 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 750 + 559", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 719 + 448", "Answer": "A: 1167", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n19 + 40 = 59\n1100 + 59 = 1159\n1159 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 631 + 722", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n30 + 20 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 335", "Answer": "A: 513", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n8 + 5 = 13\n400 + 100 = 500\n500 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 998", "Answer": "A: 1276", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 90 = 160\n1100 + 160 = 1260\n1260 + 8 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 764 + 986", "Answer": "A: 1750", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n60 + 80 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 929 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1653", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n20 + 20 = 40\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 9 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 778 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1665", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n70 + 80 = 150\n8 + 7 = 15\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 274 + 860", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 434 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1269", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 5 = 9\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 677 + 113", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 10 = 80\n7 + 3 = 10\n700 + 80 = 780\n780 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 624", "Answer": "A: 1034", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n10 + 20 = 30\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 810 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1701", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n10 + 90 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n1700 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 170", "Answer": "A: 307", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 70 = 100\n200 + 100 = 300\n300 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 933 + 380", "Answer": "A: 1313", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n\n30 + 3 = 33\n\n1200 + 33 = 1233\n\n1233 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 525", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n11 + 20 = 31\n1200 + 31 = 1231\n1231 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 101 + 404", "Answer": "A: 505", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n1 + 4 = 5\n500+5"}
{"Question": "Q: 319 + 197", "Answer": "A: 516", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n19 + 90 = 109\n400 + 109 = 509\n509 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 185", "Answer": "A: 333", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200  \n40 + 80 = 120  \n8 + 5 = 13  \n200 + 120 = 320  \n320 + 13  "}
{"Question": "Q: 508 + 872", "Answer": "A: 1380", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n8 + 70 = 78\n1300 + 78 = 1378\n1378 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 796 + 818", "Answer": "A: 1614", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n90 + 10 = 100\n6 + 8 = 14\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 133", "Answer": "A: 347", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n10 + 30 = 40\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 633 + 964", "Answer": "A: 1597", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n30 + 60 = 90\n1500 + 90 = 1590\n1590 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 285 + 831", "Answer": "A: 1116", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n80 + 30 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 785 + 233", "Answer": "A: 1018", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n80 + 30 = 110  \n900 + 110 = 1010  \n1010 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 410 + 593", "Answer": "A: 1003", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 90 = 100\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 247 + 104", "Answer": "A: 351", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n40 + 4 = 44\n300 + 44 = 344\n344 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 847", "Answer": "A: 1192", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n40 + 40 = 80\n5 + 7 = 12\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 605 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1484", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n5 + 70 = 75\n1400 + 75 = 1475\n1475 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 350 + 795", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 90 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 793", "Answer": "A: 1655", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 958 + 257", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 50 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n8 + 7 = 15\n1200 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 332", "Answer": "A: 833", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n1 + 30 = 31\n800 + 31 = 831\n831 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 354", "Answer": "A: 779", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 50 = 70\n5 + 4 = 9\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 964 + 211", "Answer": "A: 1175", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 10 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 4\n1174 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1747", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 90 = 140\n1600 + 140 = 1740\n1740 + 7 = 1747\n1747 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 910", "Answer": "A: 1755", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 10 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 696 + 668", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n90 + 60 = 150  \n1200 + 150 = 1350  \n1350 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 932", "Answer": "A: 1802", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 30 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n1800 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 683", "Answer": "A: 898", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 261", "Answer": "A: 911", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 60 = 110\n800 + 110 = 910\n910 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 176", "Answer": "A: 370", "Explanation": "190 + 170 = 360\n4 + 6 = 10\n360 + 10 = 370"}
{"Question": "Q: 117 + 320", "Answer": "A: 437", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n17 + 20 = 37\n400 + 37"}
{"Question": "Q: 300 + 168", "Answer": "A: 468", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 8 = 68\n400 + 68"}
{"Question": "Q: 802 + 396", "Answer": "A: 1198", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n2 + 90 = 92\n1100 + 92 = 1192\n1192 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 827 + 307", "Answer": "A: 1134", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n20 + 7 = 27\n1100 + 27 = 1127\n1127 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 109 + 132", "Answer": "A: 241", "Explanation": "100 + 30 = 130\n9 + 2 = 11\n130 + 11 = 141\n141 + 100"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 917", "Answer": "A: 1454", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n30 + 10 = 40\n7 + 7 = 14\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 118 + 741", "Answer": "A: 859", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n10 + 40 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 286", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 80 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 668", "Answer": "A: 1535", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n7 + 8 = 15\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 544 + 494", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n4 + 4 = 8\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 951 + 911", "Answer": "A: 1862", "Explanation": "900 + 900 = 1800  \n51 + 10 = 61  \n1800 + 61 = 1861   \n1861 + 1  "}
{"Question": "Q: 813 + 484", "Answer": "A: 1297", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n13 + 80 = 93\n1200 + 93 = 1293\n1293 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 579 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1292", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 10 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 9 + 3\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 354 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1351", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n4 + 7 = 11\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 589 + 183", "Answer": "A: 772", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n80 + 80 = 160\n600 + 160 = 760\n760 + 9 = 769\n769 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 439 + 501", "Answer": "A: 940", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 1 = 31\n900 + 31 = 931\n931 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 748 + 456", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 8 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 389 + 424", "Answer": "A: 813", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 20 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n9 + 4 = 13\n800 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 426 + 312", "Answer": "A: 738", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n20 + 10 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 618 + 727", "Answer": "A: 1345", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n10 + 20 = 30\n1300 + 30 = 1330\n1330 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 219 + 234", "Answer": "A: 453", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n19 + 30 = 49\n400 + 49 = 449\n449 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 763 + 184", "Answer": "A: 947", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 80 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 611 + 114", "Answer": "A: 725", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n10 + 10 = 20\n700 + 20 = 720\n720 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 206", "Answer": "A: 332", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n20 + 6 = 26\n300 + 26 = 326\n326 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 678", "Answer": "A: 1075", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 194 + 875", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 70 = 160\n900 + 160 = 1060\n1060 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 243", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3\n1170 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 687", "Answer": "A: 1480", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n90 + 80 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 593 + 957", "Answer": "A: 1550", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 10 = 1550"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 398", "Answer": "A: 1338", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 388 + 500", "Answer": "A: 888", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n88 + 0 = 88\n800 + 88"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1417", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n1300 + 110 = 1410  \n1410 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 939 + 285", "Answer": "A: 1224", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 132 + 558", "Answer": "A: 690", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n30 + 50 = 80  \n600 + 80 = 680  \n680 + 10 = 690"}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 730", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 286 + 442", "Answer": "A: 728", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n80 + 40 = 120\n600 + 120 = 720\n720 + 6 + 2 "}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 993", "Answer": "A: 1685", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500  \n90 + 90 = 180   \n1500 + 180 = 1680  \n1680 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 131 + 526", "Answer": "A: 657", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n30 + 20 = 50\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 965", "Answer": "A: 1527", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 137 + 723", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n30 + 20 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 891", "Answer": "A: 1572", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n1400 + 170 = 1570  \n1570 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 782", "Answer": "A: 1763", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 2 = 82\n1600 + 82 = 1682\n1682 + 81"}
{"Question": "Q: 954 + 562", "Answer": "A: 1516", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n50 + 60 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 905 + 490", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n5 + 90 = 95\n1300 + 95"}
{"Question": "Q: 315 + 571", "Answer": "A: 886", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n10 + 70 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 694 + 536", "Answer": "A: 1230", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 30 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 4 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 760 + 278", "Answer": "A: 1038", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n900 + 130 = 1030  \n1030 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 178 + 470", "Answer": "A: 648", "Explanation": "600 + 40 = 640\n70 + 8 = 78\n640 + 78"}
{"Question": "Q: 946 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1413", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n40 + 60 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 6\n1400 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 776 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1315", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 30 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n6 + 9 = 15\n1300 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 321 + 231", "Answer": "A: 552", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n20 + 30 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 901 + 564", "Answer": "A: 1465", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n1 + 60 = 61\n1400 + 61 = 1461\n1461 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 723 + 800", "Answer": "A: 1523", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n23 + 0 = 23\n1500 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 794 + 759", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n90 + 50 = 140\n4 + 9 = 13\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 345", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100  \n30 + 6 = 36  \n36 + 40 = 76  \n1100 + 76 = 1176  \n1176 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 644", "Answer": "A: 769", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n20 + 40 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 305", "Answer": "A: 575", "Explanation": "270 + 300 = 570\n570 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 321", "Answer": "A: 884", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n60 + 20 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 889 + 393", "Answer": "A: 1282", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 90 = 170\n1100 + 170 = 1270\n1270 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 637", "Answer": "A: 1281", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200  \n40 + 30 = 70  \n4 + 7 = 11  \n1200 + 70 = 1270  \n1270 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 477", "Answer": "A: 1383", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n6 + 70 = 76\n1300 + 76 = 1376\n1376 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 414 + 549", "Answer": "A: 963", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 40 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 9 \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 643 + 342", "Answer": "A: 985", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n3 + 2 = 5\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 674 + 103", "Answer": "A: 777", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n70 + 3 = 73\n700 + 73 = 773\n773 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 997 + 654", "Answer": "A: 1651", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 50 = 140\n7 + 4 = 11\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 337", "Answer": "A: 667", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 30 = 60\n7\n600 + 60 = 660\n660 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 877 + 297", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 90 = 160\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 7 + 7 = 1174"}
{"Question": "Q: 676 + 263", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 848 + 143", "Answer": "A: 991", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900  \n40 + 40 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 3   \n  "}
{"Question": "Q: 615 + 881", "Answer": "A: 1496", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n15 + 80 = 95\n1400 + 95 = 1495\n1495 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 941 + 384", "Answer": "A: 1325", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n40 + 80 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 1 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 224", "Answer": "A: 525", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n1 + 20 = 21\n500 + 21 = 521\n521 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 766 + 512", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 773 + 908", "Answer": "A: 1681", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n73 + 8 = 81  \n1600 + 81"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 164", "Answer": "A: 391", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n20 + 60 = 80\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 264", "Answer": "A: 1181", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 4 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 195 + 678", "Answer": "A: 873", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 70 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 5 + 8 = 873"}
{"Question": "Q: 807 + 529", "Answer": "A: 1336", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n7 + 20 = 27\n1300 + 27 = 1327\n1327 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 203", "Answer": "A: 1037", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n30 + 3 = 33\n1000 + 33 = 1033\n1033 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 135 + 123", "Answer": "A: 258", "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n30 + 20 = 50\n5 + 3 = 8\n200 + 50 = 250\n250 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 791 + 130", "Answer": "A: 921", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n90 + 30 = 120\n800 + 120 = 920\n920 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 517 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n17 + 60 = 77\n1100 + 77 = 1177\n1177 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 371", "Answer": "A: 1207", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 6 = 36\n1100 + 36 = 1136\n1136 + 71"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 515", "Answer": "A: 1323", "Explanation": "800 + 500 = 1300\n8 + 15 = 23\n1300 + 23"}
{"Question": "Q: 523 + 225", "Answer": "A: 748", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n20 + 20 = 40\n3 + 5 = 8\n700 + 40 = 740\n740 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 427 + 173", "Answer": "A: 600", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n20 + 70 = 90\n500 + 90 = 590\n590 + 10 = 600"}
{"Question": "Q: 245 + 959", "Answer": "A: 1204", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n40 + 50 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 499 + 425", "Answer": "A: 924", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n90 + 20 = 110  \n9 + 5 = 14  \n800 + 110 = 910  \n910 + 14  "}
{"Question": "Q: 443 + 196", "Answer": "A: 639", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n40 + 90 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 3 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 713", "Answer": "A: 984", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 10 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 695 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1565", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n90 + 70 = 160\n1400 + 160 = 1560\n1560 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 160", "Answer": "A: 399", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 60 = 90\n300 + 90 = 390\n390 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 537 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1290", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n30 + 50 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 614 + 495", "Answer": "A: 1109", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n10 + 90 = 100\n4 + 5 = 9\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 801", "Answer": "A: 1107", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n6 + 1 = 7\n1100 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 126 + 863", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n20 + 60 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 381", "Answer": "A: 894", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n10 + 80 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 922", "Answer": "A: 1428", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n6 + 20 = 26\n1400 + 26 = 1426\n1426 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 879 + 865", "Answer": "A: 1744", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 60 = 130\n9 + 5 = 14\n1600 + 130 = 1730\n1730 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 668", "Answer": "A: 1331", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n60 + 60 = 120\n3 + 8 = 11\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 394 + 193", "Answer": "A: 587", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n90 + 90 = 180\n4 + 3 = 7\n400 + 180 = 580\n580 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 946", "Answer": "A: 1396", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n50 + 40 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 635 + 488", "Answer": "A: 1123", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 80 = 110\n5 + 8 = 13\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 862 + 410", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n60 + 10 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 308 + 328", "Answer": "A: 636", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n8 + 20 = 28\n600 + 28"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 802", "Answer": "A: 1630", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n20 + 2 = 22\n1600 + 22 = 1622\n1622 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 705 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1493", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400  \n5 + 80 = 85  \n1400 + 85 = 1485  \n1485 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 738 + 503", "Answer": "A: 1241", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 0 = 30\n8 + 3 = 11\n1200 + 30 = 1230\n1230 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 212 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1178", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n10 + 60 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 407 + 547", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n7 + 40 = 47\n900 + 47 = 947\n947 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 330 + 125", "Answer": "A: 455", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n30 + 20 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 543", "Answer": "A: 976", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 3 + 3 = 976"}
{"Question": "Q: 692 + 516", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n2 + 6 = 8\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 255 + 104", "Answer": "A: 359", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n50 + 4 = 54\n300 + 54 = 354\n354 + 5 "}
{"Question": "Q: 452 + 326", "Answer": "A: 778", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 20 = 70\n2 + 6 = 8\n700 + 70 = 770\n770 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 553 + 731", "Answer": "A: 1284", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 30 = 80\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 3 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 491 + 499", "Answer": "A: 990", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n90 + 90 = 180\n800 + 180 = 980\n980 + 10 = 990"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 701", "Answer": "A: 1687", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 0 = 80\n6 + 1 = 7\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 433", "Answer": "A: 626", "Explanation": "600 + 20 = 620\n620 + 3 = 623\n623 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 451", "Answer": "A: 1309", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 8 = 58\n1200 + 58 = 1258\n1258 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 595 + 388", "Answer": "A: 983", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 5\n970 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 916 + 234", "Answer": "A: 1150", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n16 + 30 = 46  \n1100 + 46 = 1146  \n1146 + 4  "}
{"Question": "Q: 881 + 335", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 657 + 763", "Answer": "A: 1420", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 356 + 191", "Answer": "A: 547", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n50 + 90 = 140\n400 + 140 = 540\n540 + 6 = 546\n546 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 754 + 661", "Answer": "A: 1415", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 60 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 5 = 1415"}
{"Question": "Q: 465 + 177", "Answer": "A: 642", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 70 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 5 + 7 = 642"}
{"Question": "Q: 731 + 871", "Answer": "A: 1602", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n30 + 70 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 1 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 148 + 484", "Answer": "A: 632", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 80 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 290 + 401", "Answer": "A: 691", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n90 + 1 = 91\n600 + 91"}
{"Question": "Q: 572 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1475", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n70 + 3 = 73\n1400 + 73 = 1473\n1473 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 108", "Answer": "A: 878", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800  \n70 + 8 = 78  \n800 + 78"}
{"Question": "Q: 847 + 107", "Answer": "A: 954", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 7 = 47\n900 + 47 = 947\n947 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 473 + 209", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n70 + 0 = 70\n3 + 9 = 12\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 739", "Answer": "A: 1400", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n60 + 30 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 10 = 1400"}
{"Question": "Q: 191 + 840", "Answer": "A: 1031", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n90 + 40 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 110", "Answer": "A: 343", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 10 = 40\n300 + 40 = 340\n340 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 891 + 136", "Answer": "A: 1027", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n90 + 30 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1\n1021 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 296 + 105", "Answer": "A: 401", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n96 + 5 = 101\n300 + 101"}
{"Question": "Q: 449 + 695", "Answer": "A: 1144", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n40 + 90 = 130\n5 + 9 = 14\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 352", "Answer": "A: 1101", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000  \n49 + 50 = 99  \n1000 + 99 = 1099  \n1099 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 380 + 121", "Answer": "A: 501", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400  \n80 + 20 = 100  \n400 + 100 = 500  \n500 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 416", "Answer": "A: 1043", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n20 + 10 = 30\n7 + 6 = 13\n1000 + 30 = 1030\n1030 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 125", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 20 = 70\n9 + 5 = 14\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 689 + 893", "Answer": "A: 1582", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n80 + 90 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 811 + 467", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n10 + 60 = 70\n1200 + 70 = 1270\n1270 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 917 + 838", "Answer": "A: 1755", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n10 + 30 = 40\n7 + 8 = 15\n1700 + 40 = 1740\n1740 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 474 + 465", "Answer": "A: 939", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n4 + 5 = 9\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 460 + 182", "Answer": "A: 642", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 458 + 100", "Answer": "A: 558", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n58\n500 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 981 + 884", "Answer": "A: 1865", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 80 = 160\n1 + 4 = 5\n1700 + 160\n1860 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 735", "Answer": "A: 1432", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n90 + 30 = 120\n7 + 5 = 12\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 455", "Answer": "A: 1105", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 50 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 114 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1048", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n14 + 30 = 44\n1000 + 44 = 1044\n1044 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 489", "Answer": "A: 1459", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n70 + 80 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 185 + 258", "Answer": "A: 443", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 50 = 130\n300 + 130 = 430\n430 + 5 = 435\n435 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 463 + 180", "Answer": "A: 643", "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n60 + 80 = 140\n500 + 140 = 640\n640 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 179 + 468", "Answer": "A: 647", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n500 + 130 = 630  \n630 + 8  \n630 + 9  \n"}
{"Question": "Q: 826 + 713", "Answer": "A: 1539", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n20 + 10 = 30\n1500 + 30 = 1530\n1530 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 840 + 149", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 872 + 179", "Answer": "A: 1051", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 9\n1040 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 789 + 976", "Answer": "A: 1765", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 70 = 150\n1600 + 150 = 1750\n1750 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 276 + 670", "Answer": "A: 946", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n800 + 130 = 930  \n930 + 16  "}
{"Question": "Q: 270 + 437", "Answer": "A: 707", "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n70 + 30 = 100\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 341 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1062", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 20 = 60\n1 + 1 = 2\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 451 + 379", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 70 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 10 = 830\n830"}
{"Question": "Q: 988 + 565", "Answer": "A: 1553", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n80 + 60 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 203 + 694", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n3 + 90 = 93\n800 + 93 = 893\n893 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 558 + 434", "Answer": "A: 992", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n50 + 30 = 80  \n900 + 80 = 980  \n980 + 8 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 880 + 294", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n1000 + 170 = 1170  \n1170 + 4 "}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 966", "Answer": "A: 1193", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n20 + 60 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 983", "Answer": "A: 1673", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n90 + 80 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 195 + 612", "Answer": "A: 807", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n90 + 10 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n5 + 2 = 7\n800 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 433", "Answer": "A: 1153", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n20 + 30 = 50\n1100 + 50 = 1150\n1150 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 158 + 969", "Answer": "A: 1127", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n50 + 60 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 942 + 563", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 142 + 795", "Answer": "A: 937", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n40 + 90 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 762 + 143", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 40 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n2 + 3 = 5\n900 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 845 + 691", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n40 + 90 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 145", "Answer": "A: 704", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n50 + 40 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 9 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 248", "Answer": "A: 1221", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n70 + 40 = 110  \n1100 + 110 = 1210  \n1210 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 472 + 958", "Answer": "A: 1430", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n70 + 50 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 10 = 1430\n1430"}
{"Question": "Q: 644 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1432", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300\n40 + 80 = 120\n1300 + 120 = 1420\n1420 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 286", "Answer": "A: 645", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n50 + 80 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 9 \n630 + 6 \n630 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 241 + 218", "Answer": "A: 459", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n40 + 10 = 50\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 434", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900  \n91 + 30 = 121  \n900 + 121 = 1021  \n1021 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 663 + 232", "Answer": "A: 895", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n3 + 2 = 5\n800 + 90 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 681 + 228", "Answer": "A: 909", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n80 + 20 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 1 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 637 + 301", "Answer": "A: 938", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n30 + 0 = 30\n7 + 1 = 8\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 607 + 301", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n7 + 1 = 8\n900 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 734", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n40 + 30 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 820", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n20 + 20 = 40\n900 + 40 = 940\n940 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 306 + 846", "Answer": "A: 1152", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n6 + 40 = 46\n1100 + 46 = 1146\n1146 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 779 + 383", "Answer": "A: 1162", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 80 = 150\n1000 + 150 = 1150\n1150 + 9 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 755 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1607", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n50 + 50 = 100\n1500 + 100 = 1600\n1600 + 7 = 1607\n1607 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 265 + 852", "Answer": "A: 1117", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n60 + 50 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 214 + 314", "Answer": "A: 528", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 10 = 20\n4 + 4 = 8\n500 + 20 = 520\n520 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 331 + 987", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8 = 1318"}
{"Question": "Q: 514 + 196", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n14 + 90 = 104\n600 + 104 = 704\n704 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 377 + 745", "Answer": "A: 1122", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 40 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 711 + 778", "Answer": "A: 1489", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n11 + 70 = 81\n1400 + 81 = 1481\n1481 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 617", "Answer": "A: 1208", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n90 + 10 = 100\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 110", "Answer": "A: 966", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n56 + 10 = 66\n900 + 66"}
{"Question": "Q: 217 + 784", "Answer": "A: 1001", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n10 + 80 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 724", "Answer": "A: 1710", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 20 = 100\n1600 + 100 = 1700\n6 + 4 = 10\n1700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 625 + 242", "Answer": "A: 867", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5\n860 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 732 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1455", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n30 + 20 = 50\n2 + 3 = 5\n1400 + 50 = 1450\n1450 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 244 + 318", "Answer": "A: 562", "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n40 + 10 = 50\n500 + 50 = 550\n550 + 4 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 839 + 791", "Answer": "A: 1630", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n30 + 90 = 120\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 808 + 697", "Answer": "A: 1505", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n8 + 90 = 98\n1400 + 98 = 1498\n1498 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 922 + 471", "Answer": "A: 1393", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n1300 + 90 = 1390  \n1390 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 683 + 934", "Answer": "A: 1617", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n80 + 30 = 110\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 695", "Answer": "A: 951", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n50 + 90 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 6\n940 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 204 + 672", "Answer": "A: 876", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n4 + 70 = 74\n800 + 74 = 874\n874 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 746 + 221", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 20 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 432 + 927", "Answer": "A: 1359", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n30 + 20 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 9 = 1359"}
{"Question": "Q: 661 + 162", "Answer": "A: 823", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n60 + 60 = 120  \n700 + 120 = 820  \n820 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 291 + 755", "Answer": "A: 1046", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n90 + 50 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 192 + 984", "Answer": "A: 1176", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 650 + 429", "Answer": "A: 1079", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n50 + 20 = 70\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 521", "Answer": "A: 1461", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 20 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 306", "Answer": "A: 964", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 6 = 56\n900 + 56 = 956\n956 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 509", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n20 + 9 = 29\n1200 + 29"}
{"Question": "Q: 986 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1668", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n80 + 80 = 160\n1500 + 160 = 1660\n1660 + 6 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 397 + 721", "Answer": "A: 1118", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n90 + 20 = 110\n1000 + 110 = 1110\n1110 + 7 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 621 + 619", "Answer": "A: 1240", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n20 + 19 = 39\n1200 + 39 = 1239\n1239 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 271 + 944", "Answer": "A: 1215", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n70 + 40 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 233 + 918", "Answer": "A: 1151", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 10 = 40\n1100 + 40 = 1140\n1140 + 3 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 237 + 945", "Answer": "A: 1182", "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100\n30 + 40 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 5 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 495 + 636", "Answer": "A: 1131", "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n90 + 30 = 120\n5 + 6 = 11\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 116 + 618", "Answer": "A: 734", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n10 + 10 = 20\n700 + 20 = 720\n720 + 6 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 562 + 952", "Answer": "A: 1514", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 50 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 260 + 115", "Answer": "A: 375", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n60 + 10 = 70\n300 + 70 = 370\n370 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 365 + 345", "Answer": "A: 710", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n60 + 40 = 100\n5 + 5 = 10\n600 + 100 = 700\n700 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 892 + 309", "Answer": "A: 1201", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n90 + 9 = 99\n1100 + 99 = 1199\n1199 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 166 + 832", "Answer": "A: 998", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n60 + 30 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 279", "Answer": "A: 785", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n6 + 70 = 76\n700 + 76 = 776\n776 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 239 + 590", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 442", "Answer": "A: 801", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 960 + 113", "Answer": "A: 1073", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 395 + 939", "Answer": "A: 1334", "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 30 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 359 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1069", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n50 + 10 = 60\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 358", "Answer": "A: 958", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 8 = 58\n900 + 58"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1318", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n30 + 80 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 134 + 255", "Answer": "A: 389", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n30 + 50 = 80\n300 + 80 = 380\n380 + 4 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 858 + 475", "Answer": "A: 1333", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 70 = 120\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 8 + 5 = 1333"}
{"Question": "Q: 636 + 833", "Answer": "A: 1469", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n30 + 30 = 60\n1400 + 60 = 1460\n1460 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 215 + 830", "Answer": "A: 1045", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n15 + 30 = 45\n1000 + 45"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 717", "Answer": "A: 1702", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n80 + 10 = 90\n5 + 7 = 12\n1600 + 90 = 1690\n1690 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 455 + 388", "Answer": "A: 843", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n50 + 80 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 13 = 843"}
{"Question": "Q: 690 + 100", "Answer": "A: 790", "Explanation": "690 + 100 = 790"}
{"Question": "Q: 952 + 458", "Answer": "A: 1410", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n50 + 50 = 100\n1300 + 100 = 1400\n1400 + 2 \n1400 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 370 + 154", "Answer": "A: 524", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n70 + 50 = 120\n400 + 120 = 520\n520 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 303 + 232", "Answer": "A: 535", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n3 + 30 = 33\n500 + 33 = 533\n533 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 526 + 822", "Answer": "A: 1348", "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n20 + 20 = 40\n1300 + 40 = 1340\n1340 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 524 + 408", "Answer": "A: 932", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n20 + 8 = 28\n900 + 28 = 928\n928 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 651 + 316", "Answer": "A: 967", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n50 + 10 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 563 + 709", "Answer": "A: 1272", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 0 = 60\n1200 + 60 = 1260\n1260 + 3 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 516", "Answer": "A: 941", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n20 + 10 = 30\n5 + 6 = 11\n900 + 30 = 930\n930 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 540 + 275", "Answer": "A: 815", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n40 + 70 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 740 + 299", "Answer": "A: 1039", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 90 = 130\n900 + 130 = 1030\n1030 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 468 + 873", "Answer": "A: 1341", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 996 + 682", "Answer": "A: 1678", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 80 = 170\n1500 + 170 = 1670\n1670 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 513 + 353", "Answer": "A: 866", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n13 + 50 = 63\n800 + 63 = 863\n863 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 568 + 968", "Answer": "A: 1536", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n60 + 60 = 120\n1400 + 120 = 1520\n1520 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 386", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n70 + 80 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 193 + 367", "Answer": "A: 560", "Explanation": "190 + 360 = 550\n3 + 7 = 10\n550 + 10 = 560"}
{"Question": "Q: 189 + 960", "Answer": "A: 1149", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 885 + 351", "Answer": "A: 1236", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n80 + 50 = 130\n1100 + 130 = 1230\n1230 + 5 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 838 + 133", "Answer": "A: 971", "Explanation": "800 + 30 = 830\n8 + 30 = 38\n830 + 38 = 868\n868 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 619 + 659", "Answer": "A: 1278", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n19 + 50 = 69\n1200 + 69 = 1269\n1269 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 466 + 373", "Answer": "A: 839", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 268", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n40 + 60 = 100\n9 + 8 = 17\n900 + 100 = 1000\n1000 + 17"}
{"Question": "Q: 965 + 378", "Answer": "A: 1343", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n60 + 70 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 5 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 422 + 897", "Answer": "A: 1319", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n20 + 90 = 110\n1200 + 110 = 1310\n1310 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 357 + 459", "Answer": "A: 816", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n50 + 50 = 100\n7 + 9 = 16\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 836 + 903", "Answer": "A: 1739", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 3 = 33\n1700 + 33 = 1733\n1733 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 940 + 554", "Answer": "A: 1494", "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n40 + 50 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 842 + 924", "Answer": "A: 1766", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 20 = 60\n1700 + 60 = 1760\n1760 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 323", "Answer": "A: 445", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n20 + 20 = 40\n2 + 3 = 5\n400 + 40 = 440\n440 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 788 + 638", "Answer": "A: 1426", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n80 + 30 = 110\n1300 + 110 = 1410\n1410 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 744", "Answer": "A: 1169", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n20 + 40 = 60\n1100 + 60 = 1160\n1160 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 231 + 123", "Answer": "A: 354", "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n30 + 20 = 50\n300 + 50 = 350\n350 + 1 = 351\n351 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 335 + 494", "Answer": "A: 829", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 5 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 856 + 723", "Answer": "A: 1579", "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n50 + 20 = 70\n1500 + 70 = 1570\n1570 + 6 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 469 + 519", "Answer": "A: 988", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n60 + 10 = 70\n9 + 9 = 18\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 18"}
{"Question": "Q: 375 + 870", "Answer": "A: 1245", "Explanation": "300 + 800 = 1100\n70 + 70 = 140\n1100 + 140 = 1240\n1240 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 686 + 103", "Answer": "A: 789", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700  \n86 + 3 = 89  \n700 + 89"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 501", "Answer": "A: 673", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n70 + 0 = 70\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 2 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 417 + 235", "Answer": "A: 652", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n10 + 30 = 40\n600 + 40 = 640\n640 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 278 + 771", "Answer": "A: 1049", "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n70 + 70 = 140\n900 + 140 = 1040\n1040 + 8 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 591 + 940", "Answer": "A: 1531", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n90 + 40 = 130\n1400 + 130 = 1530\n1530 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 328 + 587", "Answer": "A: 915", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n20 + 80 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 8 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 390 + 555", "Answer": "A: 945", "Explanation": "300 + 500 = 800\n90 + 50 = 140\n800 + 140 = 940\n940 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 209", "Answer": "A: 906", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 0 = 90\n7 + 9 = 16\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 984 + 162", "Answer": "A: 1146", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 4 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 502", "Answer": "A: 684", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 2 = 82\n600 + 82 = 682\n682 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 420 + 262", "Answer": "A: 682", "Explanation": "400 + 200 = 600\n20 + 60 = 80\n600 + 80 = 680\n680 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 207 + 290", "Answer": "A: 497", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400  \n7 + 90 = 97  \n400 + 97  "}
{"Question": "Q: 525 + 996", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 6 = 1516\n1516 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 830 + 354", "Answer": "A: 1184", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n30 + 50 = 80\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 156 + 731", "Answer": "A: 887", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n50 + 30 = 80\n800 + 80 = 880\n880 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 997", "Answer": "A: 1780", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n80 + 90 = 170\n1600 + 170 = 1770\n1770 + 10 = 1780\n1780"}
{"Question": "Q: 209 + 547", "Answer": "A: 756", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n9 + 40 = 49\n700 + 49 = 749\n749 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 125 + 743", "Answer": "A: 868", "Explanation": "100 + 700 = 800\n20 + 40 = 60\n800 + 60 = 860\n860 + 5 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 934 + 263", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n30 + 60 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 627 + 768", "Answer": "A: 1395", "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n20 + 60 = 80  \n7 + 8 = 15  \n1300 + 80 = 1380  \n1380 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 684 + 607", "Answer": "A: 1291", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n80 + 0 = 80\n4 + 7 = 11\n1200 + 80 = 1280\n1280 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 457 + 404", "Answer": "A: 861", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n50 + 4 = 54\n800 + 54 = 854\n854 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 874 + 213", "Answer": "A: 1087", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n4 + 3 = 7\n1000 + 80 = 1080\n1080 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 302 + 351", "Answer": "A: 653", "Explanation": "300 + 350 = 650\n2 + 1 = 3\n650 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 196 + 890", "Answer": "A: 1086", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900  \n90 + 6 = 96  \n900 + 96 = 996  \n996 + 90 = 1086  "}
{"Question": "Q: 993 + 110", "Answer": "A: 1103", "Explanation": "900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 3 = 993\n993 + 100 = 1093\n1093 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 530 + 272", "Answer": "A: 802", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n30 + 70 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 882 + 888", "Answer": "A: 1770", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n80 + 80 = 160\n2 + 8 = 10\n1600 + 160 = 1760\n1760 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 967 + 265", "Answer": "A: 1232", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n60 + 60 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 7\n1220 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 122 + 410", "Answer": "A: 532", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n20 + 10 = 30\n500 + 30 = 530\n530 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 730 + 291", "Answer": "A: 1021", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 90 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 628 + 962", "Answer": "A: 1590", "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n20 + 60 = 80\n1500 + 80 = 1580\n1580 + 10\n\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 906 + 632", "Answer": "A: 1538", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500  \n6 + 30 = 36  \n1500 + 36 = 1536  \n1536 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 566 + 194", "Answer": "A: 760", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n600 + 150 = 750  \n750 + 10 = 760  \n760 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 433 + 541", "Answer": "A: 974", "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n30 + 40 = 70\n3 + 1 = 4\n900 + 70 = 970\n970 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 394", "Answer": "A: 981", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800  \n80 + 90 = 170  \n800 + 170 = 970  \n970 + 7 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 180 + 603", "Answer": "A: 783", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n80 + 3 = 83\n700 + 83"}
{"Question": "Q: 749 + 807", "Answer": "A: 1556", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n40 + 7 = 47  \n1500 + 47 = 1547  \n1547 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 867 + 158", "Answer": "A: 1025", "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n60 + 50 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 7 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 256 + 450", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "250 + 450 = 700\n6 + 0 = 6\n700 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 181 + 270", "Answer": "A: 451", "Explanation": "180 + 270 = 450\n450 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 617 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1026", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n10 + 9 = 19\n1000 + 19 = 1019\n1019 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 771 + 253", "Answer": "A: 1024", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n70 + 50 = 120\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 1 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 609 + 321", "Answer": "A: 930", "Explanation": "600 + 300 = 900\n9 + 20 = 29\n900 + 29 = 929\n929 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 739 + 105", "Answer": "A: 844", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n30 + 5 = 35\n800 + 35 = 835\n835 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 559 + 794", "Answer": "A: 1353", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n9 + 4 = 13\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 13"}
{"Question": "Q: 112 + 594", "Answer": "A: 706", "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n10 + 90 = 100  \n600 + 100 = 700  \n700 + 4  \n700 + 6  "}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 416", "Answer": "A: 825", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800\n9 + 10 = 19\n800 + 19 = 819\n819 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 227 + 809", "Answer": "A: 1036", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n20 + 9 = 29\n1000 + 29 = 1029\n1029 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 475 + 362", "Answer": "A: 837", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 60 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 5 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 338 + 326", "Answer": "A: 664", "Explanation": "300 + 300 = 600\n30 + 20 = 50\n8 + 6 = 14\n600 + 50 = 650\n650 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 541 + 935", "Answer": "A: 1476", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 734 + 235", "Answer": "A: 969", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 5 = 9\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 554 + 543", "Answer": "A: 1097", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n4 + 3 = 7  \n1000 + 90 = 1090  \n1090 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 727 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1362", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 7\n1350 + 5\n"}
{"Question": "Q: 561 + 788", "Answer": "A: 1349", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 80 = 140\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 1 + 8 = 1349"}
{"Question": "Q: 140 + 950", "Answer": "A: 1090", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n40 + 50 = 90\n1000 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 425 + 772", "Answer": "A: 1197", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n25 + 70 = 95\n1100 + 95 = 1195\n1195 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 488 + 970", "Answer": "A: 1458", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 70 = 150\n1300 + 150 = 1450\n1450 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 520 + 535", "Answer": "A: 1055", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n20 + 30 = 50\n1000 + 50 = 1050\n1050 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 527 + 994", "Answer": "A: 1521", "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n20 + 90 = 110\n1400 + 110 = 1510\n1510 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 229 + 511", "Answer": "A: 740", "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n20 + 10 = 30\n700 + 30 = 730\n730 + 9 + 1 = 740"}
{"Question": "Q: 985 + 887", "Answer": "A: 1872", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n80 + 80 = 160\n5 + 7 = 12\n1700 + 160 = 1860\n1860 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 662 + 892", "Answer": "A: 1554", "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n60 + 90 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 751 + 979", "Answer": "A: 1730", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600\n50 + 70 = 120\n1600 + 120 = 1720\n1720 + 10 = 1730\n1730 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 844 + 915", "Answer": "A: 1759", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n40 + 10 = 50\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 765 + 859", "Answer": "A: 1624", "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n60 + 50 = 110\n5 + 9 = 14\n1500 + 110 = 1610\n1610 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 667 + 539", "Answer": "A: 1206", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 7 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 654 + 206", "Answer": "A: 860", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n50 + 6 = 56\n800 + 56 = 856\n856 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 130 + 441", "Answer": "A: 571", "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n30 + 40 = 70\n500 + 70 = 570\n570 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 575 + 767", "Answer": "A: 1342", "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 70 = 140\n5 + 7 = 12\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 866 + 279", "Answer": "A: 1145", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000  \n60 + 70 = 130  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 9 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 492 + 813", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n2 + 3 = 5\n1300 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 501 + 252", "Answer": "A: 753", "Explanation": "500 + 250 = 750\n1 + 2 = 3\n750 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 783 + 710", "Answer": "A: 1493", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n80 + 10 = 90\n1400 + 90 = 1490\n1490 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 992 + 634", "Answer": "A: 1626", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n90 + 30 = 120\n2 + 4 = 6\n1500 + 120 = 1620\n1620 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 752 + 642", "Answer": "A: 1394", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n50 + 40 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 2 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 409 + 753", "Answer": "A: 1162", "Explanation": "400 + 700 = 1100\n9 + 50 = 59\n1100 + 59 = 1159\n1159 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 831 + 640", "Answer": "A: 1471", "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n30 + 40 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 450 + 160", "Answer": "A: 610", "Explanation": "450 + 100 = 550\n550 + 60 = 610"}
{"Question": "Q: 925 + 327", "Answer": "A: 1252", "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n5 + 7 = 12\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 586 + 630", "Answer": "A: 1216", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n80 + 30 = 110\n1100 + 110 = 1210\n1210 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 870 + 955", "Answer": "A: 1825", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n70 + 50 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 383 + 236", "Answer": "A: 619", "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 30 = 110\n3 + 6 = 9\n500 + 110 = 610\n610 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 446 + 389", "Answer": "A: 835", "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 80 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 6 = 826\n826 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 480 + 613", "Answer": "A: 1093", "Explanation": "480 + 600 = 1080  \n80 + 10 = 90  \n1080 + 10 = 1090  \n1090 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 141", "Answer": "A: 799", "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n50 + 40 = 90\n8 + 1 = 9\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 363 + 190", "Answer": "A: 553", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n60 + 90 = 150\n400 + 150 = 550\n550 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 408 + 991", "Answer": "A: 1399", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n8 + 90 = 98\n1300 + 98 = 1398\n1398 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 786 + 409", "Answer": "A: 1195", "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n80 + 0 = 80\n6 + 9 = 15\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 138 + 692", "Answer": "A: 830", "Explanation": "100 + 600 = 700\n30 + 90 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 10 = 830\n830"}
{"Question": "Q: 230 + 642", "Answer": "A: 872", "Explanation": "200 + 600 = 800\n30 + 40 = 70\n800 + 70 = 870\n870 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 743 + 708", "Answer": "A: 1451", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 0 = 40\n1400 + 40 = 1440\n1440 + 3 = 1443\n1443 +"}
{"Question": "Q: 653 + 534", "Answer": "A: 1187", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n50 + 30 = 80\n3 + 4 = 7\n1100 + 80 = 1180\n1180 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 345 + 112", "Answer": "A: 457", "Explanation": "300 + 100 = 400\n40 + 10 = 50\n5 + 2 = 7\n400 + 50 = 450\n450 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 835 + 929", "Answer": "A: 1764", "Explanation": "800 + 900 = 1700\n30 + 20 = 50\n5 + 9 = 14\n1700 + 50 = 1750\n1750 + 14"}
{"Question": "Q: 871 + 815", "Answer": "A: 1686", "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n70 + 10 = 80\n1 + 5 = 6\n1600 + 80 = 1680\n1680 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 860 + 399", "Answer": "A: 1259", "Explanation": "800 + 300 = 1100\n60 + 90 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 910 + 131", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n10 + 30 = 40\n1000 + 40 = 1040\n1040 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 970 + 220", "Answer": "A: 1190", "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n70 + 20 = 90\n1100 + 90"}
{"Question": "Q: 720 + 635", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "700 + 600 = 1300\n20 + 30 = 50\n1300 + 50 = 1350\n1350 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 509 + 547", "Answer": "A: 1056", "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n9 + 40 = 49\n1000 + 49 = 1049\n1049 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 172 + 902", "Answer": "A: 1074", "Explanation": "100 + 900 = 1000\n70 + 2 = 72\n1000 + 72 = 1072\n1072 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 294 + 877", "Answer": "A: 1171", "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n90 + 70 = 160\n4 + 7 = 11\n1000 + 160 = 1160\n1160 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 516 + 669", "Answer": "A: 1185", "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100  \n16 + 60 = 76  \n1100 + 76 = 1176  \n1176 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 269 + 227", "Answer": "A: 496", "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n60 + 20 = 80\n9 + 7 = 16\n400 + 80 = 480\n480 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 741 + 749", "Answer": "A: 1490", "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 40 = 80\n1 + 9 = 10\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 489 + 992", "Answer": "A: 1481", "Explanation": "400 + 900 = 1300\n80 + 90 = 170\n1300 + 170 = 1470\n1470 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 903 + 402", "Answer": "A: 1305", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300  \n3 + 2 = 5  \n1300 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 828 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1256", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n20 + 20 = 40\n1200 + 40 = 1240\n1240 + 8 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 600 + 472", "Answer": "A: 1072", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n70 + 2 = 72\n1000 + 72"}
{"Question": "Q: 775 + 589", "Answer": "A: 1364", "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n70 + 80 = 150\n1200 + 150 = 1350\n1350 + 5 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 258", "Answer": "A: 834", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n70 + 50 = 120\n700 + 120 = 820\n820 + 6\n826 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 182 + 267", "Answer": "A: 449", "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300  \n80 + 60 = 140  \n300 + 140 = 440  \n440 + 9  "}
{"Question": "Q: 658 + 652", "Answer": "A: 1310", "Explanation": "600 + 600 = 1200\n50 + 50 = 100\n8 + 2 = 10\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 506 + 177", "Answer": "A: 683", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n6 + 70 = 76\n600 + 76 = 676\n676 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 753 + 974", "Answer": "A: 1727", "Explanation": "700 + 900 = 1600  \n50 + 70 = 120  \n1600 + 120 = 1720  \n1720 + 3 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 918 + 481", "Answer": "A: 1399", "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n18 + 80 = 98\n1300 + 98 = 1398\n1398 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 857 + 498", "Answer": "A: 1355", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 90 = 140\n7 + 8 = 15\n1200 + 140 = 1340\n1340 + 15"}
{"Question": "Q: 340 + 464", "Answer": "A: 804", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n40 + 60 = 100\n700 + 100 = 800\n800 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 793 + 112", "Answer": "A: 905", "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n90 + 10 = 100\n800 + 100 = 900\n900 + 3 + 2"}
{"Question": "Q: 894 + 280", "Answer": "A: 1174", "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n90 + 80 = 170\n1000 + 170 = 1170\n1170 + 4"}
{"Question": "Q: 972 + 835", "Answer": "A: 1807", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n70 + 30 = 100\n1700 + 100 = 1800\n2 + 5 = 7\n1800 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 973 + 665", "Answer": "A: 1638", "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n70 + 60 = 130\n1500 + 130 = 1630\n1630 + 8"}
{"Question": "Q: 421 + 476", "Answer": "A: 897", "Explanation": "400 + 400 = 800  \n20 + 70 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 1 + 6"}
{"Question": "Q: 613 + 428", "Answer": "A: 1041", "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000  \n10 + 20 = 30  \n3 + 8 = 11  \n1000 + 30 = 1030  \n1030 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 198 + 379", "Answer": "A: 577", "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n90 + 70 = 160\n400 + 160 = 560\n560 + 8 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 379 + 757", "Answer": "A: 1136", "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n70 + 50 = 120\n9 + 7 = 16\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 16"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 285", "Answer": "A: 982", "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n90 + 80 = 170\n7 + 5 = 12\n800 + 170 = 970\n970 + 12"}
{"Question": "Q: 834 + 477", "Answer": "A: 1311", "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n30 + 70 = 100\n4 + 7 = 11\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 11"}
{"Question": "Q: 144 + 817", "Answer": "A: 961", "Explanation": "100 + 800 = 900\n40 + 10 = 50\n900 + 50 = 950\n950 + 4 \n950 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 770 + 310", "Answer": "A: 1080", "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n70 + 10 = 80\n1000 + 80"}
{"Question": "Q: 392 + 485", "Answer": "A: 877", "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n90 + 80 = 170\n700 + 170 = 870\n870 + 7 = 877"}
{"Question": "Q: 736 + 281", "Answer": "A: 1017", "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n30 + 80 = 110\n900 + 110 = 1010\n1010 + 6 + 1"}
{"Question": "Q: 956 + 879", "Answer": "A: 1835", "Explanation": "900 + 800 = 1700\n50 + 70 = 120\n1700 + 120 = 1820\n1820 + 6 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 680 + 549", "Answer": "A: 1229", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n80 + 40 = 120\n1100 + 120 = 1220\n1220 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 542 + 178", "Answer": "A: 720", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n40 + 70 = 110\n600 + 110 = 710\n710 + 10 = 720\n720 + 0"}
{"Question": "Q: 931 + 716", "Answer": "A: 1647", "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n30 + 10 = 40\n1 + 6 = 7\n1600 + 40 = 1640\n1640 + 7"}
{"Question": "Q: 532 + 457", "Answer": "A: 989", "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n30 + 50 = 80\n2 + 7 = 9\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 697 + 565", "Answer": "A: 1262", "Explanation": "600 + 500 = 1100\n90 + 60 = 150\n1100 + 150 = 1250\n1250 + 7 + 5"}
{"Question": "Q: 573 + 369", "Answer": "A: 942", "Explanation": "500 + 300 = 800\n70 + 60 = 130\n800 + 130 = 930\n930 + 9 = 939\n939 + 3"}
{"Question": "Q: 576 + 174", "Answer": "A: 750", "Explanation": "500 + 100 = 600\n\n70 + 70 = 140\n\n6 + 4 = 10\n\n600 + 140 = 740\n\n740 + 10"}
{"Question": "Q: 587 + 269", "Answer": "A: 856", "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n80 + 60 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 7\n840 + 9"}
{"Question": "Q: 301 + 607", "Answer": "A: 908", "Explanation": "300 + 600 = 900\n1 + 7 = 8\n900 + 8"}
